Chapter 2173 – Demons of the Black Pagodas

Woosh! Woosh!

Two giant plumes of water erupted in the muddy yellow Emperor Bone Sea. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei flew into the Emperor Bone Sea at the entrance of the abyssal ritual smelting trial.

Along the way, Lin Ming felt an intense tearing force pass over him. The surroundings began to rapidly change. Lin Ming knew that he was passing through a transmission array and quickly held onto Sheng Mei’s hand to avoid them being separated by the tearing force of the transmission array.

This tearing force grew stronger and stronger. Although Sheng Mei and Lin Ming had formidable divine souls, it was impossible for them to be immune to this type of brutal tearing force. But, as Lin Ming felt the strength of this storm, he was left secretly dumbfounded. If an abyssal at the Empyrean level or below were to enter it, their soul would be crushed and torn apart by the massive force and they would perish before they even made it to the other end of the transmission array.

This was the might possessed by the highest echelon of mystic realm in the entire universe. Not to mention the emperor force field that was gathered in this mystic realm, just the space storm here weren’t something that could be compared to those of the 33 Heavens. The space here was exceedingly stable, but at the same time, once it shattered, the storm that erupted would be hundreds of times more terrifying!

This sort of disorienting scene continued for an unknown period of time. Lin Ming felt his body lighten and in the next moment he arrived in a strange space.

Because of their powerful divine souls, the moment they exited the transmission array, they immediately rid themselves of their dizziness to clearly see the scene in front of them.

In the middle of this space was a vast and endless road. This road was shrouded in gray fog that seemed completely stagnant, and carried with it an aura of deathly stillness.

On both sides of this road were great towering pagodas. Each pagoda was a thousand feet high and stood tall like a black monument.

Lin Ming gazed at one of these pagodas. This pagoda had 12 floors and gates that was 100 feet high. The gates were tightly closed shut and the relief of a three-headed and six-armed demon god was carved into it. This demon bit down onto a demonic sword.

From behind the great gates, Lin Ming could faintly feel a mysterious and extraordinary aura sealed within, one that left the heart shocked.

“Are these the burial grounds of the great demon emperors that died in ancient times 100 billion years ago?”

Lin Ming suddenly asked on a whim. There were so many demon pagodas; could each one be the grave of a demon emperor?

As Lin Ming was thinking about this, he could feel the Magic Cube suddenly start trembling from within his inner world.

“Mm?”

Lin Mig was startled. “Magic Cube?”

“What is it?”

Sheng Mei’s thoughts were connected to Lin Ming’s. She looked towards him. Then, with a thought, Lin Ming summoned a grandmist force field that blocked out the surrounding space. He waved his hand and the dark gray Magic Cube appeared in the world, slowly revolving above his palm.

“Magic Cube?”

After accompanying Lin Ming these past several years, Sheng Mei already knew the name that Lin Ming had given the Magic Cube. She also recalled the myth of the Stone of Eternal Life passed down amongst the spiritas.

“The Magic Cube gently trembled just now. For a brief moment, it transmitted a strange aura. There is something extraordinary happening with this place…”

At this moment, Lin Ming felt the Magic Cube in his hand heat up a little. This made him even more wary, because Jiu’er was hiding in the Magic Cube space.

Lin Ming felt that the Magic Cube space was the safest place possible. Thus, he hid Jiu’er inside and had Ruby look after her.

After hearing Lin Ming’s words, a thoughtful look crossed Sheng Mei’s face. “According to the Demon God’s Tomb jade slip, there are many ancient demon emperors buried here. After they died, their remnant souls also remained here for eternity without being destroyed. Could it be that the Magic Cube had some reaction because it resonated with these powerful soul auras?”

Sheng Mei’s speculation was reasonable. In fact, since the Magic Cube was the ultimate divine tool when it came to the aspect of souls, it could have suddenly been excited upon encountering so many formidable souls.

However, these ancient demon emperors were far too amazing. Even just a single remnant soul would be too difficult to deal with.

“But no matter what, just be careful.”

Lin Ming put away the Magic Cube and took down the isolating grandmist force field.

But the moment that Lin Ming removed the grandmist force field, he suddenly heard a deafening roar coming from outside!

Hou - !

Hou - !

Hou - !

Horrifying roars filled with the air and reverberated in space. These roars left the ears tingling with numbness.

“Hahaha! To think such delicious food has delivered itself to my door once more!”

A crazed and maddened voice echoed out. What this voice spoke in was the ancient abyssal language. If it weren’t for Lin Ming having obtained many of Famine’s memories he wouldn’t have been able to understand it.

“What!?”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. He originally thought that the ancient demon emperors here had all died off and never expected that there could be one that emitted such a brutal roar.

He stretched out a hand to reach for the Black Dragon Spear. And at this time, not too far away, he saw a 12 level pagoda emit a dim black flash of light.

Gudong!

With a loud bang, the front gates of the pagoda fiercely trembled.

From behind the great gates, loud rumbling sounds echoed out. These were the sounds of thick chains being dragged across the ground, as if some ancient beast that was wrapped in chains wanted to rush out.

“This is a king of the ancient demon race?”

Lin Ming looked at the violently shaking gates of the black pagoda and the tremendous impact force that seemed to be striking it like a falling star. The vibrations grew increasingly fierce, as if the door would be broken open.

However, in that moment, the demon relief on the gates began to shine. The eyes of the demon relief radiated with a blood red light and the countless intricate runes engraved atop the relief started to emit a dazzling light.

Then, a pitiful cry echoed out from behind the gates.

“Ahh!”

That ancient demon emperor seemed to suffer some agonizing form of suppression. He fiercely struggled and roared. Then, the runes on the gate flashed once more and the roar became increasingly weak before eventually devolving into hateful curses. Eventually, even those curses subsided to nothing and the entire black pagoda returned to tranquility once more, as if nothing happened.

This small interlude caused Lin Ming’s heart to skip a beat. He stared at the demon relief on the gates of the pagoda and a strange thought appeared in his mind.

The style of this demon relief as well as the carving technique were completely similar to what he saw in the underground cavern!

The only difference was that in the underground cavern, the demon relief had a bronze coffin in its mouth. But, the demon relief on the black pagoda held a demonic sword in its mouth instead.

The black pagoda and underground cavern had similar demon reliefs. But, one was used to refine a demon bone and the other was used to seal in a demon…

With such a scene, one couldn’t help but produce some associations.

“What are you thinking of?”

Lin Ming asked Sheng Mei as he continued to eye the demon relief.

Sheng Mei said, “I’ve thought of many things, but none of them are good…”

The ancient bronze coffin filled with blood, the demon locked in the black pagoda, these things caused Sheng Mei to feel as if there was something bloody and hideous hidden in the dark.

This was not the first time that the Demon God’s Tomb had opened, but these things she saw hadn’t been recorded in the Demon God’s Tomb jade slip. Only by entering deep into the Demon God’s Tomb could one see such scenes…

“Let’s continue onwards. We’ve already come this far. Although peerless demon emperors from ancient times are buried here, all that is left of them are their remnant souls. Even if one of them manages to free itself, we can still fight them.”

The Lin Ming of today was no longer the same person he had been before. He was no longer a genius of the younger generation, but one of the characters who truly stood at the highest levels of the universe.

Even if they were ancient demon emperors, it was still impossible for them to be Beyond Divinity.

And even if they were at the limits of a True Divinity, after having been dead for so many years and only having a wisp of their remnant soul and will remaining, their strength would inevitably be limited. Lin Ming had full confidence he could deal with all incoming challengers.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei pushed forwards. On the side of the road, demon pagodas appeared one after another.

Some demon pagodas were extremely calm, even emitting an aura of complete deathly stillness, as if they were ancient graves that had never been moved for all of eternity.

But some demon pagodas began to emit earth-shaking roars as Lin Ming and Sheng Mei approached.

“Flesh and blood! Fresh flesh and blood!”

“Me! Me! Give it to me!”

These voices were filled with madness, loneliness, despair, and utter hostility and hatred. They didn’t seem to resemble the voices of ancient peerless powerhouses at all, but rather like hungry ghosts that had gone insane.

In Lin Ming’s impression, even if these ancient peerless powerhouses were part of the cruel and barbaric demon race, they would still reveal a grand and majestic aura of a great emperor once they obtained absolute strength; they wouldn’t resemble crazed beasts and starving ghosts.

Perhaps those that were sealed in the black pagodas weren’t ancient demon race emperors at all, but some evil and depraved souls.

This thought flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. It was also his only guess.

Chapter 2174 – The Dark Altar

The various clues and traces spread throughout the Demon God’s Tomb caused Lin Ming to form all sorts of suspicions in his mind. As for whether any of his suspicions were true, he would have to see with his own eyes to find out.

But at this time, Lin Ming discovered that Sheng Mei had slowed her pace. He turned to see Sheng Mei with a strange look on her face.

“Mm? Are you alright?”

Sheng Mei’s actions left Lin Ming startled. Although this underground graveyard was filled with an emperor force field and soul pressure, with her cultivation she should be more than able to withstand it.

“Something is… strange. I thought that my spiritual sea was touched by something just now, as if something was summoning me… but as I tried to feel it more carefully, I couldn’t find anything at all…”

Sheng Mei grasped her chest, carefully spreading her sense all around her. Yet, that feeling had already disappeared.

When her spiritual sea had been touched, it was an extremely light touch. But, Sheng Mei’s soul force was already powerful to an incredible degree, so it was impossible for her to mistake this feeling. It truly had occurred.

“Something touched your spiritual sea?” Lin Ming said, surprised. He couldn’t figure out a reason either.

“It’s fine. Let’s continue onwards. If I have this feeling again, I should be able to understand more things about it.”

As Sheng Mei spoke, the fog in front of them began to gently shake. The fog separated and a dark figure slowly appeared. This was an octopus-like monster with thick six limbs, and a soft and wet body that was covered in green spots.

“Awo!”

The monster let out a thunderous roar to reveal rows of sharp and dense fangs. “More living beings! There were several that came before but I didn’t manage to catch any of them. Now, you are all mine!”

The monster spoke in the ancient abyssal language. Its grotesque green eyes stared straight at Sheng Mei as drool began leaking out of its jaws. “A woman with a pure bloodline, the best type of food, hahaha!”

The monster cackled and threw itself onto Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

Lin Ming’s complexion turned icy cold. He took a step forwards and thrust out the Black Dragon Spear.

Peng!

Lin Ming’s strength surged and a wild explosion formed atop the tip of the Black Dragon Spear. The surrounding fog began to stir about like a storm.

The green tentacle demon cried out in pain. It was struck away by Lin Ming’s immense strength and one of its tentacles was severed!

The monster was frightened. It never thought that Lin Ming who only had an Empyrean level cultivation would actually possess such horrifying strength.

It was now afraid. Then, it turned around and fled.

But Lin Ming didn’t give it a chance to escape. He stepped forwards, his body moving like ghosts and gods as he instantly appeared in front of the demon.

Ca!

The Black Dragon Spear slashed downwards. Like a scythe, the unstoppable blood red spear light sundered the monster in half!

Puff!

Blood rained down. This blood was extremely thick and nearly pitch black in color, like the blood that was in the ancient bronze coffin after having been sealed away for countless years.

As the black blood splashed out, a wisp of remnant soul rose up, seeming to want to escape.

Lin Ming’s fist came crashing out.

The remnant soul blew apart and turned into power of demon gods that began slowly dissipating. Lin Ming waved his hand, summoning the Swallowing Laws to completely absorb the strength of this remnant soul.

In these past years, Lin Ming had absorbed a great deal of the power of demon gods. It was enough for him to reach the limits of an Empyrean.

However, having sufficient energy was only one part of the equation; he needed enough time to digest it. Lin Ming needed to go into seclusion for several dozen years in order to steadily break into the Empyrean limit.

But, he didn’t have the time.

“Perhaps that monster just now was formed from the bloody infernal energy here and the remnant soul of some ancient demon emperor.” Lin Ming put away the Black Dragon Spear and glanced at the black blood that was scattered over the ground.

Although the emperors of the ancient demon race were powerful, after having devolved into such a bizarre blood monster, their strength was only comparably to the weakest of True Divinities.

“Let’s continue. I wonder if we will meet any living True Divinities from the Flood Alliance or Deep Alliance here…”

Upon mentioning the Empyrean level abyssals of the Deep Alliance that died, Sheng Mei felt the dark clouds in her heart become thicker and heavier. Even now, she and Lin Ming still couldn’t figure out why all those abyssals had died.

As they moved forwards, they encountered several more blood monsters along the way. These monsters all possessed the remnant souls of ancient demons.

It seemed that within the Emperor Bone Sea, only the most powerful demons were sealed away in the black pagodas. The weaker ones were scattered out in all directions and some of them eventually formed these corpse devils.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were a union of strength upon strength; they were an irresistible force as they moved forwards.

They didn’t know how far they walked forwards, but at some time, a great muddy yellow river appeared in front of them.

The river roiled with great billowing waves, and yet it didn’t make a single sound of splashing water. With such a macabre deathly silence, this strange feeling caused Lin Ming and Sheng Mei to pause their step.

This vast deathly still river reminded Lin Ming of the fabled Yellow Springs River.

The road between the demon pagodas traversed the river, like a black and red rainbow.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei stepped atop the river, flying beneath the rainbow. The river waters were dark yellow, and seemed as if they would dissolve any flesh and blood that fell in.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei didn’t know how long they flew for, but eventually they passed the river to reach the opposite shore.

In the legends of the mortal worlds, the other shore of the Yellow Springs River was filled with life and vibrant colors, flowers of all hues. Yet here, the other side of the river was still barren desolateness.

“There’s something in front of us…”

Sheng Mei’s heart stirred and she sent Lin Ming a sound transmission.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. Through the light gray fog, he could see vague shadows at the end of his field of vision.

As he probed further with his sense, he could make out a black altar.

And not too far away from the black altar were five similar altars.

The six altars formed a six-sided star, and each altar was at the end of one of the star’s points.

And around these altars stood three demon pagodas.

The demon pagodas were arranged in a zigzagging pattern around the black altars; all extremely far from each other.

These demon pagodas were all taller than ones Lin Ming had seen before. Along the way here, the demon pagodas that Lin Ming saw had 12 levels, 15 levels, and 18 levels was already the limit.

But the demon pagodas in front of him each had 30 levels or above.

Respectively, these three pagodas had 30 levels, 33 levels, and 36 levels.

The black gates at the base of the demon pagodas were also much larger. At the same time, the gates were also engraved with demon reliefs.

Although the design of the reliefs was similar, the engravings were clearly filled with a much greater power. Just by looking at them, one felt as if their souls would be swallowed, as if the demon reliefs were all alive.

Would ancient demon emperors also be buried in these three exceedingly tall pagodas?

It should be… the Master of the Demon God’s Tomb that was buried here, right…?

If the height of a pagoda was proportional to the strength of the demon sealed within, then the taller the pagoda, the more powerful the demon was. If so, then these three demon pagodas were on a whole different level from the hundreds of demon pagodas he had seen on his way here.

To suddenly increased by over 10 levels, these new pagodas were almost twice the height of the previous ones.

If so, then was it possible that those hundreds of pagodas he saw before had entombed ancient True Divinity level demon emperors from a span of 100 billion years? And as for these three exceedingly tall pagodas, they actually contained existences Beyond Divinity?

The Dark Abyss had a history of 100 billion years. If it was said that three Beyond Divinity level abyssals were born at some time, then Lin Ming wouldn’t be surprised, and instead think that this number wasn’t high at all. After all, the primal god race had produced two Beyond Divinity level existences.

“Lin Ming…” Sheng Mei stared at these altars and the high pagodas. She said in a soft sound transmission, “When we came to these altars, I felt that summoning feeling appear again…”

“Oh?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. If it was as he thought, then these six altars were where the abyssal ritual took place. The six altars each separately represented the six ceremonial rites books!

The abyssals that flocked to the Demon God’s Tomb all dreamed that they could one day pass the abyssal ritual and become totem level abyssals.

Lin Ming’s original plan here was to carry out the abyssal ritual. But today, as he stood in front of these six altars and looked upon the dark black sacrificial blood on the altars and the enormous amount of infernal blood energy contained within, he began to hesitate.

He and Sheng Mei had brought the three ceremonial rites books to this final step; it seemed as if their decision to continue was already made for them. After all, whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, they were each confident that they could pass the abyssal ritual. If they couldn’t pass this test, then there was likely no other abyssal that could.

However, obtaining everything like this seemed far too simple. And with all the ominously foreboding scenes they saw before this, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei naturally wouldn’t recklessly rush onto an altar.

Sheng Mei’s inexplicable feeling and the beating of the Magic Cube caused Lin Ming to raise his guard.

As he sensed the Magic Cube in his inner world, he could feel it faintly vibrating. But along the way, he still hadn’t discovered any reason for why the Magic Cube could be excited and start to throb.

“We’ve come this far and yet haven’t run into another True Divinity level abyssal…”

Lin Ming said, his voice grim. Had these abyssals all died off? If so, then how had they died?

Where had Deep Child gone?

That mysterious and unfathomable abyssal had always aroused a sense of dread in Lin Ming. Even that incredibly haughty and prideful Great Flood Crown Prince was afraid of Deep Child.

Yet, this sort of abyssal had vanished upon entering the Demon God’s Tomb.

Lin Ming hadn’t seen him in the underground cavern and he didn’t even have a ceremonial rites books. So, where could he have gone?

If someone told him that Deep Child perished somewhere, Lin Ming wouldn’t believe them at all.

Lin Ming even thought that Deep Child had some connection to the Soul Emperor.

“What should we do?” Sheng Mei said, a bit unsure. The various signs they had seen in the Demon God’s Tomb indicated that everything they did was wrapped up in some terrifying plot.

But they had still come here. As the arrival of the apocalypse was descending upon them, they were pushed to this position and could no longer avoid it. They could only welcome these plots and face them head-on.

Lin Ming thought for a moment. At this time, he still couldn’t decide.

As he was lost in his thoughts, a gentle and scholarly voice echoed out from behind them. “You two have already come this far, so how come you haven’t gone up?”

Lin Ming’s mind chilled. He flipped around, the Black Dragon Spear crying as it soared out!

Chapter 2177 – The Terrifying Deep Child

Deep Child’s killing intent became increasingly deep and increasingly profound. And at this time, far on the opposite shores of the Yellow Springs River, several other demon pagodas began to light up with a dim glow!

Seeing these demon pagodas begin to gather energy to send towards Deep Child, at this time, Lin Ming could no longer stand idly by and allow Deep Child’s momentum to climb even higher.

“Attack!”

Lin Ming cried out. Beside him, Sheng Mei also attacked. She grasped her pitch matte black bone sword and silently slashed out. For a time, innumerable black flower petals bloomed atop the sword blade. These flower petals immediately began to wither after they bloomed as they were filled with the Concept of Death.

At the same time, Lin Ming rushed forwards from another side. He activated the strength of his Asura blood without hesitation. Behind him, an Asura war god phantom appeared. He poured all of his energy into the Black Dragon Spear and thrust outwards!

The two attacks were joined together with perfect harmony. They came from two angles that blocked off Deep Child’s evasion paths, and even blocked off the flow of world energy to prevent Deep Child’s momentum growing.

If an ordinary middle True Divinity were to encounter such a strike, they would be at a loss for what to do, and would likely be severely wounded by this joint attack.

However, even though Deep Child was also at the middle True Divinity realm, he only chuckled as he faced Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s combined attack. He didn’t revolve any energy, but all around his body there was actually an invisible ‘potential’!

This sort of ‘potential’ was different from common force fields. It was like the potential of the world, capable of shaking mountains and rivers and affecting the sun and moon!

When this great potential emerged, a horrifying pushing force erupted from Deep Child’s body, like a raging shockwave that spread out in all directions. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were caught up in this strength and felt as if their bodies had smashed into a towering mountain.

Peng!

With a series of loud explosions, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s bodies violently quaked. They felt this unstoppable pushing force wrap over them like a storm. Placed within, they were haplessly blown backwards. Lin Ming felt his blood vitality restlessly tumble in his body. Luckily, with his deep foundation he summoned energy to suppress his roiling blood vitality. However, as he turned around he saw that the corners of Sheng Mei’s lips were already stained with blood.

Lin Ming’s heart tightened. He forcefully reversed his body in the storm and grabbed onto Sheng Mei’s hand. He stabbed the Black Dragon Spear deep into the ground, drawing a line of sparks.

Bang!

Sheng Mei and Lin Ming crashed into the ground. They both felt their blood vitality jumbled into disorder and their meridians injured.

The two of them looked up at Deep Child.

Lin Ming’s eyes were filled with astonishment.

Was Deep Child really only a middle True Divinity?

In that instant, Lin Ming clearly felt that his and Sheng Mei’s joint attack was weakened for the most part by the storm. However, the rest of it had been absorbed by Deep Child!

Deep Child was actually able to absorb the energies from their attack? How had he managed to do this?

“The Soul Emperor still has this sort of cultivation method?”

Lin Ming’s complexion was dark and dignified as he asked Sheng Mei this question with a sound transmission. The Laws he used and the Laws Sheng Mei used had reached an extremely high boundary, so how could they be so easily absorbed?

Even Famine who was skilled in the Swallowing Laws could also swallow dead things or the strength of others through its tentacles; it was impossible to directly swallow an enemy’s attacks like this.

“I don’t know.” Sheng Mei guiltily said as she bit her lips. The Soul Emperor was far too mysterious and too deeply unfathomable. During these years, most of the time, Sheng Mei only obeyed the orders of the Soul Emperor. As for the Soul Emperor’s cultivation methods, she only knew the Holy Scripture Laws.

Although Deep Child could be called her senior-apprentice brother, the truth was that she didn’t understand his hidden depths at all. It was clear from this that Deep Child was much more trusted by the Soul Emperor.

“Are you surprised?” Seeing the shock on Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s face, Deep Child laughed, and he laughed extremely recklessly and freely. “Let me plainly tell you something. No matter what, you two cannot defeat me! This is the disparity of our levels, a disparity that neither of you can make up for! And, what is most pitiful is that you two don’t even know where this disparity is.

“I will give you two one final chance. Be good little children and obediently step onto the dark altar and withstand the baptism of the abyssal ritual! This is an opportunity that others can only dream of! Once you successfully pass the dark ritual, the two of you can become the highest level abyssals in the Dark Abyss, and you will each become one of the rulers of the future world!”

As Deep Child spoke, he slowly drew out his own weapon.

This was a black trident.

This black trident was 15 feet long. Just the end of the trident was three feet wide and the three prongs were wild and savage. The shape of the trident was overly exaggerated and exceedingly hideous and fierce.

“You… passed the abyssal ritual?” Sheng Mei coldly asked. With Deep Child’s strength and his identity, she couldn’t help but develop such a guess.

“Hahaha!” Deep Child cackled. He swayed his neck from side to side as he slowly stepped down from the altar, walking towards Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

“If you want to know whether or not I have passed through the abyssal ritual, why don’t you come up and experience the true abyssal ritual for yourself first?”

Deep Child approached Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, one step at a time.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. He could already confirm that from the moment he appeared in Deep King Road and defeated Sheng Mei with his middle Empyrean cultivation, he had already been targeted by Deep Child. Or, it could be said that he had been targeted by the current ruler of Deep King Road.

His entry into the Demon God’s Tomb was the same as walking into a trap. Whether or not he possessed the Book of Eon and whether or not he came to the Emperor Bone Sea on his own initiative… sooner or later, Deep Child would have found him.

This Deep Child was like a loyal hound personally raised by the Soul Emperor in order to monitor the smelting trial of the Demon God’s Tomb!

Lin Ming had snuck into the Dark Abyss and while he had done so to increase his strength, he had also become prey at the same time…

Now, the only thing that Lin Ming could be thankful for was that his identity as a human had not been discovered by Deep Child.

After all, Deep Child had yet to fully mature and his cultivation and field of vision were limited, thus he hadn’t been able to see through Lin Ming.

However, if the Soul Emperor were to personally arrive, Lin Ming didn’t have the faintest hopes that he could trick him.

But the current problem was that if he didn’t reveal his true self, there would truly be no hope of defeating Deep Child.

Even if he did reveal his true self, the chances of defeating Deep Child were extremely small. And once he did reveal his true self, then the battle here would end with one of them dying; Deep Child would never let him go after that.

In addition, even Sheng Mei would be implicated in his mess. A great catastrophe would descend upon her head and she would suffer the charge of being a traitor.

Seeing Lin Ming’s complexion, Sheng Mei seemed to understand just what Lin Ming was thinking. She said with a sound transmission, “I gave birth to Jiu’er and also erased the spirit mark that the Soul Emperor left in my spiritual sea. At this point, I have already burnt all my escape routes and can only fight to the bitter end. It’s already come to this. If you have any scruples still then toss them aside. You and I must fight with everything we have.

“If we can somehow luckily survive today, then I will follow you to the ends of the earth and the edges of heaven. If we are buried here today, then I will follow you to the Yellow Springs. But no matter what the result is, I have no regrets!”

In such a situation, Sheng Mei’s brief sound transmission touched Lin Ming’s heart.

He was aware that since birth, Sheng Mei was accompanied with infinite sorrow and misery.

Regardless of what she did in the past, regardless of her reluctance or whether or not she was willing to do what she did before, regardless if it was her or Jiu’er, they had already become marks that were deeply ingrained in his life. They could not be erased nor could they be severed.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and slowly clenched his fists. As he looked at Deep Child again, his eyes blazed with a brilliant fighting spirit!

Deep Child’s eyebrow tipped up and he shook his head in regret.

“It looks like… there is no more room for discussion. How stupid of you. I already said that no matter what happens, it is impossible for you to defeat me!”

“You sure speak enough nonsense!”

Lin Ming roared out loud. Energy erupted from his entire body as the power of the Nine Stars began to gather unto him. The Black Dragon Spear came pounding down!

A horrifying strength, like a crashing star, came sweeping down over the world.

Bang!

With an explosion, the eruption of energy turned into an incredibly wild and tyrannical shockwave. Deep Child was caught in the shockwave and sent flying away!

But in the next moment, Deep Child lightly landed on the ground. Lin Ming’s strength and Laws seemed to be completely suppressed. Even his spear light had been absorbed by Deep Child’s bodily protective energy with nothing left behind.

All around Deep Child, the same vague and invisible world potential remained. It seemed as if no amount of strength and no type of ability would be able to destroy this potential.

Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. He was well aware that the might of his strike just now was enough to instantly kill a lower True Divinity, and even weaker True Divinities would be injured.

But against Deep Child, his strike had been easily received and blocked as if it hadn’t taken any energy or effort to do so.

Lin Ming was now using his demon avatar. If he used his true self, his strength could rise by a great deal, but it absolutely wouldn’t double.

Now, Lin Ming began to suspect that even if his strength increased, he still wouldn’t be able to do anything to Deep Child.

“Why is he so strong? He clearly only has a middle True Divinity cultivation!”

Chapter 2178 – Life and Death Crisis

“You two have already used your moves, it should be my turn…”

Deep Child approached Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, one step at a time. He looked at Sheng Mei and smiled, “Junior-apprentice Sister, shouldn’t you try to persuade your little lover here? Or do you plan to stare on helplessly as he dies?”

Just as Deep Child’s voice fell, killing intent erupted from his body.

Bang!

He rushed forwards like gods and ghosts. His trident came smashing down!

Without any trident light, without any recklessly tumbling energy, without even any Law fluctuations, Deep Child’s attack seemed incredibly ordinary. However, every movement and action that Deep Child took was followed with the potential of the world. Facing him was like facing an entire world!

Lin Ming saw Deep Child hurtle towards him and felt the surrounding space immediately lock tight around him. It was like he was placed in a space cage, without any direction to dodge in.

As Lin Ming watched Deep Child’s trident come pounding down, he roared out loud and brought the Black Dragon Spear crossing in front of his body.

Kacha!

The trident and Black Dragon Spear collided. The Black Dragon Spear bent deeply downwards, completely bent as bone slices wildly flew off!

In that moment, Lin Ming felt his eyes tingle with numbness as if his bones had broken. Deep Child’s strength had reached an unimaginable degree!

“Not bad!”

Deep Child held the trident with one hand and flew upwards. With his right knee bent, he struck Lin Ming’s chest.

Peng!

Because he was locked down by the space cage and also suppressed by Deep Child’s immense strength, Lin Ming wasn’t able to resist this strike at all. The moment that Deep Child’s knee struck his chest, it was like a trillion jin hammer crashed into him. His ribs shattered and his organs jumbled about. He spat out a mouthful of blood as he was sent tumbling backwards!

Lin Ming plummeted onto a corner of a dark altar, the scale behind him cracking open!

“Lin Ming!”

Sheng Mei’s body flashed and she arrived near Lin Ming. She didn’t shout out his name and only used sound transmissions.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s heart ached to the extreme. When Deep Child had attacked just now, he used a powerful wave of world potential to separate her. She hadn’t been able to approach the battlefield and there wasn’t anything she could have done to support Lin Ming.

The disparity between her and Deep Child could be imagined!

“How can he be so strong… is there nothing you know about him?”

Lin Ming coughed, the blood thick and dark, even mixed with bits of his organs.

The gap was simply too great. Deep Child was a middle True Divinity and Sheng Mei was a half-step True Divinity, someone who had reached the limits of an Empyrean. But according to the current difference in strength, even if Sheng Mei broke into True Divinity she still might not be Deep Child’s match.

In other words, the talent that Deep Child displayed now was not any lower than Sheng Mei’s!

Sheng Mei said. “From what I knew, Deep Child should have only been a bit better than the Great Flood Crown Prince. I never knew he had hidden his depths so deeply…”

“Is that so…” Lin Ming wiped the blood from the corners of his mouth. He couldn’t believe that an abyssal in the Dark Abyss who didn’t have any prominent reputation before would actually possess such a level of talent!

If Deep Child was truly so fierce then there would have been no need for him to hide himself, because hiding his talent was meaningless.

Compared to the current Deep Child, the past overly arrogant Good Fortune Saint Son wasn’t worth anything at all. Lin Ming even believed that if Deep Child continued forwards with such talent, he might have hopes of attacking the realm Beyond Divinity.

“The muscles on your wounds are wriggling, growing, and your broken ribs are quietly healing. What amazing recovery abilities!”

Deep Child looked at Lin Ming’s chest and praised out loud, “What a powerful mortal body, it really stirs up one’s envy. To become fertilizer like this is just too pitiful.”

As Deep Child spoke, he lifted his trident, pointing it straight at Lin Ming and Sheng Mei!

“Lin Ming!”

As Sheng Mei sent out a sound transmission, she stretched her hands in front of herself. Her ten slender fingers flew through the air as a blood red divine light shot out from between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows!

Flower petals fluttered about. The nine revolution divine lotus dazzled with divine light.

And at this time, Lin Ming also moved forwards. He thrust out his spear, and this time his spear struck against the center of the nine revolution red lotus!

Lin Ming poured all of his strength into the nine revolution red lotus. With a framework of Sheng Mei’s Laws as the foundation, he added in his strength and his own Laws to erupt with an even greater might!

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s joint attack had been able to kill the peak middle True Divinity Great Flood Crown Prince. From this, it could be seen just how powerful this strike was!

Kacha!

The trident smashed into the nine revolution red lotus. The nine revolution red lotus contained the Laws of Life and Death and the power of the soul; it was the ultimate display of the limit of Sheng Mei and Lin Ming’s strength. In an instant, everything burst out as the strike swept towards Deep Child like a storm!

In that moment, Deep Child’s smile finally drew back a little.

As he drew back, he thrust out his trident again and again. Each one of Deep Child’s attacks didn’t have any energy poured into it, but actually carried around that simple ‘potential’!

Impact after impact, the flower petals of the nine revolution red lotus withered and fell, the energy rapidly weakening. And, a considerable part of this energy was sucked into Deep Child’s body.

Deep Child drew back a thousand feet and the nine revolution red lotus completely vanished. From start to finish, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s joint attack hadn’t been able to touch Deep Child’s scales at all.

This attack had been considerably taxing on Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, and yet it just barely managed to force Deep Child back.

“What a strong attack! You two really make a wonderful duo!” Deep Child casually waved his hand and scattered the last wisps of energy like a spider’s web. Then, he grasped his trident and walked towards Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

“What do we do…”

Sheng Mei said, her complexion slightly pale. Anyone who met such a terrifying opponent where every one of their attacks was useless would feel desperation.

This Deep Child was no longer someone that she or Lin Ming could defeat.

And at this time, Lin Ming was actually staring at the void in front of Deep Child. In this part of the void, the energy ripples of the disappeared nine revolution red lotus still echoed.

Recalling the moment that Deep Child broke apart the nine revolution red lotus, a light lit up in Lin Ming’s mind.

“You… drew support from the strength of this world?”

Lin Ming suddenly said. Deep Child paused in his step and looked at Lin Ming with some surprise.

“All of your moves do not have any Laws fused in nor do you use your own strength. But, the truth is that you use your body as a medium to mobilize the strength of this world, and this is the so-called potential in your moves! When we fight you, the truth is that we are fighting this world!”

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Deep Child lightly sighed. “How interesting, you were actually able to see through my combat methods. Indeed, what you said is true; I draw support from this world’s strength. Within the Demon God’s Tomb, I am the absolute ruler here, no different from a divine god!

“10 billion years ago, two peerless Beyond Divinity existences appeared amongst the races of the 33 Heavens – Asura and Immortal. They each cultivated the inner universe and outer universe and each had different ideas and stepped on different roads of martial arts. The two of them even fought because of this. But in my opinion, whether it is Asura or Immortal, neither of their Laws reached the peak.

“One cultivated ‘heaven’ and the other cultivated ‘man’, and yet neither of them were able to gather heaven and man as one. Yet, my master managed to accomplish this…

“The Demon God’s Tomb is the ultimate world of my master! In this world, my master can merge together with the world, whether it is in body, soul, or mind!

“My master is the world and the world is my master. If the world is not destroyed then my master cannot be destroyed. If this world is immortal, then my master is immortal!

“And just how stable is the world of the Demon God’s Tomb? In the previous universal era, the Demon God’s Tomb even managed to resist the great Shattering!

“A world that can resist the great Shattering of the universe, that means it will continue on in perpetuity, being truly immortal. That is true eternal life, true immortality!”

Deep Child laughed as he spoke these heaven-shaking words.

Even Lin Ming, who had practiced many of the top Laws to exist, was still shocked upon hearing this.

A fusion of a martial artist and the world!

If the world isn’t destroyed, then the martial artist isn’t destroyed!

If the world was immortal, then the martial artist was immortal!

This was true eternal life, true immortality! Since ancient times, countless proud sons of heavens had chased after eternal life, and yet all of them failed without exception.

But the so-called master of Deep Child actually thought of fusing together with a world. As long as this great world was able to withstand the great Shattering the universe, then whether it was the world or the martial artist, both would remain forever.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but be stunned by such ideas.

Although Lin Ming stood opposite to this behind the scenes manipulator, he couldn’t help but acknowledge that this secret existence was one of the most terrifying geniuses to ever walk down the road of martial arts since ancient times!

While he couldn’t say whether or not someone similar could appear in the future, this existence was already unprecedented since the past!

Lin Ming couldn’t help but think of his own inner world. His inner world was extremely special; it was fused with a true world seed and also contained a massive amount of world power.

Lin Ming always wanted to fuse together the inner universe Holy Scripture and the outer universe Asura Sutra, fusing the two great Laws as one. From this meaning, the truth was that Lin Ming was walking down the same road that the behind the scenes manipulator of the Demon God’s Tomb was walking.

The difference was that he had just started down this road, but this behind the scenes manipulator had already reached large success!

This disparity was far too great!

Chapter 2179 – Assault

Wu wu wu –

All around Deep Child, the potential of the world began to gather once more.

Deep Child’s own strength was not necessarily much higher than that of the Great Flood Crown Prince. However, he possessed the ability to control the strength of the Demon God’s Tomb, and by relying on the ‘potential’ formed from the strength of the world, then as long as he stood in this land he was invincible.

Nearly the only road laid in front of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei was a dead end. In the world of the Demon God’s Tomb they were like turtles in a jar, without any way to escape.

“Is there really… no way to survive?”

In this life or death crisis, each breath that Lin Ming took seemed incomparably long. Although his body was tensed, his mind was preternaturally calm.

His thoughts raced at a terrifying speed with thousands and millions of situations flashing through his mind as he tried to search for a path to survival in this hopeless situation.

Currently, the only cards he had left in his hands were his true self and the Magic Cube. But even if he brought out these cards, it still wouldn’t be enough to defeat Deep Child.

Unless…

A light lit up in Lin Ming’s mind. In all of these dead ends, there seemed to be a singular path to survival. But, the chances of realizing this slim possibility were far too low…

“Junior-apprentice Sister, Master has spent so much effort to train you and yet you would betray him for nothing but a man! You are just far too disappointing!”

Deep Child simply didn’t seem to care about Lin Ming at all. As he spoke, he reached out for Sheng Mei!

The moment Deep Child moved, the potential of the heavens and earth formed a cage that locked down the space around Sheng Mei. Sheng Mei cried out in alarm, unable to control her body at all. Like a feather caught in strong winds, she started flying towards Deep Child.

“Get out of the way!”

Lin Ming shouted. His body flew out like a sharp sword. All the muscles on his body bulged as he poured every ounce of strength into the Black Dragon Spear and then threw it out!

Hum - !

This spear carried the limit of Lin Ming’s strength. As it tore through the void, it formed visible ripples of energy as it shot right at Deep Child’s head!

“You don’t even want your weapon. Have you already given up?”

Deep Child sneered and reached out a hand.

Shua - !

The Black Dragon Spear was grasped by Deep Child. It continued forward beneath the terrifying impact force, rubbing with Deep Child’s palm, the friction creating flames.

Wrapped with the potential of the world, the Black Dragon Spear reached half an inch from Deep Child’s eyebrows before using up its strength. But in the end, it wasn’t able to injure Deep Child in the least!

“What a last ditch effort!”

Deep Child coldly sneered. However, at this moment, the sneer on his face froze.

The Lin Ming that threw out the spear suddenly rushed right before Deep Child with inconceivable speed. He drew out a giant spine from his spatial ring. This spine resembled a grotesque centipede, and the bone was so thick that even the towering demon avatar of Lin Ming needed both hands to hold it.

Lin Ming grabbed the end of the spine, thrusting it straight down!

At this time, a barrier of world potential had still formed around Deep Child, an impregnable defense.

Puff!

With a loud explosion, the gathered world potential was torn apart by the spine in Lin Ming’s hands, as if this spine had a clear suppressive effect on the world potential.

After the world potential shattered, the icy cold spine thrust straight towards Deep Child’s heart!

“How!?”

For the first, shock flashed on Deep Child’s face.

Deep Child stormed back hundreds of feet as he waved the trident in his hands.

Kacha!

The trident collided with the spine in Lin Ming’s hand. The originally invincible trident actually began to curve beneath the impact.

And in this moment, as Deep Child blinked, he suddenly felt as if Lin Ming’s mortal body were transforming. The nearly 20 foot tall abyssal began to shrink and the scales started rapidly disappearing. Finally, he turned into the form of a human!

Lin Ming reached out a hand. A black cube started to rapidly revolve in his palm as a horrifying suction force erupted outwards!

The moment Lin Ming’s true self appeared he simultaneously summoned the Magic Cube. He had used the demon bone to break through the layers of world potential and then brought forth the Magic Cube at an extremely close distance, so that there was no barrier to contact between them.

A powerful suction force shrouded Deep Child’s body. Lin Ming wanted to suck Deep Child into the Magic Cube!

Deep Child was a faithful servant to the behind the scenes manipulator of the Demon God’s Tomb. He was able to borrow the strength of the world of the Demon God’s Tomb.

In other words, as long as Deep Child was in the Demon God’s Tomb, he was invincible.

Then the only possibility to defeat Deep Child was to have him temporarily leave the world of the Demon God’s Tomb.

And the Magic Cube was a great world seed; the space within the Magic Cube was itself a rudimentary world. If Deep Child could be drawn into the Magic Cube space, then with the Magic Cube’s unfathomable strength there was a high chance that the strength of the world of the Demon God’s Tomb would be isolated outside. Once this happened, then Deep Child would lose the support of the world Laws of the Demon God’s Tomb and he would be like a tiger without fangs; there would be no need to fear him.

To Lin Ming, this was the only possible chance of victory!

However, as Deep Child was about to be sucked into the Magic Cube, he emitted the roars of a wild animal!

He bit down on his tongue and spat out a fog of blood from his chest. Then, three fierce demon phantoms flew out from his body.

Roar! Roar! Roar!

These three demon phantoms emitted horrifying roars and hurtled towards Lin Ming before exploding on him!

As the demon phantoms exploded they created a powerful shockwave that thrust the Magic Cube away. As for Deep Child, he also borrowed the force of this storm to draw backwards.

Bang!

Divine light overflowed in all directions and surged through space. The Magic Cube raised up another suction vortex, but all it managed to draw in were the remnant souls of the demon phantoms. As for Deep Child, he had already escaped a thousand feet away and was standing atop a dark altar.

Deep Child’s burning eyes seemed as if they could bore a hole through Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming had already returned to the shape of his true self. He grasped the Magic Cube in one hand and the Demon God’s bone that was taller than him in the other.

The thunderous blow he released just now had failed because of the three demon phantoms that rushed out from Deep Child’s body!

Lin Ming was well aware that these three demon phantoms had come from the three far off demon pagodas. They had been summoned by Deep Child, where he held them in his body to increase his combat strength.

He never thought that in a key moment Deep Child could discard these three remnant demon souls to break apart his killing move.

And once he missed that moment, this meant that Lin Ming’s plan had failed. Because once Deep Child was aware and on guard, it would be far harder to suck him into the Magic Cube.

The situation could no longer become worse than it already was!

“You are actually… not part of the abyssal race!” At this time, Deep Child’s expression and gaze were much fiercer.

His eyes were poisonous and sharp. He could immediately make out that Lin Ming wasn’t an abyssal nor was he one of the ancient races that dwelled in the Dark Abyss. Rather, he came from the 33 Heavens!

This Ninth Elder was actually someone that came from the 33 Heavens and infiltrated their way into the Dark Abyss!

When joined together with the shocking talent that Lin Ming displayed, a brilliant light lit up Deep Child’s eyes.

“I know who you are! So that’s how it is! That’s how it is! You’ve truly hidden yourself deeply!”

Deep Child’s complexion became darker than water. His eyes exposed a ruthless killing intent. He looked at Lin Ming and then turned his gaze to Sheng Mei, his eyes narrowing.

“No wonder you didn’t hesitate to betray the master after just being with him for a few years. So this Ninth Elder is actually your old lover! Hah! Were you really moved by a human? You’re actually willing to sacrifice yourself for him? Sacrifice the supreme position you will obtain so easily in the future? Did you think that this human who has yet to grow up can actually defeat the master?”

Deep Child aggressively said.

However, with things having reached this stage, Sheng Mei’s eyes had already been opened to the truth. “Do you really think that after that old freak achieves his ambitions, he will give you everything you want? Keep on dreaming! A dog that has lost his use will only be tossed aside!”

Chapter 2180 – Change in the Magic Cube

Sheng Mei’s words seemed to stab painfully into Deep Child. For a time, killing intent erupted around Deep Child as if 10,000 demons were howling around him.

Weng –

On the opposite shores of the Yellow Springs River, three demon pagodas gently trembled and three more beams of light shot up into the skies, rapidly soaring towards Deep Child!

Deep Child had once again summoned the strength of the ancient demon emperors slumbering deep within the Emperor Bone Sea.

Shua – !

With the power of demon souls added into him, Deep Child’s entire body seethed with demonic strength. His strength was no weaker than it was before and he looked greedily at the Magic Cube in Lin Ming’s hand.

“That thing in your hand is truly extraordinary. For it to absorb the remnant soul of ancient demon race emperors and also break through the strength of the Demon God’s Tomb world, that really makes me wonder just what it is…”

Lin Ming’s complexion turned cold and he tightly gripped the Magic Cube.

Deep Child’s smile grew. “Lin Ming, oh Lin Ming, you are my lucky star. If I kill you, and give your head as well as that thing in your hand to my master, how do you think the master will reward me?”

As Deep Child spoke he couldn’t help but lick his lips.

But at this time, the Magic Cube in Lin Ming’s hand grew increasingly hot.

When Lin Ming stepped into the Emperor Bone Sea the Magic Cube had already started to vaguely shiver as if it were extremely excited. Moreover, there even seemed to be a somehow heated feeling.

Now that he arrived at the center of the six dark altars in the focal point of the Emperor Bone Sea, and especially after summoning the Magic Cube, he could feel this burning heat become stronger and stronger and the shaking become that much more fierce.

“What is happening here?”

Lin Ming was startled. He originally thought that the Magic Cube was shaking in the Emperor Bone Sea because it was excited at encountering so many remnant souls of ancient demon emperors, but this was clearly not the case.

Not only did the Magic Cube tremble, but beside Lin Ming, Sheng Mei also covered her chest with her hands, her eyes clouded over with confusion. “Lin Ming, whatever I felt before that was summoning me, it is a hundred times more intense now than it was when I first entered the Emperor Bone Sea…”

The changes in Sheng Mei and the Magic Cube left Lin Ming increasingly puzzled. However, he no longer had any time to think about this because Deep Child had already started moving. Deep Child grasped his trident and gathered the world potential of the Emperor Bone Sea around him once more to smash down at Lin Ming!

“You’re still distracted at this time? Die!”

Deep Child’s strike contained irresistible potential. The world potential locked in the space around Lin Ming once more, making it so that he had nowhere to dodge.

Lin Ming’s heart chilled. He held the demon bone in his hand to resist Deep Child’s strike.

In his heart, he was aware that Deep Child had combined together with this world and his energy was nearly infinite here. Moreover, with strength that surpassed his own to begin with, the chances of victory were incomparably slim.

Even the demon bone in his hands, the only thing he could rely on, was itself questionable. This was because this spine was possibly related to Deep Child’s secret master, so what if it were turned against him?

In every possible situation he could imagine, he held all the disadvantages.

Kacha!

The trident clashed with the demon bone. The massive impact force caused Lin Ming’s arms to sink downwards.

At this time, when the demon bone faced Deep Child, it no longer displayed its previously overwhelming force. Instead it was faintly cast away by Deep Child’s world potential.

After all, the demon bone was in the end not Lin Ming’s weapon and Lin Ming hadn’t been able to refine it. Before, Deep Child has suffered a loss because he had been caught off guard. Now Lin Ming was quickly finding that his control over the demon bone was weakening, even seeming as if it wanted to separate from his hands and be controlled by Deep Child!

“This entire world obeys me! If you want to use something from this world to defeat me, that is simply impossible!”

The trident in Deep Child’s hand came crashing down with epic vigor. Lin Ming barely managed to resist it. The blue veins bulged on his arms and his blood vessels nearly burst apart!

The disparity in strength was far too great!

While Lin Ming struggled to deal with this onslaught, he simultaneously looked for a chance to fight back.

But at this time the Magic Cube’s trembling became increasingly fierce, nearly slipping out of Lin Ming’s control.

“Just what is going on here?”

Lin Ming thought to himself, confused. But now, he could feel some sort of vague spiritual message come from the depths of the Magic Cube, as if the Magic Cube was desperately thirsty for energy.

The Magic Cube needed his strength?

This thought raced through Lin Ming’s thoughts as he fought Deep Child. He was already nearing exhaustion; if he were to divide any of his strength to the Magic Cube then that was nearly suicidal behavior.

Kacha!

After another fierce strike, Lin Ming was sent flying backwards. Pain coursed through his right arm and his bones nearly shattered. But taking advantage of the time he was sent tumbling away, Lin Ming fiercely clenched his teeth and summoned all of his strength to pour it into the Magic Cube without reserve!

For him to arrive at this step in his life, the Magic Cube had played an inestimably great role. In this life or death crisis Lin Ming chose to place all his trust in the Magic Cube!

Peng!

Lin Ming plummeted onto a dark altar, blood overflowing from his lips. After pouring out all his energy, Lin Ming didn’t have much excess energy left to defend himself.

“Die!”

Seeing Lin Ming pour energy into the Magic Cube as if he wanted to use this divine tool once more, Deep Child sneered. He suddenly threw out his trident like a javelin!

Woosh!

The trident tore through the void, howling towards Lin Ming like a meteor.

At this time Lin Ming no longer had the strength to resist. Seeing the giant trident nearly nail him onto the dark altar, in this flash, a dazzling nine revolution red lotus bloomed in front of Lin Ming once more. The nine flower petals contained the mysterious Concepts of Life and Death as they collided with the trident.

Bang!

The red lotus exploded to pieces. Flower petals waned and withered and the trident slowed down a great deal. Still, it continued forwards, carried by the potential of the world.

At this time Sheng Mei’s figure flickered and she appeared in front of Lin Ming. Her face was pale white as she lifted her arms.

A wall of ice formed in front of Sheng Mei.

Kacha! Kacha! Kacha!

The trident crashed into the ice wall, the cold trident edge thrusting straight at Sheng Mei’s neck!

Sheng Mei!

Lin Ming’s heart tightened. With everything hanging by a hair, Sheng Mei gathered her hands together and caught the trident edge with her palms. The momentum sent her flying backwards and crashing into Lin Ming’s chest!

In the final moments, Sheng Mei issued a piercing scream. Pushing out her arms with all her strength, she forcefully shifted the trajectory of the trident.

Ding –

The trident grazed past Lin Ming and Sheng Mei and stabbed deep into the dark altar.

By this time, Sheng Mei’s hands were covered in blood and her right arm had been twisted and the bones broken due to the tremendous impact of energy!

Although she had barely managed to guarantee Lin Ming’s life, Sheng Mei had consumed the majority of her strength to do so. Moreover, Lin Ming’s situation wasn’t much better. It would be difficult to withstand Deep Child’s next strike.

“What a pair of fated lovers, truly a sad song you play.”

Deep Child mockingly said, diabolically grinning as he walked towards Lin Ming and Sheng Mei. “Junior-apprentice Sister, although you have committed an unforgivable crime, I will not kill you, because the master has a use for your life. I will bring you back… hehe, I wonder how the master will deal with you, I’m looking forwards to it very much!”

As Deep Child spoke, the smile suddenly froze on his face.

The Magic Cube that Lin Ming had poured all of his strength into suddenly flew out of his hands like an arrow!

Deep Child’s heart tightened and he rapidly drew backwards. Facing the Magic Cube, Deep Child still held a deep sense of dread. He had already faintly guessed the Magic Cube’s origins.

Such a divine tool was no trifling matter; a single accident could lead to catastrophic failure!

Weng –

The Magic Cube’s trembling grew fiercer. Even the stable space of the Demon God’s Tomb seemed as if it would start breaking apart due to the strength of the shaking.

The Magic Cube raced through a strange path. It didn’t attack Deep Child, but flew past him instead!

With unbelievable speed, its goal was actually one of the three demon pagodas!

Near the six great dark altars there were three exceedingly high demon pagodas.

The demon pagoda that the Magic Cube flew towards was the 33 level demon pagoda!

Guang dong!

Whether it was Lin Ming, Sheng Mei, or even Deep Child, none of them had time to respond. The Magic Cube already smashed into the gates of the 33 level demon pagoda.

The powerful impact caused the front gates to violently shiver. The demon relief on the front gates seemed to come alive, its eyes glowing with blood as endless runes started revolving to resist the impact of the Magic Cube.

However, as these runes appeared, most of them were instantly crushed by the Magic Cube!

Guang dong!

Another bang echoed out. Another impact smashed into the gates without any gap. Large pieces of the demon relief scattered out, as if the front gates were going to be smashed open by the Magic Cube.

“This is bad!”

In that instant, Deep Child’s complexion changed because he had thought of a possibility, and this possibility left him feeling like he had fallen into an icy lake!

With a loud shout, he recklessly rushed towards the Magic Cube!

Chapter 2184 – Abyssal Ritual

When Lin Ming stood in the center of the dark altar, he could feel his divine soul connect through the altar and commune with the entire Emperor Bone Sea. He faintly felt this world and the strength that flowed through it.

“Originally, this so-called abyssal ritual is to accept a baptism of the strength of the Emperor Bone Sea’s world… the Soul Emperor wants to completely control the Emperor Bone Sea and fuse together with the Demon God’s Tomb, but he lacks the soul force to achieve this. Thus, he laid out all sorts of plans to accomplish it. He needed powerful minions for his plans, so he divided a portion of the Emperor Bone Sea’s strength to the peak talents of the Dark Abyss, training them into totem level abyssals that he could control himself…”

“If I withstand a baptism of the Emperor Bone Sea’s world but am not controlled by the Soul Emperor, then that is the same as slicing off a piece of meat from the Soul Emperor’s body…”

After understanding this, Lin Ming was somewhat worried. These actions would be the same as touching the Soul Emperor’s reverse scale; could it lead to disastrous consequences?

“Senior, could the Soul Emperor personally come to the Demon God’s Tomb in his anger?”

If the Soul Emperor arrived then the consequences would be inconceivable.

Immortal Sovereign said, “When I killed Deep Child, I called upon the remnant souls here to use the strength of the world to block out the Emperor Bone Sea. That old fellow is currently in total seclusion, so whether it is any changes that occur here or Deep Child’s death, it won’t be easy for him to realize it.”

As Immortal Sovereign spoke, he pointed to the Magic Cube in Lin Ming’s hands. “Deep Child’s remnant soul is already inside.”

Lin Ming then remembered that when Immortal Sovereign killed Deep Child, Deep Child’s soul had been left behind and then taken in and suppressed by the Magic Cube.

The Laws in the Emperor Bone Sea were extremely special. When a martial artist died their soul wouldn’t scatter away. In fact, this could be said to be living in a state between life and death.

And a method to know if someone was living or dead was to keep a wisp of their life soul as a signaling mark. However, if Deep Child’s soul didn’t scatter then the wisp of their life soul wouldn’t vanish, and thus it would be difficult to find out about his death.

If the Soul Emperor was paying attention to the situation then he naturally would have methods to discover this. But Lin Ming was aware that the Soul Emperor was currently in seclusion. Moreover, this was an extremely critical part of his seclusion. In all likelihood, the Soul Emperor was using his Eternal Soul as some sort of catalyst to refine some secret soul skill, finally allowing him to completely control the Emperor Bone Sea. For the Soul Emperor, this was a matter of the utmost importance because it concerned realizing his ambitions of everlasting immortality.

If he wanted to do all this without distraction then it would be difficult to focus on things happening in the outside world.

As Lin Ming was thinking, Immortal Sovereign said to Sheng Mei, “You also stand.”

“Mm.” Sheng Mei nodded and stood beside Lin Ming. At this time, the strength of the world began to surge about them. The entire Emperor Bone Sea seemed to animate around Lin Ming and Sheng Mei. Across the shores of the Yellow Springs River, over 100 demon pagodas began to shiver.

“Who? Who dares to disturb my rest?”

Suddenly, an ancient spiritual sense lashed out like a thunderclap in Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s ears.

“Kill! Kill! Kill! Fight! Fight! Fight!”

Another spiritual sense reverberated outwards.

“Flesh and blood! Give me flesh and blood!”

A frenzied voice cried out in Lin Ming’s ears. This was the soul of a wild beast, one filled with demented anger and fierce slaughtering intent.

“I want to die! Who can kill me!?”

“Hehe, there is actually a woman, a fresh and beautiful woman! I haven’t tasted a woman for tens of billions of years! Give me! Give me!”

Bang! Bang! Bang!

A demon crazily smashed into the gates of a demon pagoda. From a slit in the gates, a fierce but withered claw stretched out.

Chaotic spiritual senses gushed out for a time, filled with endless hope and maddening bestial desires as they rushed towards Lin Ming and Sheng Mei like a tide.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei weren’t prepared for this to occur at all, so they were slightly startled. However, they immediately revolved their spiritual seas and soul force erupted to block out these spiritual senses. Otherwise, if these spiritual senses were to break into their spiritual seas, there would be a chance they would be assimilated by these beast-like spiritual senses and lose their minds.

“All of you shut up!”

With a loud shout, Immortal Sovereign’s words cracked like lighting. This voice formed a shockwave that radiated outwards.

Bang!

The over 100 demon pagodas seemed to shake simultaneously. The originally discordant cackle of sounds vanished and the remnant souls calmed down.

“Immortal!”

“Immortal!”

“Immortal!”

Several demons diabolically shouted. Their voices echoed through the Emperor Bone Sea, broad and cold.

“You actually managed to leave the demon pagoda?”

“Hehe, how useless! You still cannot escape the Law bindings of the Emperor Bone Sea!”

“Here, we cannot beg for life or beg for death. You will never leave!”

Hearing these curse-like words, Immortal Sovereign’s complexion remained as usual. He only lifted his palms and pushed them outwards.

Bang!

The strength of the world formed a massive wave that swept towards the 100 plus demon pagodas.

The demon pagodas wildly shook, as if a storm appeared in the Emperor Bone Sea.

The remnant souls of the demons were sealed in the demon pagodas and couldn’t be harmed by such actions. But, the vast strength that erupted from Immortal’s body was enough to frighten and shock many demons.

“Contribute your world strength!”

Immortal’s voice reverberated in the air along with the storm, his expression one that brooked no refusal.

“Why!?” Demons clamored together.

“Why should I listen to you?”

“Hehe, give me that woman and I will consider it.”

The abyssal ritual was a powerful ceremony that would give birth to a totem level abyssal. But, totem level abyssals were existences at the limit of True Divinity, and they were much stronger than the current Immortal Sovereign and his remaining remnant soul.

With Immortal Sovereign’s strength it was impossible for him to mobilize the tremendous amount of energy required to baptize Sheng Mei and Lin Ming. Thus, he had to draw support from the other remnant demon souls in the Emperor Bone Sea.

“On the basis of these two people standing here! Don’t you wish you could tear the controller of the abyss to shreds, drink his blood and eat his flesh? You are all nothing but pigs and dogs reared here in cages, waiting for him to butcher you with a knife. When do you think your obsessions will ever come true?”

Immortal Sovereign spoke slowly, but his words carried a powerful vibration that wildly surged outwards.

“Hahahahahaha! A remnant demon soul suddenly raucously laughed. “What nonsense are you spouting? Are you thinking that this man and woman that are no different from little kittens are going to be able to defeat that old freak!?”

“Did I hear wrong? You want us to contribute our world strength to undergo a baptism for these two little things?”

“Hahahaha! They are Empyreans! Not even True Divinities! You have been sealed away for 10 billion years and now you’ve gone crazy!”

Many demons wildly laughed. They were originally wild and rebellious individuals and after being sealed away for tens of billions of years, their hearts were filled with hostility.

Moreover, they didn’t belong to the same race that Immortal came from. Even if they had a common enemy in the Soul Emperor, wanting them to obey without question was easier said than done.

Immortal slightly frowned. He looked at Lin Ming and asked, “Are you confident you can pass the abyssal ritual?”

Immortal had witnessed the battle between Lin Ming and Deep Child. When Deep Child was supported by the strength of the world, he possessed strength above that of an upper True Divinity. Yet, Lin Ming with his peak upper Empyrean cultivation was able to battle Deep Child for dozens of breaths of time without dying. This level of strength had left Immortal Sovereign shocked.

As for Sheng Mei, although she was a little worse than Lin Ming, she was still the reincarnation of his daughter. Her strength and talent were beyond a shadow of a doubt.

Thus, Immortal Sovereign was confident in allowing them to withstand the trial of the abyssal ritual and challenge the nearly invincible Soul Emperor!

“If it is only a test of potential, then there is no problem at all!”

Lin Ming calmly stated. In truth, potential was equivalent to talent. The most visible and intuitive way to judge this was to measure a person’s overall combat strength in comparison to their age.

In this aspect, no one could surpass Lin Ming.

“And if it is at an even higher, more difficult level?” A flash of light burst out from Immortal Sovereign’s eyes.

Lin Ming was startled, but he still clenched his teeth and said, “I can give it a try!”

If the abyssal ritual rose by yet another degree of difficulty, it was hard to imagine what it would be like. But, if he wanted to defeat the Soul Emperor then he needed to push himself to the edge and go beyond his limits!

“Good!”

A light of appreciation flashed in Immortal Sovereign’s eyes. He took a deep breath and turned around, facing the many crazed demons. He said, “If any of you doubt me, then you can pour your strongest strength here and see if they can withstand it!”

Immortal Sovereign’s words left many demons shocked. Within the Emperor Bone Sea, everything suddenly quieted down.

Chapter 2185 – To the Heart’s Content

“You want us to pour our strongest strength into the bodies of these two Empyrean juniors?”

“Hehe, Immortal, do you think you’re dreaming? If we pour the strength of our hundred some soul forms into this boy and girl, it will cause their bodies to explode!”

“Hahaha! Immortal, you might have some grudge with these two babies but there isn’t a need to use such cruel methods to torture them!”

After several breaths of quiet, many demons began to howl in laughter. The abyssal ritual was an excruciatingly painful process, and the greater the intensity of energy, the greater the pain that followed it.

If one couldn’t withstand the impact of energy then their body would blow up. This method of death was at least a hundred times more painful than death by being torn apart.

Moreover, after dying their soul would also be sealed here. However, they wouldn’t be sealed in the demon pagodas but beneath a great array formation beneath the Emperor Bone Sea. In that crowded and dark array formation, being caged up in that sort of environment would cause one to go even crazier than if they were locked up in a demon pagoda!

Immortal Sovereign remained unmoved. He coldly sneered and said, “You are already dead, so what is the point of keeping your energies? If you still have a slim hope of being able to revive someday, then I advise you to stop dreaming! However, I believe that even if you pour the greatest amount of world strength that you have in your body, you still won’t be able to fill these two juniors up!”

“Heh, there is no need for you to stir us up, Immortal. If you want to reduce these two juniors to ashes then let me help you!”

A demon fiendishly laughed. But just as this demon was about to act, a series of even more shrill laughs echoed out. “Jejejeje! Yuan Chi, pass this matter over to us brothers instead!”

As this voice finished speaking, it focused on Immortal and said, “Aren’t you confident in these two little babies? Good, then us brothers will act on that boy. We will pour in our greatest energies, and if we kill him then you will toss that young beauty over there to us for us to enjoy. How about it?”

Hearing these insolent and brazen voices, Lin Ming’s complexion darkened. He clearly remembered who these voices belonged to; they were from the hungry ghosts who had drooled over Sheng Mei.

After staying in the Demon God’s Tomb for so long, some remnant souls would start to understand each other, and it wasn’t surprising for some minds that shared mutually disgusting interests to be on close terms with each other.

Immortal remained expressionless. He clenched his fists and highly compressed world strength began crackling in his palms!

“What? Do you want to attack us? We are locked in these demon pagodas, so there is nothing you can do to us!”

These demons didn’t fear Immortal Sovereign. Indeed, Immortal Sovereign wasn’t able to do anything to them. They had already died and could no longer die again. Moreover, these demon pagodas would protect their divine souls.

And if in fact they could die, they would be overjoyed to die forever. They had been locked in these demon pagodas for endless years and had gone crazy with loneliness and despair. Their futures were to be nothing but beasts reared in cages, waiting for the day that the Soul Emperor completely refined this world, whereupon they would be slaughtered no differently than beasts.

But at this time, Lin Ming coldly said, “Enough nonsense. I want to see just what your strongest strength is. If you can’t do anything to me, how about you admit that you are nothing but base dogs 10,000 times over?”

Although these ancient demon emperors had died and nothing could be done to them, most of them were still incredibly arrogant and prideful. If they actually had to admit that they were nothing but dogs 10,000 times over, then they wouldn’t have the face to continue existing in this Emperor Bone Sea.

“You are seeking death!”

Hearing Lin Ming’s insults, the demons that spoke before were incensed.

“Let us begin! Blow this boy’s body up!”

“Kill him!”

This group of demons had arrived in the Demon God’s Tomb at around the same time period. There were six of them together and six great demons struck out together. Six demon pagodas began to shake and tremble!

Of these six demon pagodas, the shortest was 15 levels and one of them was 18 levels. On the opposite shores of the Yellow Springs River, this was considered the highest demon pagoda.

But this wasn’t the end. When these six demon moved, they also galvanized nine surroundings pagodas that were originally quiet, and all of these pagodas began to gush out with a wild world strength.

Bang!

Thick black beams of light shot into the heavens. Like 15 giant pythons of varying sizes, they all came hurtling towards Lin Ming!

Lin Ming sent out a ray of soul force and sent Sheng Mei away. Then, he looked up, his eyes blazing as he stared at these 15 pythons.

“Come on!”

In this moment, Lin Ming’s mind seethed with killing intent. If he wanted to defeat the Soul Emperor, then everything would begin from here!

Bang!

15 pythons violently rushed onto the altar. A terrifying explosion followed!

Lin Ming felt as if a massive bucket of lava was poured across his body. The 36,000 pores of his body began to emit an incomparably hot stream of heat, his entire body releasing steaming hot air!

This tyrannical and brutal energy rampaged through his meridians. It impacted into his inner world, breaking in and exploding, compressing, exploding, and then compressing again!

Lin Ming could feel that his foundation was being struck by a heavy hammer, maliciously hardened and tempered again and again!

If he had to describe this feeling with a single word, then it would be…

Amazing!

“Haha, how wonderful!”

Lin Ming emitted a loud cry to his heart’s content. His shout pierced into the skies, reverberating through the entire Emperor Bone Sea.

The impact of energy upon his body was painful, but sometimes, pain wouldn’t cause misery, instead it would sometimes cause joy and excitement.

Now, as these demons poured their energies into Lin Ming’s body, the pain it brought just happened to reach this degree. Lin Ming easily withstood it, and even felt a sense of comfort course through his body.

“What!?”

“This brat!”

Seeing Lin Ming withstand their energies and not only not explode to death, but also not suffering any distress or excruciating pain and instead yell out in joy, this was simply a slap to the faces of these demons.

“You are courting death!”

“Make him suffer! Make him die!”

Six ancient demons went mad with rage. They emitted violent roars of rage as their fierce strength rushed into Lin Ming’s body.

Lin Ming clenched his fists together and emitted a long howl.

“Awesome!

“Come again! Make the energy even stronger!

“Did you not eat enough before this? Keep on coming!”

Lin Ming yelled out. And at this time, the six ancient demons were flushed with anger. They were rapidly using up their soul force and in a short several breaths of time they had used up over half of the world strength they had gathered.

Seeing these six great demons try their best and also seeing Lin Ming relax as if he were taking a hot bath, many ancient demons were shocked.

These six perverted demons had lustful and lascivious natures, but their strength was beyond reproach. Moreover, they even controlled a few of the silent demon pagodas. These six demons had joined forces and launched a joint attack with everything they had, yet they weren’t even able to do anything to a little peak Empyrean junior?

“Interesting, how interesting…”

An ancient voice resounded from another demon pagoda. This demon pagoda was also 18 levels, but every level of this pagoda was taller than the levels of the other pagodas. Amongst the rows of demon pagodas, this one felt as if it stood out, like a crane amongst chickens.

“This little fellow is truly unbelievable. Perhaps he really might be able to give a bit of trouble to that old freak.”

Another old voice sounded out.

“What use is there in being just troublesome? It is only good if he can at least cut off a piece of meat from that old freak’s body. And this is… if he had enough time to grow!”

“Hehe, grow? Then let me give him a helping hand!”

Suddenly, on the other shores of the Yellow Springs River, another demon pagoda emitted a beam of light. This beam of light was crimson, like a giant blood dragon that claws its way towards Lin Ming!

Bang!

An explosion swept across the dark altar. Lin Ming’s hair scattered outwards, all of his joints emitting explosive crackling sounds.

“You came just in time!”

Lin Ming grit his teeth and veins stuck out on his muscles like blue worms.

Just the strength of this crimson beam alone was around a third of the sum total of those six demons’ energies gathered together!

And besides feeling pain surge through his body, Lin Ming still forcefully withstood it without any sense of collapse.

Seeing this scene, the six previously clamoring demons felt as if they had been slapped silly. They all wished to find a hole to crawl into. Even with the six of them together along with a demon emperor that was stronger than any one of them, they still weren’t able to do anything to Lin Ming, let alone cause his body to explode.

“I can’t believe it…”

These six demons still grit their teeth and continued. But at this time, more demons leapt into the fray.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Four more beams of divine light shot into the skies!

“How interesting! Then let us join in and give this brat some more material!”

Chapter 2187 – The Limit of Pain

Over a hundred giant beams of world strength shrouded in the aura of demons came crashing down, each one dazzling, their brilliance spreading out for tens of thousands of miles.

It was like a river of stars came falling down from the skies, their massive momentum slamming into the earth, causing the world to shake.

The Emperor Bone Sea began to boil over as monstrous demonic auras filled the air. The mysterious rules and the countless remnant traces of ancient demons were quickened.

Steaming black energy filled the air, seemingly filled with the forms of ancient demons. They formed a storm that raged out in all directions.

Bang!

Lin Ming bore all of this immense world strength. His body that glistened like jade was suddenly curved by the impact into a tightened bow. His skin, his skeleton, everything emitted creaking sounds that blasted out like the roars of dragons and cries of phoenixes.

Beneath this tremendous pressure, he remained unyielding. His tendons twisted over the surface of his body like snakes. He raised his arm and hands up and roared into the heavens.

At the same time, Sheng Mei was also joined together with him. Her strength blended together with Lin Ming’s and together they withstood this baptism of world strength!

Ka ka ka!

Lin Ming’s muscles and blood vessels began to rapidly crack. An indescribable pain shot into his spiritual sea.

This sort of feeling was as if his mortal body had been tossed beneath a stone mill, forcefully grinded down by it!

However, Lin Ming’s consciousness remained clear and sober the entire time.

Sheng Mei held tightly onto Lin Ming’s hand, blood flowing down from her lips. She withstood less energy than Lin Ming but she was also weaker than Lin Ming. In terms of the pain she withstood, it was no less than Lin Ming.

And at this time, not too far away, Immortal Sovereign was watching all of this occur with a calm expression. A treasure sword had to be tempered and sharpened and the fragrance of plum blossoms only emerged after the bitter cold. Compared to the upcoming apocalypse of existence, what Lin Ming and Sheng Mei withstood was nothing.

Weng –

Weng –

Weng –

Between Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, the blending of energy became increasingly intense.

This strength was several times greater than an ordinary occurrence of the abyssal ritual.

Although Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were withstanding it together and dividing the pressure between the two of them, this still far outstripped an ordinary abyssal ritual.

In particular, Lin Ming withstood the majority of the energy. He clenched his teeth and persisted.

There were too many things he carried on his shoulders. He had experienced countless tribulations, countless perilous life and death situations, and had even experienced the boundless ups and downs of life. Pushing his way through all of that he arrived here today, shouldering the destiny and hopes of innumerable people. Because of that, he absolutely could not allow himself to fail here!

Beneath the galvanization of the world strength, Lin Ming’s body instinctively evolved strands of the Great Dao Laws that he excelled in the most to compete with the world strength, making it even better to swallow and refine them.

As these Laws appeared, the raging world strength seemed to solidify, the essence condensing into little droplets that slowly revolved around Lin Ming.

The strength of the world slowly steadied, forming a sealed space where they circulated within.

As the 100 demons watching from the side saw this, their eyes began to shine.

At this time no one was mad anymore. In fact, there was even a hint of heated fanaticism in their hearts!

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were truly able to withstand the baptism of the Emperor Bone Sea’s world potential. Perhaps they could truly rise from here and help them exact vengeance upon their enemy!

“Everyone, let us transfer the world strength of the Emperor Bone Sea together and stabilize that force field.”

“There might be feuds between us and we may be at odds with each other, but let us work together today and give this our everything!”

Of the 100 some demons, no one dared to slack off. Even the six demons who clashed with Lin Ming had slowly put away their embarrassment and rage towards him. First, they didn’t want to do anything that would offend the other demons here, and secondly they truly, truly wished to break from these cages and take revenge against the Soul Emperor to obtain true freedom, true relief from this hell.

Beneath the joint efforts of all the demons, they began to gather all the world strength they could summon to the area around Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

An invisible force field completely covered Lin Ming and Sheng Mei. This force field was like a giant cocoon that isolated the Laws and formed a sealed space, allowing Lin Ming and Sheng Mei to live in an independent world. And this independent world contained an incredibly rich world strength!

The abyssal ritual was an extremely long process but it only took the 100 some demons several hours to contribute their world strength. Afterwards, the world strength would seal itself into a force field and the trial challengers would soak within it to slowly refine it.

After the force field was completely sealed up, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei felt the excruciating pain rise by several degrees.

This world strength continually crushed and pulverized their mortal bodies, soul, and even inner worlds. Burning hot energy raced through their pores, acupoints, breaking into their meridians and blood vessels as it recklessly galloped about.

If the pain before was like being thrown beneath a grinding pan, then now, while their bodies were being grinded away, they were also being boiled in scalding oil!

Beneath the tremendous impact of energy, their flesh and blood started to tear open and flip over!

However, within this force field, special Laws existed in the rich world strength that increased the rate at which Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s cracked flesh regenerated.

Their flesh cracked open and regenerated again and again. The two of them had incredibly powerful mortal body foundations, but even so, this sort of endless cracking and regeneration consumed a mind-boggling amount of energy!

They did not take pills nor did they drink spiritual liquids. The energy they needed to consume would have to be derived from the surrounding world strength.

In this repeated tempering, their bodies absorbed the surrounding world strength without end. By letting their bodies crack open and regenerate again, they used this method to consume this strength!

And, this process would continue for years!

Pain. If pain only lasted for a while, then many people could grit their teeth and bear it. But to withstand such pain for dozens of years or even hundreds of years, it was enough to make one go crazy!

When trial challengers were placed in the abyssal ritual, this was the test of their will, the test of withstanding the massive level of pain!

If their potential was lacking, then their bodies would explode from being unable to withstand the great volume of energy.

If their willpower was lacking, then they would go crazy from the pain!

If their souls weren’t strong enough, then the continuous impact of pain would turn their souls to ashes.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei existed at the peak when it came to these three aspects. Even so, to withstand such agonizing pain for such a long time was still a difficult challenge for them.

“You must both remember a single word – endure!”

Immortal Sovereign’s words pierced through the boundaries of the force field and entered into Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s ears.

“Gather your will and never lose your consciousness. Imagine yourself as the deep and heavy earth. No matter what pain you experience, you must remain motionless! Defend your minds at all costs. If your willpower ever fails then the world strength that is in your body will no longer be controlled by you. Once that happens, not only will your body not regenerate but you will be torn to shreds. If that happens you will be deader than dead. You will become a lonely soul here that is suppressed in the great array formation beneath us, becoming nourishment for the Demon God’s Tomb!

“What you need is to forget this pain and control your nerves, even treating this pain as pleasure. Only like this can you last for a hundred years or even hundreds of years!”

Endure!

Forget the pain. That was easy to say, but how difficult was it to do!?

However, no matter how difficult it was, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei would still give it a try. With the massive levels of soul force they possessed they would continually push at their boundaries and try to transform themselves.

“Control my nerves, drive out the pain, and even treat this pain as pleasure!”

These thoughts raced through Lin Ming’s mind.

He tried his best to forget this pain. But, with the feeling of being drowned in boiling oil and crushed beneath a grinding pan coursing through his body, how could it be so easy to forget?

Slowly, Lin Ming endured such pain for a month. But no matter how powerful his divine soul was, it would still slowly weaken.

At this time Lin Ming’s face was as pale as paper. Although he had plenty of energy, he had to sit motionlessly and be tormented by agonizing pain, so how could he have a happy expression?

“Pain comes from the body, but it actually reflects in the soul and mind… if I can control my soul, then no matter how painful it is it cannot be this fierce…”

As Lin Ming was pushed to the limits of what he could bear, this thought flashed in his mind.

“My soul, because it has been solidified by the Magic Cube and after having been cultivated through seven reincarnations, has already re-entered the realm of the Eternal Soul. If I had to describe it in words, it should be unchangeable and immutable.

“To have an unchangeable and immutable soul, I should be as steady as the great earth. How could I not be able to withstand such trivial pain of the flesh?”

Lin Ming roared out in his heart. In this moment, his consciousness became crystal clear and he felt the pain in his body reduce by a great deal.

His mortal body was still being torn apart and energy was still burning through his meridians, but all of that lessened with this new comprehension.

Lin Ming could feel that the tearing pain of his mortal body caused a faint excitement to stir in his soul. And the feeling of his meridians being burned was similar to soaking in a hot spring bath. Although it still hurt, it was no longer unbearable like before.

He felt as if he truly turned into the deep and steady earth, capable of withstanding the baptism of world strength without a single movement.

This sort of comprehension had only just begun. But as his comprehensions deepened, Lin Ming’s abyssal ritual would become increasingly smooth until he absorbed all the world strength he could!

Chapter 2188 – The Critical Point of True Divinity

Years passed silently. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei quietly withstood the long abyssal ritual.

Ever since Lin Ming comprehended the mysteries of the Eternal Soul, the impact of pain against his soul grew increasingly weak as he slowly adapted to it. He even began to do as Immortal Sovereign said and took this pain as pleasure.

And beside Lin Ming, Sheng Mei also found her own methods to adapt to this pain. While she didn’t have Lin Ming’s Eternal Soul, she used her talent to forcefully take control of her nerves.

At the start Sheng Mei had to rely on revolving the Holy Scripture Laws, using the life strength of endless growing to neutralize the agonizing impacts.

But several years later, Sheng Mei was already able to erase the pain to her soul.

Ten years later, Sheng Mei sat cross-legged within the small independent world, her expression like that of a sleeping baby. It was hard to imagine just what sort of energy impact she was actually withstanding at this moment.

As for Lin Ming, he was like a never-changing statue, not even uttering a single word.

From the beginning and even now, Immortal Sovereign stood by the side, silently waiting.

He floated high in the air, his divine sense constantly examining the situation within the independent world.

As for the 100 some demon emperors, every 10 years they would pour their world strength into the force field that Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were in, in order to ensure that the world strength within it was always at a highly saturated state!

10 years, 20 years, 30 years…

100 years, 200 years, 300 years…

In this independent world, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei remained unmoving for several hundred years.

They only held hands and quietly withstood all of this. Beneath the repeated impact of energy, their foundation became increasingly solid.

From the outside, nothing seemed to have changed. The only thing that changed was the time period from when those ancient demon emperors would pour their world strength into the independent world.

At the start it was every 10 years, but afterwards, it was once every five years.

After that, it was once every three years.

And 900 years later they would pour their world strength into the force field every single year.

After 900 years of bitter cultivation, the energy within Lin Ming and Sheng Mei had gathered to an extreme; they had already reached their limits.

In fact, Sheng Mei’s cultivation was originally higher and over 500 years ago she had already reached the critical point for breaking into True Divinity. However, in order to step forwards with Lin Ming and form a harmonious yin yang energy cycle, she continually suppressed her cultivation to help Lin Ming cultivate.

Because of this, 900 years later, their cultivations had become increasingly close.

This long abyssal ritual even left the many ancient demon emperors of the Demon God’s Tomb shocked. Before this, there had been abyssal demons who passed the test of the abyssal ritual and slowly grew into totem level abyssals in the future.

But the abyssal ritual they withstood was only several hundred years in total, while Lin Ming and Sheng Mei withstood one that was approaching a thousand years. This was truly inconceivable!

Like this, time continued to the 1000th year. The many ancient demon emperors had started to pour their word strength into the independent world every 10 months.

1080 years later, on one day, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly flashed open. At this moment his skin started to explode like stars and pieces of his jade-like flesh fell off, blowing outwards from the tremendous and chaotic flow of energy.

This flesh had a strong medicinal fragrance. Covered in the milky white light, it was actually abandoned like this. Even the demon emperors felt their hearts ache at such a loss.

When Lin Ming’s old flesh and skin fell off, new flesh and skin had already appeared. This new flesh was crystal bright and shined like a sun, illuminating the surrounding world.

Countless golden vortexes appeared atop every pore. Immortal beings seemed to sit atop these vortexes, reciting ancient mantras.

His entire being was shrouded in a haze of these ancient mantras, as if some great revered being was being born.

Meanwhile, Lin Ming’s body also trembled. Bones penetrated through his flesh and blood, sticking out like divine pillars.

If one looked at these bones carefully, they could see numerous tiny marks on them, as well as some areas that were pitch black, and even blood markings of the Great Dao.

Now, these bones were being forcefully pushed out of Lin Ming’s body.

He was replacing his flesh and blood, being reborn.

This scene was extremely macabre and abnormal. As the old demons around the Emperor Bone Sea saw this, they were shocked, all of them rendered speechless.

After Lin Ming reached this step, he still managed to replace his flesh and blood once more. It was obvious just how useful this world strength was in tempering his mortal body.

Kacha! Kacha!

Lin Ming’s bones shattered without end. An energy broke out from them, filled with the roars of demons as it floated into the air.

These bones were engraved with mystical bone runes. For anyone else these would be supremely rare and valuable bones, and yet Lin Ming was discarding them so easily.

However, this was not the end. After several breaths of time, these bone that were discarded were destroyed. As the fragments of bone dust fell all around, the purest life energy contained in those bones actually returned to Lin Ming’s body.

Even some of the medicinally fragrant flesh that Lin Ming discarded rapidly turned into ash. Their essence energy as well as the source Law fragments contained within flew back into Lin Ming!

Many old demons marveled at the spectacle.

To be reborn to such a degree was simply inconceivable.

This was a true perfect body!

Lin Ming had already taken pain as pleasure. But, in the process of his birth, he fell into agonizing pain once more. His source Great Dao had already been fused into his bones and flesh and blood, and wanting to discard it from his body to be replaced and to be reborn, that was incredibly difficult.

One needed the most formidable of wills as well as an incomparably stable foundation.

Not too far away, Immortal Sovereign’s eyes lit up with a fascinated light. As he looked at Lin Ming’s changes, he had already stood up.

Now, what he was waiting for was Lin Ming’s true transformation!

He knew that this moment of replacing the bones and flesh was only the prelude to Lin Ming’s breakthrough into True Divinity.

Beside Lin Ming, Sheng Mei also opened her eyes. In truth she had waited for Lin Ming for 600 years. Waiting this long wasn’t a waste, but was actually highly significant to her.

This was because if she could step into True Divinity together with Lin Ming, then the two of them could touch upon the Heavenly Dao together and arouse the trembling of the world Laws. Because they were complementing each other in yin yang circulation, they would obtain the greatest benefits!

As Sheng Mei was fermenting her own energy, the nine revolution red lotus mark between her eyebrows began to shine with divine light.

She wanted to complete her breakthrough together with Lin Ming.

At the same time, Lin Ming’s replacing of bones and flesh was continuing. As his bones were reborn anew, his organs also started to transform.

An unknown period of time passed. Lin Ming’s blood vitality scattered again and again, but was reborn repeatedly due to the perfusion of world strength.

Finally, his body dazzled once more, and creamy white bones grew out from his old shattered ones.

These bones were densely carved with mysterious ancient runes. It was like towering mountains grew within his body, supporting his infinite power.

Fresh blood boiled over, the sounds like roaring True Dragons.

He emitted a loud cry into the heavens. The sound waves turned into tumbling sea waves that surged into the Emperor Bone Sea.

His gaze was like the sun and moon. As he opened and closed his eyes, it was like worlds were being born and extinguished, rivers of stars flowing within without end.

And at this time, Immortal Sovereign pointed out a finger.

With a light cracking sound, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s spatial rings shattered. Three ancient black books emerged from their two spatial rings.

These were the ceremonial rites books left behind by the Soul Emperor!

The ceremonial rites books had been tampered with by the Soul Emperor. If one withstood the abyssal ritual using them, their spiritual sea would be invaded.

And now, beneath the support of all the ancient demon emperors, Immortal Sovereign was using this world potential to refine these ceremonial rites books!

Without a doubt, these three ceremonial rites books contained an incomparably pure strength. How could Immortal Sovereign waste it?

Now, Immortal Sovereign was refining these books to draw out their strength. This would undoubtedly allow Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s cultivations to take a step further, and provide them with the maximum energy possible for their breakthrough into True Divinity!

Over 100 ancient demon emperors suddenly stirred up, their thoughts focusing. They revolved their strength, moving as much world strength as they could towards Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

And at this time, an ancient voice leisurely echoed out, shaking the heavens and earth.

“What a grand occasion that hasn’t been seen for even 100 billion years…”

This voice actually came from the 30 level pagoda that was around the dark altars!

Originally, there were only three pagodas around the dark altars and only Immortal Sovereign had been awakened because of the battle between Lin Ming and Deep Child. As for the other two pagodas, they remained quiet. Yet at this time, a response rose up in one of them!

Immortal Sovereign’s eyes began to shine.

Chapter 2190 – Double True Divinities

When a martial artist broke into the realm of True Divinity, the powerful Laws within their bodies would manifest one after another.

The Supreme phantom behind Lin Ming had already half-fused with his mortal body. It sat atop a seven-leaf red lotus, a giant Asura Wheel spinning above its head.

At this moment, the seven revolution red lotus was like the earth and the Asura Wheel was like the heavens.

And between the heavens and earth, the Heretical God Tree that Lin Ming cultivated as well as the fused martial intent Bodhi Tree began to appear. Between these divine trees, True Dragons and True Phoenixes danced in the air; this was the dragon and phoenix blood within Lin Ming’s body!

Divine chains of order also began condensing in the void. These divine chains of order wrapped around the trees like wreaths of gemmed necklaces.

At this moment, the various Laws that Lin Ming refined were appearing and slowly integrating into the divine chains of order.

This was a transformation of Laws!

However, as Lin Ming’s mortal body had fused 90% with his Supreme phantom, beside him, an even greater red lotus bloomed. This red lotus had nine flower petals and each flower petal was like its own separate world.

Above the red lotus, wind and snow howled and raging deep blue energy surged, forming a frosty river that connected the heavens and earth.

Sheng Mei had begun breaking into True Divinity.

Bang!

World strength swelled up from all over and rushed towards Sheng Mei, forming a vast sea that washed over every inch of her flesh and blood, every wisp of her divine soul!

At the same time, the divine chains of order around Sheng Mei began to loudly shatter, turning into source Law fragments that joined together with the strength of the world to break into her body.

This was a baptism of the heavens and earth that a martial artist underwent when becoming a True Divinity. To all True Divinities, including Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, such a chance only appeared once!

When a martial artist became a True Divinity they would undergo a baptism of Laws and the world’s strength; this was an incomparably precious opportunity!

And at this time, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were holding hands. This world energy not only flowed through Sheng Mei’s body and divine soul, but also flowed through Lin Ming.

A part of the Laws and energy passed through Lin Ming’s body before returning to Sheng Mei. Although it was only flowing through, it still brought incomprehensible comprehensions and advantages to Lin Ming.

Every wisp of Laws and energy left behind their own unique mark within Lin Ming. Lin Ming could feel the red lotus beneath him tremble in excitement and the Asura Wheel also howled in joy. The Heretical God Tree, the Bodhi Tree, everything shined with overflowing vitality, their branches and leaves stretched outwards as new roots budded!

At this time, a clear divine sense spread into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. “Daddy, how could you forget me with something so good happening?”

This was Jiu’er’s voice. Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and he looked into the Magic Cube space. A cute little girl that looked just a bit over ten years old was looking up at him with wide and hopeful eyes.

Without much thought, Lin Ming reached out a hand and a part of the endless Laws and world energy that belonged to Sheng Mei flowed into the Magic Cube space before flowing back out.

And these energies and Laws rushed into Jiu’er’s body.

To withstand a baptism of energy of a True Divinity’s breakthrough was already an unimaginable lucky chance. And, the comprehensions brought about when Sheng Mei stepped into the realm of True Divinity actually far surpassed other ordinary True Divinities’!

According to all common sense, with Jiu’er’s strength, even if she was soaked in this world strength she still wouldn’t be able to comprehend many things. However, Jiu’er was Sheng Mei’s own flesh and blood daughter and their two bloodlines were linked together. And when Jiu’er was breeding within Sheng Mei and had been sealed away, she had also come into contact with many of Sheng Mei’s Laws.

Now, the world strength that Sheng Mei guided into herself was completely unimpeded as it swept into Jiu’er. Every inch of Jiu’er’s body and divine soul were being baptized by the Law fragments and world energy.

Jiu’er couldn’t help but cry out in joy. To her, this baptism would have an extremely profound influence on her future road of martial arts.

At this time the small black dragon and Ruby that were also within the Magic Cube couldn’t obtain such a great advantage like Jiu’er.

However, the baptism had only just begun.

Bang!

Bang!

Bang!

Horrifying explosive sounds rang through the world. Just ten breaths into Sheng Mei breaking into True Divinity, the energy in the world began to turn frantic and mad.

If it was said that the world strength that Sheng Mei gathered during her breakthrough was like a vast sea, then now, this vast sea had formed hundred mile high waves, an incomparably crazy sight!

Lin Ming’s breakthrough had also begun!

The world strength he gathered as he broke into True Divinity was much greater than Sheng Mei’s. This was an unimaginable amount!

And just like Lin Ming obtaining advantages during Sheng Mei’s breakthrough, Sheng Mei also obtained incredibly benefits during Lin Ming’s breakthrough.

World strength and energy of Laws passed through Sheng Mei’s body, leaving behind permanent marks before pouring back into Lin Ming.

The magnetic life fields of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei had already superimposed on top of each other. At this time, their flesh and blood and divine souls had all come together in perfect harmony!

This sort of union could no longer be described simply as yin yang reinforcement. Between the two of them, each was leaving profound marks in the other’s lives.

And the advantages that these marks brought were already indescribable.

Weng –

Weng –

Weng –

A horrifying shaking sound thundered through the world. From above Lin Ming’s head and below his feet, the Asura Wheel and Holy Scripture red lotus began to approach each other. Slowly, the two of them were beginning to fuse together!

When Lin Ming was at the Sky Spill Continent and started to become aware of the Laws of Life and Death, he had already attempted to join the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra together to fuse the universe of the world and the universe of the body. After all sorts of experiences and lucky chances, he was finally beginning to make progress.

And now, as Lin Ming was breaking into True Divinity, the phenomenon of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra fusing together was appearing once more.

Lin Ming’s achievements in the Asura Heavenly Dao were higher. But when it came to compression, his understandings of the Holy Scripture were no less than the Heavenly Sutra.

Especially at this time, Sheng Mei was sitting beside Lin Ming. She had undergone perfect nine revolutions and the connection between their souls only boosted this fusion.

Seeing this, many ancient demons were at a loss for words. Even Immortal Sovereign’s heart shook. He stood up, his eyes blazing as he looked at Lin Ming.

As the creator of the Holy Scripture he certainly knew how difficult it was to unify the great Laws of the world’s universe and the body’s universe. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have formed such a contentious disagreement of ideas with the Asura Road Master 10 billion years ago.

Lin Ming sat in the void, solemn and dignified. The Asura Wheel and Holy Scripture red lotus grew closer and closer. However, after fusing just a part, their speeds actually slowed down.

As if there was something blocking their fusion.

These were two of the highest Laws of the 33 Heavens. Even if they were to start fusing together, it wasn’t something that could be accomplished in a single go.

Bang!

An explosion rang out. World strength gathered. The Asura Wheel and Holy Scripture red lotus stopped here. They shattered into fragments, turning into the most source Law energies that began to baptize Lin Ming’s body

Within the Magic Cube space, Jiu’er leapt up in joy. During Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s breakthrough she had obtained all the advantages she could ask for.

Whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, they shared a bloodline with her, and thus there would be no rejection of energy between them!

She greedily basked in the baptism of energy brought about by her father and mother, lazily stretching out her body.

And beside Jiu’er, the one that obtained the next greatest advantages was the little black dragon.

The little black dragon was unable to fuse together with Sheng Mei’s energies, but it could actually withstand the baptism of world strength brought about by Lin Ming. This was because when the little black dragon was born, it already shared a bloodline with Lin Ming.

World strength gathered into a sea. This process continued for an unknown period of time, but finally, Lin Ming’s strength began to explosively grow!

At this time Lin Ming was already being reborn anew. His 36,000 pores emitted divine beams of light that shot out for a hundred thousand feet.

World strength raged around him. Even the stable space of the Emperor Bone Sea shook without end due to the unified strength of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s breakthrough!

Within their demon pagodas, when the ancient demons faced Lin Ming, they even felt a hint of… awe!

Although they had all been upper True Divinity existences and above when they were alive, they had already been dead for innumerable years. All that was left behind of them were wisps of their remnant souls. Now, facing the tremendous pressure brought about by Lin Ming’s breakthrough into True Divinity, this still wasn’t something easy for them to withstand.

Lin Ming slowly opened his eyes. The strength within his body seemed as if it would burst out of him, as if a punch could break a world, as if a chop could sever a river of stars.

He looked at his hands and slowly gripped his fists together.

This was the legendary True Divinity realm.

Once, it had seemed a distant and unachievable goal, but today he had finally broken through!

Chapter 2191 – Refining the Soul Emperor’s Strength

After breaking into True Divinity, Lin Ming had a fervent desire to fight!

However, he was well aware that after reaching this boundary, there were few in the entire universe that were capable of being his match!

Lin Ming pulled Sheng Mei’s hand.

After breaking into True Divinity his senses had become exceptionally sharp. He could faintly feel an energy hidden deep within Sheng Mei that was discordant with her bloodline.

This energy was similar to the world strength of the Emperor Bone Sea that Lin Ming had absorbed, but, it was actually much fiercer and far more evil.

“The strength of a totem abyssal!”

This thought flashed through Lin Ming’s thoughts. Thinking about it, he recalled that Sheng Mei once stated that the Soul Emperor had left behind two marks within her.

The first was a spirit mark; Sheng Mei had already shattered that by herself.

The next was an energy mark. The essence of this mark was the strength of a totem level abyssal. While it could be used in critical situations to control Sheng Mei, it could also protect her.

Originally, it would have been impossible for either Lin Ming or Sheng Mei to do anything to the Soul Emperor’s strength. But now that Sheng Mei and Lin Ming broke into True Divinity together, if they joined forces they absolutely could refine this strength.

“Lin Ming…”

Sheng Mei and Lin Ming had become of one mind. At this time, Sheng Mei also knew what Lin Ming wanted to do.

She slowly nodded. Lin Ming put his hands together, revolving the divine power within him.

Hum –

Weng –

Supernatural powers surged like a giant grinding pan, pressing down on the totem level strength within Sheng Mei’s body, disintegrating.

This strength was of an extremely high quality. Even if Sheng Mei and Lin Ming joined forces, they could only wear it away a bit at a time.

Peng!

With a loud explosive sound, this totem strength burst out, forming a hazy phantom in the skies.

This phantom had the appearance of an old youth. However, the appearance was greatly different from that of the Soul Emperor. His features were far more fierce and diabolical than the Soul Emperor’s and his face was pale white without the least bit of depth, as if he was a 10,000 year old corpse that had all its blood sucked out.

Without a doubt, this was the strength of a totem level abyssal left behind by the Soul Emperor.

Lin Ming looked at this phantom and a cold light glinted in his eyes. He poured out all of his strength into this phantom, slowly breaking it apart!

This phantom naturally wasn’t able to resist Lin Ming and Sheng Mei. But, as the phantom’s body broke apart, not only did it not have a frightened expression but there was still that lightly taunting smirk hanging on his face.

Lin Ming frowned. He placed his hands together and poured out the Asura Heavenly Dao and Holy Scripture Laws.

Bang!

The phantom finally exploded, turning into countless fragments that floated into the void. However, that taunting expression was like a curse, still lingering in the void and not scattering for a long time.

Lin Ming didn’t blink an eye. He thrust out a hand and the phantom exploded once more. This time, it completely turned into the purest world strength that was refined by Lin Ming’s energy.

“Lin Ming…”

Although Sheng Mei had just broken into True Divinity and her strength had risen precipitously, the Soul Emperor’s appearance still caused dark and gloomy clouds to envelop her heart.

This was unrelated to her heart of martial arts and it also wasn’t because she was afraid. It was because she had followed the Soul Emperor for many years and was deeply aware of just how terrifying he was.

“I seem to have… restored some of my previous life’s memories…”

Sheng Mei quietly muttered. After breaking through to True Divinity and undergoing a baptism of the world Laws and divine chains of order, she had faintly touched upon the vast and boundless memories of her past self from 10 billion years ago.

These memories contained the comprehensions of the Life and Death Laws of her past life, as well as her fighting skills and even the cultivation methods she trained in.

The memories were far too disorganized and convoluted. When Sheng Mei broke through to True Divinity she had only touched upon a small part of them and needed time to slowly sort them out. Even so, these memories would bring a massive advantage to her.

“Oh? What have you remembered?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. Sheng Mei’s memories were of crucial importance. Although Immortal Sovereign also knew of the events from 10 billion years past, he had perished far too early in the war between the races.

After Immortal Sovereign died, the races of the 33 Heavens still struggled against the Dark Abyss for tens of thousands of years. This was the part of history where the Asura Road Master and the races of the 33 Heavens were finally able to force back the abyssals, and as for the specifics of what happened here, Immortal Sovereign wasn’t sure.

And if Sheng Mei knew then this would naturally be a great help to Lin Ming understanding more.

However, Sheng Mei shook her head, saying, “I cannot remember many details about the great calamity from so long ago… I only know that 10 billion years ago, my previous life underwent a blood sacrifice and used a divine tool to manifest the Eternal Wall and block out the Dark Abyss. In truth, my past life also left behind a single turning point for reincarnation – this could be called the tenth cycle of reincarnation… in my past life I was cold and arrogant and even though I knew I would die in battle, I also hoped that I would be able to draw upon personally experiencing ‘death’ to comprehend the Life and Death Laws to a far more profound degree, and then after the ninth reincarnation, carve out a path for the tenth reincarnation. Like that, I would have been able to break through my limits, surpassing my father and even surpassing the Asura Road Master.

“But as for what happened afterwards, I do not know.

“Now, it seems that my tenth reincarnation failed. My memories were lost and my cultivation was abandoned, and I had to begin anew… moreover, I don’t know how but I was discovered by the Soul Emperor and he knew of my true identity.

“The Soul Emperor has incredibly hidden depths. He trained me, but I’m afraid there is some unknown purpose behind it all…”

As Sheng Mei spoke to here, Lin Ming’s thoughts chilled.

The Soul Emperor was unfathomably deep. Not only was he terrifyingly strong but he had laid down a plot of the heavens and earth that spread out over 100 billion years. Compared to him, those True Divinity overlords of the spiritas, saints, or Asura Road, were nothing at all.

Even the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was lacking.

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was the ruler of the saints and had the great ambitions of swallowing all life in the 33 Heavens, when compared to the Soul Emperor he was nothing at all.

Not to mention anything else, just amongst the many ancient demon emperors that the Soul Emperor had locked in the Emperor Bone Sea, if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were placed within he would only be at the middle or upper reaches of them…

Across a horrifying timespan of 100 billion years, even spreading into the last universal era, cruel and vicious elite demons had poured forth from the Dark Abyss, and there were dozens if not hundreds of powerful abyssals that were far stronger than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could hope to be.

But, when one considered the weakened human race of the 33 Heavens, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was far too formidable. Through the entire human race, they couldn’t find someone that could run away safely in front of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign much less defeat him.

And calculating the time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign should have already emerged from seclusion. By now, he had likely swallowed up the karmic link between the 33 Heavens’ essence gathering system and the human race.

If so, then humanity was in an even more precarious position.

Of course, to Lin Ming, this sort of karmic link of destiny had no influence. Whether it was in terms of Laws or the energy saved within his body, he far surpassed the essence gathering system. And even if the Laws were imprisoned, Lin Ming could still break through with his strength!

Now, the only things that Lin Ming dreaded were the Soul Emperor and Demon God’s Tomb.

However, before he confronted them he would need to return to the 33 Heavens.

He had to solve the trouble around the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Facing the terrifying enemy that was the Dark Abyss, the infighting between the humans and saints no longer held any meaning.

Of course, wanting the saints to believe him wouldn’t be easy. Even so, Lin Ming didn’t plan to try persuading them too much, because in the world of martial arts strength was all – strength would forever be a weapon countless times more powerful than words!

“I will return to the 33 Heavens!”

Lin Ming suddenly said. He looked at Sheng Mei. Although he didn’t say anything, his meaning was clear; he wanted Sheng Mei to follow him.

The Eternal Wall couldn’t cage in the races of the 33 Heavens. Even though Lin Ming became a True Divinity it still wouldn’t be a problem for him to pass.

As for the bloodlines within Sheng Mei, although they were convoluted, it was still her previous life that had formed the Eternal Wall through her blood sacrifice. Because she had been the one to lay it down, the Eternal Wall wouldn’t imprison even the True Divinity realm Sheng Mei.

Chapter 2192 – Origin Amethyst Crystal

The world strength that swept through the Emperor Bone Sea began to slowly weaken over three days.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei perfectly passed their trial.

Originally, breaking through to True Divinity meant that one would be a martial artist who stood at the highest echelons of the universe. Moreover, whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, they both possessed enough talent to show disdain to all other rivals at their boundary. Their strength was already great enough that they could affect the future of the universe and alter the grand chess game of the world!

However, Lin Ming also knew that this was only the first step in resisting the Soul Emperor. The Soul Emperor should currently be cultivating some sort of cultivation method, and once he finished he would be able to perfectly control the Demon God’s Tomb. By that time, his strength would reach incomprehensible levels!

The time they had was far too short. Once the Soul Emperor’s cultivation method reached large success he would learn of everything that occurred in the Demon God’s Tomb. At that time, Lin Ming would only be able to directly face the Soul Emperor in a life or death battle!

Ripples spread through the void and the enchantment that created the small independent world disappeared. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei appeared in the gaze of the many abyssals, a consummate pair of man and woman.

Seeing Lin Ming and Sheng Mei come out, Immortal released a long breath of relief. Then, a smile bloomed on his face. A thousand years of effort, 10 billion years of waiting, at least none of this had passed in vain.

“Much thanks, Senior!”

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei fell to their knees as they saw Immortal, deeply kneeling in respect.

This was because to Sheng Mei, Immortal could be called her true birth father and since Lin Ming and Sheng Mei could also be called husband and wife, then Immortal was Lin Ming’s father-in-law.

Moreover, whether it was the Holy Scripture Laws that allowed Lin Ming to undergo a nirvanic rebirth after losing his source soul, or whether it was this abyssal ritual, Immortal had shown great graciousness to them. He was their teacher.

Regardless of whether it was as a teacher or father, Immortal was more than worthy of this bow.

“Children, stand up.” Immortal said, his expression filled with happiness and gratitude. But while he was happy at seeing such juniors, he was also worried. He knew that after Lin Ming and Sheng Mei left, they would be faced with a truly terrifying enemy; the pressure on their shoulders was just far too heavy.

Lin Ming stood up and looked at the distant 30 level demon pagoda as well as the over 100 demon emperors that existed across the shores of the Yellow Springs River. He bowed to them all.

Especially the Demon Lord of the 30 level demon pagoda. He had awoken in order to help him and Sheng Mei, and this was a kindness that Lin Ming would forever remember.

“Seniors, junior will try his best in the future to rescue all of you from here.”

Lin Min solemnly vowed. But, the only reply he heard was raucous laughter.

“Heh! Brat, I have already died, so how could you possibly rescue us? If you have the ability then scatter my remnant soul – that will be true freedom.”

“Haha, I do not expect you to rescue us. The only possible way is if you manage to break apart the rules of this world. In the future when you step Beyond Divinity, bite out a piece of meat from that old freak and bring it here for us to eat, hahaha!”

The crowd of demons recklessly spoke.

After being sealed in the dark and enclosed demon pagodas, they faced an unchanging environment for tens of billions of years. The pain of this was unthinkable.

If a mortal were enclosed in a small black room for a month they would turn crazy and even develop irrevocable mental issues. Even though martial artists had formidable wills, they would still start to turn mad after being caged in for tens of billions of years.

Lin Ming was left speechless. He sighed inwardly. In truth, these many ancient demon emperors were locked here because they weren’t able to resist the temptation that was eternal life, even if at the time they arrived they knew the Emperor Bone Sea only contained an uncertain hope for them.

Lin Ming didn’t know whether or not eternal life should be pursued, but he deeply felt that eternal life actually didn’t mean eternal happiness, it didn’t mean eternal joy.

Eternal life was not the highest pursuit of martial arts.

The pursuit of martial arts was the heart.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but look at Sheng Mei. Currently, what Sheng Mei pursued was no longer eternal life, but instead what could truly touch her heart and move her soul.

To cultivate to fulfill one’s own heart, perhaps this was truly touching upon the peak of martial arts.

But in reflection, what was one’s heart?

Perhaps that was to allow oneself, one’s lovers, one’s spouses, one’s children, one’s family, one’s friends, one’s people, to allow everyone to live in peace and happiness…

……..

“Children, come with me.”

Immortal suddenly said. He turned towards the 33 level demon pagoda.

Immortal Sovereign was originally the master of the Magic Cube. With the help of the Magic Cube and Lin Ming, the gates to the 33 level demon pagoda had been smashed open. But during the 1000 some years that Lin Ming had gone into seclusion, potent world strength had gathered around the gates, superimposing upon itself in layers and evolving into shining demon runes.

The runes connected together, causing the demon relief on the gates to look that much fiercer, as if it the gates would close up once more.

“The Laws in the Emperor Bone Sea are truly dreadful…”

Lin Ming immediately thought. At this rate, the 33 demon pagoda that caged Immortal Sovereign would be sealed up again sooner or later.

At this time, the three of them already stood firmly in the demon pagoda.

Within the demon pagoda, everything was carved from black stone. This black stone had experienced a passing of innumerable billions of years and exuded the changings of times. Everything emitted the thick smell of history.

Immortal Sovereign put out a hand. He said to Lin Ming, “Give me the Magic Cube…”

Lin Ming was startled for a moment but didn’t question anything. He thrust out a hand and the Magic Cube appeared in his palm.

Then, he respectfully handed the Magic Cube to Immortal Sovereign.

The Magic Cube quietly floated in Immortal Sovereign’s palm, slowly revolving. Immortal Sovereign sighed with emotion. “In this universal era, three divine tools exist within the 33 Heavens. They are the Stone of Eternal Life, Grandmist Spirit Bead, as well as the… Origin Amethyst Crystal.”

“Origin Amethyst Crystal?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. Without a doubt, this divine tool was the Purple Card.

This was the first time that Lin Ming had heard the Purple Card’s true name. When Lin Ming referred to the Purple Card in the past, he was only referring to the color and shape of the Origin Amethyst Crystal.

“Is it the divine tool that the Asura Road Master used in the past?”

“Yes.” Immortal Sovereign nodded. “The Origin Amethyst Crystal might be a purple crystal form condensed from the source energies of this world. As for the Stone of Eternal Life and Grandmist Spirit Bead, they are also similar. The three divine tools are instruments that exist on the same tier. If they are completely activated they will evolve into a large universe, so they are in truth three world seeds.

“But, although these three divine tools are of the same tier, the reality is that they are divided into high and low.

“Mm?” Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were shocked. The three divine tools represented essence, energy, and divine, so how could they be divided into high and low?

Seeing Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s doubts, Immortal Sovereign explained, “The three divine tools themselves don’t differentiate into high and low. But, sometimes, the strength of a divine tool looks not at the divine tool itself, but at the person using them! Whether a divine tool can grow, the quality of that growth and the speed of that growth, all depends on the divine tool’s experiences with the user!”

“It depends on the user of the divine tool?” A light lit up in Lin Ming’s eyes.

“That’s right. This is especially true when a user reaches the realm Beyond Divinity. In truth, this boundary already stands on the same level as a great universe, and this person can create and destroy worlds. At this time, the user themselves is capable of influencing the three divine tools.

“Before the great calamity erupted 10 billion years ago, the Origin Amethyst Crystal had followed Asura for over a billion years. Similarly, the Stone of Eternal Life was also with me for several hundred million years. During these several hundred million years I was always together with the Stone of Eternal Life, constantly nourishing it with my strength and deepening its connection to my soul…”

As Immortal said this, Lin Ming was quietly shocked. Indeed, for a Beyond Divinity level existence to raise the Magic Cube like this, the Magic Cube was certainly out of the ordinary.

Let alone the Magic Cube that was a world seed, even a true great world could be constantly reinforced and nourished.

For instance, the Demon God’s Tomb. This was a very high level world, and over 100 billion years and all sorts of scheming by the Soul Emperor, its stability had increased by a large degree compared to the past.

Looking at the three divine tools, the Magic Cube and Purple Card seemed far more powerful than the Grandmist Spirit Bead. And, the symbol for this would be that the Magic Cube and Purple Card had managed to breed their own ‘artifact spirits’, yet the Grandmist Spirit Bead hadn’t.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming’s heart stirred. “Ruby, come out!”

As Lin Ming’s voice fell, a mass of fog rose up from the Magic Cube and turned into the cute appearance of a red-clothed little girl.

At this time, the little girl had a lost expression as she gazed at Immortal Sovereign. This black-robed man seemed familiar but also a complete stranger at the same time.

Chapter 2193 – Leaving Behind the Magic Cube

As Immortal Sovereign saw Ruby, he let out a sigh, infinite love and emotion filling his face. Although he was looking at Ruby, his gaze seemed to pierce through 10 billion years of time to see Ruby’s past appearance…

“Your name is Ruby?”

“Mm…”

Ruby stared wide-eyed at Immortal Sovereign with the curiosity of a child. She only thought that this man in front of her was familiar and he also had a nice smell exuding from him, just like her Big Brother Lin Ming.

“Ruby, huh… that’s a nice name.” Immortal Sovereign gently patted Ruby’s head. “These years have been hard on you…”

“Eh?”

Ruby didn’t know just what Immortal Sovereign was trying to say.

“Uncle, what did you say?”

“Nothing.”

Immortal Sovereign lovingly smiled and traced Ruby’s head again. Then, he turned to Lin Ming and said, “Take good care of her.”

“I will.” Lin Ming solemnly vowed.

Immortal Sovereign sighed. He said, “In the past, Ruby was the Stone of Eternal Life’s world spirit…”

“World spirit?”

Lin Ming was stunned. The so-called world spirit was the soul of a world. Mountains had mountain souls, seas had sea souls, stars had star souls, and weapons had artifact spirits.

All things in existence, when all sorts of lucky chances coincided and after an incredibly long period of time passed, could develop wisdom. For instance, the Ancient Elysium Seal was one such example.

Immortal Sovereign predicted that the Soul Emperor was the world spirit of the Demon God’s Tomb.

He appeared with the identity of ‘Deep’, seized the body of the Soul Emperor, and then took control of Flood. Not just that, but he controlled the two greatest influences of the Demon God’s Tomb – the Deep Alliance and Flood Alliance. Even powerhouses like Sheng Mei and Deep Child had been firmly grasped in his hands.

“Ruby, she seems to have also reincarnated… her memories have been lost. In that past war, her soul nearly turned to ashes.”

Immortal Sovereign casually stated. But, Lin Ming could imagine just how heaven-shaking that war had been.

The Magic Cube and the Purple Card went through the same war and Fishy’s experiences were likely similar to Ruby’s. Both of them had suffered catastrophic losses in that war 10 billion years ago.

Now, Fishy had returned to the Purple Card, which was the Origin Amethyst Crystal. Hopefully she would be able to recover a little…

Lin Ming prayed in his heart. Towards these two little girls with similar fates, he felt a deep sense of pity. In his eyes these two little girls were living beings, no different from the races that lived in the 33 Heavens.

“Child, stand.”

Immortal Sovereign said to Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei didn’t know what Immortal Sovereign was about to do, but she obediently stood in front of him.

“Don’t resist…”

As Immortal Sovereign spoke, he gently placed the Magic Cube between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows. The fist-sized Magic Cube began to rapidly shrink until it reached the size of a grain of rice. Then, it fell into the nine revolution red lotus mark between her eyebrows.

Lin Ming locked his sense on Sheng Mei the entire time. He knew that the Magic Cube had submerged into Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea.

To a martial artist, their spiritual sea was an extremely fragile yet important place. Once their spiritual sea cracked apart, a martial artist would suffer damage to their divine soul and perhaps even become an idiot.

The Magic Cube was a divine tool of the soul. Once it entered a person’s spiritual sea it could erupt with a strength that could instantly shred the spiritual sea to shreds.

However, because Lin Ming trusted Immortal Sovereign, he didn’t say a word. He quietly looked on, wanting to see what Immortal Sovereign was trying to do.

An incense stick of time passed. Immortal Sovereign’s concentration was completely focused and his complexion was dignified. It was clear he was giving his full effort, and was even somewhat strained.

After a while the Magic Cube flew back out. In that instant, Lin Ming faintly felt that a source mark belonging to Sheng Mei seemed to have quietly fallen into the Magic Cube…

“Senior, you…”

Lin Ming didn’t know what Immortal Sovereign was trying to do, he seemed to be carving Sheng Meil’s soul mark into the Magic Cube. As for why he was expending so much effort to do so, Lin Ming didn’t know.

But Immortal Sovereign wasn’t finished. He controlled the Magic Cube again so that it flew between Lin Ming’s eyebrows and sank into his spiritual sea.

Immortal Sovereign focused his concentration to leave behind Lin Ming’s soul mark within the Magic Cube. Then, he brought out the Magic Cube.

Lin Ming looked at Immortal Sovereign, a bit puzzled.

“Lin Ming, I asked you to bring out the Stone of Eternal Life today because I would like you to leave it here.”

Let alone Lin Ming, Immortal Sovereign’s words even shocked Sheng Mei. No one knew why he would make such a request.

Currently, it was obvious that the Stone of Eternal Life would be more useful to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s strength had already reached the top levels of the universe, and there was still much room left for growth in his future.

If there was the Magic Cube to help him, then he would have much more assurance to deal with the Soul Emperor.

“Senior, may you tell me the reason?”

When it came to Immortal Sovereign, Lin Ming felt a deep level of respect towards him.

Not to mention that Immortal Sovereign was his elder, but he had also died in the great 10 billion years ago for the races of the 33 Heavens and had established countless war merits.

Just the Holy Scripture Laws had helped him rise from the lowest valley of his life. There was also the thousand year process of the abyssal ritual that had allowed him to complete his final accumulations and break into True Divinity. With all of these things, Lin Ming felt nothing but gratefulness towards Immortal Sovereign.

This sort of benevolence couldn’t even be described as being as heavy as mountains and rivers.

Immortal Sovereign said, “If you face the Soul Emperor then the Magic Cube will be a powerful weapon. But in truth, upon reaching the boundary Beyond Divinity, it will not be able to display much of a wonderful role…”

When Lin Ming was at a low boundary, the Magic Cube was nearly invincible when it appeared. No matter how powerful a soul they still seemed incredibly fail in front of the Magic Cube.

But Beyond Divinity was different. This was a boundary where one could create and destroy worlds. The heights they stood were on a level on par with the great universe.

Not just the current times, but even 10 billion years ago, Immortal Sovereign possessed the Magic Cube and the Asura Road Master possessed the Purple Card, yet even together they were only able to cause heavy losses to the Soul Emperor and hadn’t been able to annihilate him.

From this it could be seen just how terrifying the Beyond Divinity boundary was.

Immortal Sovereign continued to say, “The function of the Stone of Eternal Life mainly manifests in its supportive abilities; it is by no means purely a weapon. As for the reason I would like for you to leave it behind, it is because during the last span of years, I have been in discussions with the Demon Lord. Perhaps… we have means of dealing with that old freak so that it isn’t easy for him to completely control the Emperor Bone Sea.

“But in order to do this, we will need the support of the Magic Cube.”

“But…” Lin Ming said, a bit hesitantly. He was afraid that the Magic Cube would be stolen away by the Soul Emperor. However, as he thought about it more carefully, with Immortal Sovereign’s skills and experience there was no way he could commit such a low level mistake.

If their plan couldn’t affect the Soul Emperor at all and would instead deliver a treasure to the Soul Emperor, then Immortal Sovereign would never carry out such a plan.

“I am only borrowing it. Your source soul mark is imprinted into the Stone of Eternal Life, and in the future I will have the means to return it to your hands…”

Immortal Sovereign confidently spoke these words.

For some unknown reason, Lin Ming had a foreboding premonition in his heart.

Immortal Sovereign and the Demon Lord would join together to resist the Soul Emperor; just what sort of result would occur?

Could they stand the ruthless retaliation of the Soul Emperor?

Lin Ming felt that with the Soul Emperor’s methods and his understandings of the soul, he likely had thousands of ways to refine a soul and thousands of ways to have one suffer unimaginable tortures.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming was a bit worried. “Senior, are you really sure you can contend with the Soul Emperor?”

In Lin Ming’s impression, the Soul Emperor was far too strong an existence. Immortal himself was nothing more than a wisp of remnant soul and the Demon Lord likely wasn’t much stronger. Just what could they do to the Soul Emperor?

“How will we know if we don’t try?”

Immortal Sovereign smiled. He didn’t go into much explanation as to what he would do. “Cultivate here for some time. Afterwards, you can leave…”

Lin Ming hesitated for a bit, and then reluctantly nodded. He deeply looked at the Magic Cube and left it behind.

In his life, Lin Ming had obtained the Magic Cube at 15 years of age, and now was the first time that the Magic Cube was leaving him.

The reason he did this came from his absolute trust in Immortal Sovereign.

Chapter 2194 – Leaving

The Dark Abyss’s 12th layer, the Endless Sea –

This was an unfathomably deep sea that extended onwards without end. The sea was a dark and deep blue that was thick and heavy, similar to mercury. The sea didn’t have ordinary fish and shrimps; only powerful demon beasts and abyssals were able to survive here.

At this time, the thick mist above the Endless Sea was as deep as a wall and as heavy as lead. A mortal couldn’t even see a foot in this fog and even a martial artist’s divine sense would be hindered a great deal.

“Ao!”

A sharp roar cut through the calm surface of the sea, echoing over the horizon. With it, the thick mist parted and dozens of figures hastily rushed out. These people all wore loose blue robes and had appearances no different from the races of the 33 Heavens; they were the ancient race martial artists of the Dark Abyss.

These ancient race martial artists seemed panicked and their movements were messy, as if they were being hunted down by something.

“Those damned beasts can also fly through the skies and shuttle through the seas. Their speed is also much faster than ours. If we cannot reach the home base fast enough then they’ll eventually overtake us.”

A middle-aged martial artist panted. He gripped symbol papers in his hands and every now and then he would crush one and throw it behind himself. As the symbol paper exploded in the thick fog, a howl would follow; it was clear it was some sort of demon beast.

Unfortunately, these yells weren’t the screams of demon beasts being killed by the explosions of the symbol papers, but cries of pain from the demon beasts being injured.

The middle-aged man’s symbol papers were only meant to create some trouble for the demon beasts behind him and delay them for as long as he could; they simply couldn’t kill them and only served to enrage them.

But there was nothing else that could be done.

“Father, I remember that there is a nameless island in front of us. This island has towering trees and these trees are also demon trees that are as hard as iron. If we lead those demon fish inside the dense forest then they’re sure to be slowed.”

The blue-clothed girl who spoke was the daughter of the middle-aged man. Although she was young she had an extremely high status in the group, and this clearly stemmed from her powerful strength.

As soon as she offered this suggestion, the ancient race martial artists felt their hearts sink. That forest of demon trees wasn’t friendly to them either. Those demon trees could also devour people, and if they rushed into the forest then it would be no different from entering the tiger’s den after fleeing the wolves. If the fight continued like this, they were bound to be in an even more dire state.

But the current situation didn’t allow for any hesitation. If they didn’t enter the demon tree forest then there really wouldn’t be any chance to survive.

The howls behind them grew increasingly close. The thick mist above the sea was cut open by the demon beasts. A number of flat creatures that were dozens of feet long were racing over the sea, dragging a long python-like tail behind them as they appeared from the fog.

These were clearly the demon fish that the blue-clothed girl spoke of.

These demon fish were also one of the countless species of abyssals. However, their intelligence was far, far lower than most other abyssals’.

At this time, these demon fish would soon overtake the ancient race martial artists. If this were to continue then they wouldn’t even make it to the demon forest.

The blue-clothed girl clenched her teeth and turned around to slash out with her sword!

To turn around in a chase like this to attack was an incredibly dangerous move. It was easy to be surrounded by these flying demon fish and then be eaten up without even bones remaining.

Moreover, the blue-clothed girl’s sword strike wouldn’t necessarily be able to harm these demon fish; the most it would do was delay them a little.

The disparity in strength between the two sides was simply far too great.

The moment that the blue-clothed girl struck out with her sword, the middle-aged man felt his heart skip a beat; he was afraid something would happen to his daughter.

However, before he could cry out in alarm, a stunned expression filled his face. He stared helplessly on as after the blue-clothed girl slashed out her sword, the single sword light suddenly turned into an overwhelming wave that changed the winds and clouds, causing a rain of blood to fall down from the skies!

The hundreds of demon fish were completely split open by this sword light. They were all torn apart, instantly killed without even time to scream!

And after the demon fish died, even the fog above the sea was cut apart. Every sword light cut opened sections that were a foot wide in the mist. Without the fog to block their way, the middle-aged man could see through this slits to dozens of miles away.

And after several breaths of time, all the fog dissipated. As if it were blown away by a great storm, the entire sea appeared.

The middle-aged man was shocked and the blue-clothed girl was also startled; this sword light was clearly not sent out by them.

Not to mention the might behind the sword light, just the color was different. The little girl’s sword light was blue, but that overwhelming sword light just now was black.

Could the black sword light be from a master who caught up to them from the home base?

This thought flashed through the mind of the blue-clothed girl. Then, not too far away, she could see a black-clothed woman floating high in the skies.

This woman had an appearance that neared perfection. Her long hair hung to her waist and she unknowingly exuded a cold and lofty aura that seemed as if she were demanding all others stay at least a thousand miles away. This sort of arrogant aura wasn’t deliberate, but was merely something she was born with, making it hard for anyone to muster the courage to look at her.

She had no sword in her hands. In truth, she hadn’t used a sword just then either; she had only used her sword fingers.

“This is the ancient race rebel army you spoke of…”

The black-clothed woman lightly said. It was only then that the ancient race martial artists discovered someone else had appeared in the skies at some unknown time.

This man had looks that seemed carved by a saber. His eyes were like a sea of stars, unfathomably deep.

After this man appeared, the black-clothed woman stood beside him, just a little bit behind. Whether it was in mindset or in action, this woman seemed to take this man as the lead.

Such a terrifying woman took this man as a lead. Then this man…

The ancient race martial artists were completely dumbfounded. No matter how they looked at it, this man and woman didn’t seem like abyssals at all, but were similar to themselves in appearance. How was this possible…?

Could it be…

A light lit up in the middle-aged man’s mind. Many years ago, the leader of the ancient race rebel army, Mo Eversnow, once had some old friend visit her. This person was said to be a man with strength no less than that of Mo Eversnow.

Was it him?

As this middle-aged man was lost in his thoughts, the man actually closed his eyes and felt the salty sea breeze that wafted past him, his mind filled with emotions.

1500 years!

Just the abyssal ritual continued for 1080 years. In addition to the 10 previous years, that was around 1100 years.

Afterwards, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei didn’t immediately emerge, but stayed in to cultivate for another 400 years to thoroughly consolidate their lower True Divinity boundary.

After that, with the help of Immortal Sovereign and the Demon Lord, they directly left the Demon God’s Tomb using a hidden passage and even passed through the Dark Abyss’s 18th layer in a single journey and went all the way to the 12th layer.

All of this happened without anyone noticing.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s True Divinity level strength had completely stabilized. The Nine Stars of the Dao Place was just a little bit away from opening the eighth Dao Palace.

It could be said that Lin Ming’s strength had undergone its greatest rise upwards in his life!

He had been reborn!

After returning to the Dark Abyss, Lin Ming planned to head back to the 33 Heavens with the fastest speed possible. But before that he had to find Mo Eversnow.

He now knew the secrets of the Demon God’s Tomb and also knew of the upcoming war between the Dark Abyss and the 33 Heavens. If Mo Eversnow were to continue staying in the Dark Abyss then it would be extremely dangerous for her.

Lin Ming’s thoughts were to leave the Dark Abyss together with Mo Eversnow.

Thus, he quickly found this place using a mark he had agreed with Mo Eversnow beforehand.

Within Lin Ming’s current strength, as long as he was within a certain range then his sense could lock onto Mo Eversnow’s position. After all, Lin Ming was familiar with the array formations she had arranged, so to him these array formations didn’t block him much.

“The ancient races have truly declined…”

Sheng Mei sighed. She already knew the situation of the ancient races, however, she hadn’t known of her life experiences before so the situation of the ancient races was irrelevant to her. Now, she knew that in her previous life, she was part of the primal god race.

Whether it was the Asura Rod Master or Immortal Sovereign, both of them stemmed from the primal god race.

“Mm… good fortune is forever changing.” Lin Ming sighed with emotion. Then, he turned to the ancient race squad and said, “Is Miss Mo present? Take me to see her…”

The ancient race martial artists glanced at each other. Then, the middle-aged man nodded and slowly said, “The leader, she… she is here…”

Chapter 2195 – Returning to the 33 Heavens

The ancient race uprising had continued for over a thousand years. For this revolt to continue for such a long time was mainly because of the opening of the Demon God’s Tomb which had shifted the majority of the Demon Association’s attention somewhere else.

After the venture into the Demon God’s Tomb ended, all of the masters from the Flood Alliance and Deep Alliance had been utterly destroyed. To the numerous abyssal influences, this was simply a lightning strike from nowhere!

For a long time after the exit to the Demon God’s Tomb opened, not a single higher abyssal came out. This left the numerous abyssal influences bewildered.

Every large influence, including even the totem level influences, had been severely wounded. And with the deaths of several True Divinities and dozens upon dozens of Empyreans, this wasn’t something that any influence could withstand.

During such times, the Demon Association naturally didn’t have the heart to pay attention to the ancient race uprising that wasn’t on too large of a scale to begin with.

Moreover, in these past years, the ancient race rebels had remained far more low key. From the beginning when they battled all around, they went quiet in order to recuperate and further develop themselves.

Mo Eversnow had inherited a part of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s memories. In addition to some ancient race cultivation methods that Lin Ming provided, all of these things were distributed amongst the ancient race martial artists to practice with. In these past years many new powerhouses appeared in the ancient race resistance.

The headquarters of the ancient race resist was deep in the Endless Sea.

Before entering the headquarters, Mo Eversnow had sensed Lin Ming and similarly Lin Ming sensed Mo Eversnow.

The two met each other in a grand hall. Mo Eversnow could see through Lin Ming’s cultivation with a glance.

Deep astonishment rose up in Mo Eversnow’s face. “You… you broke into True Divinity!?”

Lin Ming had broken into the Empyrean realm at around 700 years of age. Afterwards, he spent 5000 years in Tragic Death Valley to reach the peak of the middle Empyrean realm. After that, he took another 1500 years to break into True Divinity. This degree of speed was simply defying the heavens.

“Mm… it is because of reasons concerning the Demon God’s Tomb. It is a long story. Senior-apprentice Sister, let us speak as we go.”

“Go? Go where?” Mo Eversnow was slightly surprised. She didn’t know what Lin Ming was referring to.

Moreover, she was also puzzled about who Sheng Mei was, standing near Lin Ming.

Even Lin Ming had been surprised about Sheng Mei’s presence in the Dark Abyss. It was natural for Mo Eversnow to not know about her either.

“We will return to the 33 Heavens!”

Lin Ming succinctly stated. The ancient race rebel army consisted of several hundreds of thousands of people. This amount of people could easily fit into Primordius Heavenly Palace, and transferring them inside wouldn’t be difficult either.

And with Lin Ming’s strength, he could easily help them pass through the horrifying energy storms around the Eternal God Wall to successfully escape the Dark Abyss.

Lin Ming was already impatient to return. First, the Dark Abyss was too dangerous and second, he was worried about humanity’s current situation.

And in truth, humanity’s situation was just as Lin Ming worried; it wasn’t good at all…

…….

33 Heavens, wild universe –

Over 1500 years had passed since Lin Ming left to go to the Dark Abyss.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign left seclusion 600 years ago, and by that time, humanity’s war campaign back into the Divine Realm had ended. Empyrean Divine Dream led humanity back into the wild universe, and by using the Asura Decree, another connection had been formed through the God Lamenting Wall, linking the wild universe with another neighboring universe.

By relying on these two incomparably vast universes, humanity and the saints began a guerilla war once more.

Humanity had caused severe damage to the saints before the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign emerged from seclusion. Thus, even though it was impossible for humanity to directly face the saints now, the saints had limited manpower and resources. With this, the human forces were able to rely on the complex terrains within the wild universes to barely maintain themselves.

This was a chaotic meteor belt with space storms and interstellar dust that blocked a martial artist’s sense. Because this interstellar dust was able to block out the light of stars, this region was hard to locate in the broad universe.

In fact, finding one such meteor belt was meaningless. In the wild universe, the number of similar meteor belts formed of interstellar dust was counted with ‘trillions’ as the base unit. Every interstellar belt could extend for trillions of miles, and if one wished to search through all of them it required transferring over a massive number of masters to carry out a full on carpet search with their sense.

Those with the ability to carry out such a search in a short period of time needed to have at least an Empyrean level cultivation, and many saint Empyreans had perished. Even so, Empyreans still needed to cultivate. It would be impossible for the saints to encircle humanity in the wild universe like they did the first time.

In this meteor belt there were all sorts of complex spatial structures that formed a maze. In the center of this maze were layers upon layers of interconnected illusory magic arrays.

These illusory magic arrays were incomparably mystical. Let alone an ordinary saint martial artist, even if a saint Empyrean were to step inside, they would be left confused by the arrays and stranded within.

Such potent illusory magic arrays were Divine Dream’s handiwork. With her strength, it would be impossible for anyone to break through them unless the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign personally arrived.

In the last 8000-9000 years that humanity had resisted the saints, although humanity had suffered losses, they also grew by a great deal. This was particularly true when it came to their abilities to conceal themselves and lay out formations.

In order to protect the growing seeds of humanity, Empyrean Divine Dream personally laid down hundreds of these illusory magic arrays through the wild universe, making it that much harder for the saints to find them.

Like this, humanity continued to struggle with the saints. They managed to hold on, but there was a matter that caused dark clouds to hover in the hearts of all human martial artists.

That was… when the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had gone into seclusion, he had swallowed up the destiny of humanity’s essence gathering system. Now, there was a divide that separated humanity from the essence gathering system Heavenly Dao.

This divide didn’t affect the existing strength of a martial artist, but it hindered them from furthering their cultivation.

Now, when a human martial artist cultivated to the Nine Divine Shifts, they would feel incredibly strained. At the World King boundary, this resistance increased by hundreds and thousands of time, making it almost impossible to break through.

As for lower Empyreans rising to middle Empyreans, and middle Empyreans rising to upper Empyreans, this process was originally not easy to begin with, but it had now become far more difficult.

If this continued, then the destiny of humanity would eventually fade away to nothing.

This was the so-called moment when a race’s destiny reached its end.

In the endless flow of history, it wasn’t uncommon for a race to meet their demise because their destiny had reached its end. 10 billion years ago, the primal god race were unimaginably powerful, yet they too slowly withered away because their destiny was at its end.

Compared to the primal god race, humanity was far from being able to compare, whether it was in strength or numbers. Thus it wouldn’t be strange if humanity perished in this great calamity.

Now, the young generations of humans had already started to wither and wane. Underneath this curse, martial artists with ordinary degrees of talent were only able to reach the Divine Sea realm. Proud children of humanity would be able to break into Holy Lords, but upon encountering the World King realm, all sorts of resistances would rise to meet them so that they weren’t successful.

An atmosphere of gloom and dread began to slowly spread amongst humanity.

Although there was the protection of array formations, there were no new masters born within the younger generation and it was difficult for the older generation to rise again in strength. Amongst the human powerhouses, one dead meant one less.

If this continued for long enough, then humanity would be defeated without even being able to put up a fight.

Within this belt of interstellar dust, within a small independent world –

A youth sat in the void. This youth wore black clothes and had a spear harnessed to his shoulders. His looks were solemn and decisive, and the edges of his face were sharp and distinct. He gave off a swift and fierce aura.

Looking at this youth carefully, he resembled Lin Ming somewhat.

He was Lin Ming’s eldest son – Lin Huang.

At this time, six people were standing in front of Lin Huang – Xiao Moxian, Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, Hang Chi, Emperor Shakya, as well as a black-clothed girl with a beautiful appearance and skin as white as snow.

This girl appeared around 17-18 years old. Her figure was slim and her legs were thick and round. Although she was beautiful, her weapon was a dark red nine foot long scythe.

This scythe had an extremely fearsome shape. It was like three sharp fangs were stacked on the edge from large to small, but even the smallest blade was half a foot wide. When this weapon was contrasted with the girl’s slender figure and her porcelain-like skin, it formed a strong visual contrast.

This black-clothed girl had once encountered Lin Ming. Her name was Sable Ink and she was Dark Demon Monarch’s direct disciple. She was renowned within the younger generation of humanity and was called the second coming of Xiao Moxian.

At this time, Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, Sable Ink, Lin Huang, Hang Chi, and Xiao Moxian were sitting at the ends of a six-point star drawn in the void.

As for Emperor Shakya, his hands were gathered together as he stood still in the center of these six people.

An invisible momentum rose out from Emperor Shakya’s body, forming a different world.

In this world, there were buddhist platforms and buddhas reciting abstract truths. Beams of divine light soared through the skies, turning into flows of golden scriptures that snaked through the void.

After 1500 years, Emperor Shakya had broken into True Divinity!

Chapter 2196 – Imprisonment of the Divine Chains

Emperor Shakya had always been one of the most peak powerhouses of humanity. If it weren’t for the great decline of humanity’s martial arts civilization, his road of cultivation would have been far smoother.

In the first great invasion that the saints launched in the wild universe, he had been at the Empyrean limit. But now, he had finally stepped into True Divinity.

Emperor Shakya was also the second True Divinity of humanity.

Seven people were sitting in a grand hall, silently. Emperor Shakya sat above a lotus throne, his ten fingers weaving together as he produced buddhist seal after buddhist seal.

This lotus throne was one of Mount Potala’s magic tools. Mount Potala had an inheritance that extended for billions of years, and the throne was one of their most precious cultivation support items.

When it came to magic tools, there were numerous offensive and defensive kinds. But when it came to auxiliary magic tools, they were actually quite rare because the array formations required to refine one were exceedingly complex.

Hum –

Hum –

Golden light dazzled outwards on the lotus throne. The surrounding heaven and earth origin energy gathered around the six surrounding people. For a time, the light Laws sparkled and Supreme phantoms appeared behind these six people.

A Supreme phantom was the symbol of an Empyrean.

Now, Dragon Fang, Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang, Hang Chi, Sable Ink, and Jun Bluemoon all had Empyrean level cultivations; the only difference was that they were in different small boundaries.

In the great calamity of humanity, many human masters grew at an astonishing speed.

For geniuses at the rank of Lin Huang or Sable Ink, they didn’t need 10,000 years to become an Empyrean; 7-8 thousand years was enough. 10,000 and several thousand some years was enough time for them to reach the upper Empyrean realm or even the limits of an Empyrean.

Unfortunately, several hundred years ago the destiny of humanity had been imprisoned, so if these people wanted to make a breakthrough they first had to break through the Heavenly Dao’s divine chains of order.

However, wanting to break through these divine chains was easier said than done. When Lin Ming broke through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he had relied upon an inestimable accumulation of destiny and treasures. In addition, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had dual cultivated, and while he was being chased down by Tian Mingzi and his back was against the river in a life or death situation, it was only during that critical moment that he broke through the Heavenly Dao dao diagram and obtained the power of the Nine Stars.

But amongst humanity, there really wasn’t anyone capable of comparing with Lin Ming, and it was also difficult to reproduce the same situation that Lin Ming faced in the past.

Thus, the proud elites of humanity each started to test different methods to make breakthroughs.

For instance, within the great array formation managed by Emperor Shakya, six Empyreans attacked the bindings of the divine chains together.

Within the great array, Emperor Shakya was only playing a supportive role. Whether or not one could break past the chains relied on a martial artist themselves.

The higher a cultivation a martial artist possessed, the stronger their shackles would be.

Ultimately, everything boiled down to one’s talent, potential, as well as their determination in attacking chains of the Heavenly Dao.

All of this together decided if one was strong enough to defy the heavens and change their lives!

Six lights wove together into a star. Emperor Shakya emitted brilliant golden light from every acupoint. This light coalesced into a buddha as the sound of chanting sutras lingered in the world, persisting for a long time.

At this time, in the skies, the divine chains of order had formed a heavenly dao diagram that pressed down on the heads of all present.

The lotus throne beneath Emperor Shakya’s feet revolved and a golden hand shot upwards. At the same time, the six Empyrean martial artists around Emperor Shakya each tried to break through their own respective cultivation bottlenecks!

During these years that the essence gathering system had been sealed away, they had all reached their peaks in their small boundaries. If it weren’t for the divine chains of order hindering them, they would have already made their breakthroughs.

Bang!

The golden hand gathered together with the strength of the six people and violently crashed into the heavenly dao diagram, causing it to shake!

Again and again, the brutal strikes continued. Every time the dao diagram dimmed, it was immediately supplemented by the golden divine chains of order that snaked around like pythons, adding more energy to the dao diagram.

If one attacked the heavenly dao diagram, they would cause a backlash to occur.

Xiao Moxian was fortunately able to withstand it. She had a deep background and possessed formidable potential, and she even possessed the body of a God Beast.

But as for Hang Chi and Sable Ink, they were shaken by the strength of the Heavenly Dao. Their meridians were damaged by the shaking strength and blood flowed out from the corners of their mouths.

Before their impact against the heavenly dao diagram lasted for an incense stick of time, they had already exhausted themselves.

If this continued then they would suffer catastrophic and irreversible losses.

They slowed down. Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, and Lin Huang also slowed down a great deal. After an incense stick of time passed, Xiao Moxian stopped too.

This time, their attempt to break past the chains of the Heavenly Dao had been defeated.

This result didn’t leave them surprised because they had already failed many times before this.

But, the repeated failures caused gloomy clouds to appear in their hearts.

The several of them were already the elites amongst the human elites. If they weren’t able to break through the chains of the Heavenly Dao then there was no need to mention other martial artists.

During these years, many human martial artists had turned their gaze towards the body transformation system and began to cultivate the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

This included Lin Huang; he placed even more of his time in cultivating the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

But humanity’s body transformation technique had been abandoned for 3.6 billion years. How easy could it be to redevelop this cultivation system from the ground up?

Moreover, even the body transformation Laws were still partially blocked by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. If one wished to cultivate them, there was still tremendous resistance!

In truth, after humanity’s destiny had been shackled, besides relying on one’s potential to break through, one could also rely on brute force.

When a martial artist reached the upper True Divinity realm and they possessed the corresponding Laws (such as the Swallowing Laws or the Curse Laws), then they would have the ability to change the destiny of an ordinary race. If they could reach the realm Beyond Divinity, then they would have the ability to create and destroy worlds, and even influence the flow of destiny for an entire universe.

Likewise, if one wished to use brute force to break through the chains of the Heavenly Dao, they needed at least an upper True Divinity level of strength to accomplish this.

However, amongst the entire human race, no one had reached this boundary.

When it came to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, whether it was Divine Dream or Emperor Shakya, they were both a great deal weaker than him.

And with the essence gathering system locked away, it would be even more difficult for Divine Dream or Emperor Shakya to surpass the Good Fortune Saint Son.

At this time, Sable Ink swallowed a pill and began to meditate and restore herself. As she stabilized her tumbling blood vitality, she looked up at the heavenly dao diagram that was gradually fading away into the skies. She couldn’t help but sigh deeply and say, “Senior Lin Ming… he is truly an outstanding human hero.”

Sable Ink was well aware that when the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was sealed away in the past, Lin Ming had relied on his amazing potential, his determination, as well as Xiao Moxian’s help to break past the heavenly dao diagram.

With Emperor Shakya assisting through an array formation and the six Empyreans joining forces, the difficulty of breaking into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace in the past was far greater than what these six people had to undergo now.

Yet none of these geniuses were able to break past the barrier. Moreover, the more attempts they tried, the more they could feel how terrifying the bindings of the Heavenly Dao were. Without feeling this for themselves, none of them would have had an inkling of how difficult this was for Lin Ming in the past.

“Lin Ming…”

As Xiao Moxian heard Sable Ink speak of Lin Ming, her gaze seemed to turn distant. Since Lin Ming left, he had spent 500 years in Tragic Death Valley and around 1500 years in the Demon God’s Tomb; he had been gone for a full 2000 years.

Because Xiao Moxian hadn’t cultivated in Tragic Death Valley for such a long time like Lin Ming did, her age hadn’t yet reached 10,000 years. However, for most of this time, she and Lin Ming had been separated.

In their first parting, 7000 years had passed. In their second parting, 2000 years had already passed…

Moreover, this time, she didn’t know if Lin Ming was alive or dead, or even if he was doing well. How could she not be worried?

Lin Ming had gone to the Dark Abyss this time, and that place was just far too dangerous…

“Father will be safe.”

Beside Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang had just recovered. He gently held onto his mother’s hand to comfort her.

“Mm.” Xiao Moxian nodded.

At this time, Sable Ink felt a bit embarrassed by her loss of decorum just now. She said, “In the past, even when Senior Lin was being chased down by Soaring Feather God King he was still able to create miracles. This time Senior Lin will surely return and his strength will definitely have risen. He should have steadily reached the upper Empyrean realm, or perhaps even reached… peak Empyrean!”

Sable Ink’s eyes flashed with reverence and admiration.

There was no one in humanity that didn’t respect Lin Ming. And, Sable Ink and Lin Huang could be considered peers of the same generation. She had grown up listening to Divine Dream tell stories of Lin Ming, and when it came to respect and worship of the older generation, her fervor was naturally much more intense than that of those like Dragon Fang and Jun Bluemoon who came from Lin Ming’s generation.

“Peak Empyrean…”

Xiao Moxian couldn’t confirm this. In fact, Lin Ming’s talent and potential mainly manifested in his ability to leap past boundaries to fight.

In terms of cultivation speed, Lin Ming couldn’t be regarded as an extreme genius; he was even somewhat slower than Xiao Moxian.

When Xiao Moxian had broken into the Empyrean realm, Lin Ming had only been a half-step Empyrean; he wasn’t much faster than Lin Huang.

This was mainly because the Laws that Lin Ming cultivated were far too high and their difficulty far too great.

Now, Xiao Moxian was merely a little bit from reaching the peak Empyrean realm. It would already be wonderful if Lin Ming could reach the upper Empyrean realm.

Chapter 2197 – Meeting

“We cannot keep depending on Benefactor Lin. Although we failed in breaking through the heavenly dao diagram this time, we have still gained experience. If this time fails we have next time, and if next time fails we will have the time after that. There will come a day when we break past these chains, and once those chains break, our martial arts accumulations will rise even further than before.”

Emperor Shakya slowly said. This could be a summary of the failures in breaking past the heavenly dao diagram this time.

Emperor Shakya was well aware that they couldn’t pin all their hopes on Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s current cultivation was likely at the upper Empyrean realm and to defeat the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign at this boundary was impossible. No matter how heaven-defying Lin Ming’s talent was, there still wouldn’t be a chance for him.

“Benefactor Ji…”

Emperor Shakya said as he saw Xiao Moxian appear a bit listless. He wanted to say some words of comfort but didn’t know just where to start.

“I’m fine.” Xiao Moxian waved her hand. “I understand that Lin Ming won’t return for a long time, but I’m simply a bit worried since I haven’t received any news about him in such a long time…”

With what Xiao Moxian knew of Lin Ming, his character was firm and stubborn and once he decided on something he would stick to it until the end. Now that he had gone out adventuring, she wondered if he would be able to cultivate enough to contend with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign when he returned.

However, to resist the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was easier said than done. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign possessed immeasurably deep strength to begin with, and now that he had swallowed humanity’s destiny, his strength had likely taken another step forwards. And in the 33 Heavens, besides the Soul Emperor who had never acted and whose strength no one knew, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was an absolutely invincible existence.

If Lin Ming wanted to surpass the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign he would likely need a considerably long period of time. Like this, she might not see him for at least another 2000-3000 years.

Moreover, the essence gathering system had been blocked by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Would Lin Ming’s breakthroughs be hindered by this?

“Father will surely be able to break past the chains of the Heavenly Dao.”

Lin Huang confidently said. He could sense what Xiao Moxian was thinking. Lin Huang’s reverence and admiration of Lin Ming had already reached unreasonable degrees.

“Brother Lin can even break past the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, so there shouldn’t be any problems with the essence gathering system’s Heavenly Dao. The likelihood is that his cultivation speed will be slowed down a little, but to Brother Lin, this might not be a bad thing. There are no chains that can cage in a True Dragon.”

Jun Bluemoon quietly commented.

“As for me, I am looking forward to Lin Ming returning and watching him break through the shackles of the Heavenly Dao with my own eyes. Perhaps I can even gain some enlightenment.”

Dragon Fang said as he looked up at the vanishing heavenly dao diagram in the skies. As the spatial ripples faded away, there was a deep sense of unwillingness in his heart.

“Let everything continue on its natural course…” Xiao Moxian silently said. But at this time, her body shook. The pill bottle that was in her hand tumbled to the ground, shaking until the medicinal pill within tumbled out.

Everyone around Xiao Moxian was startled. With her strength it was naturally impossible for a pill bottle to slip out from her hands.

“Mother, what is it?”

“What is it?”

Everyone was concerned. Emperor Shakya had already stood up, his hand tracing his spatial ring. His expression was dignified. During this extraordinary period of time, even they weren’t safe within Divine Dream’s illusory magic arrays. There was a high chance that there could be an enemy attack!

Xiao Moxian touched her chest and took out an old string necklace.

This necklace was the Thousand Mile Heartlink that allowed Lin Ming to find Xiao Moxian when he went to the wild universe. The Thousand Mile Heartlink was refined through the divine runic arts, and because of Xiao Moxian using it too many times in the past, its energy had been used up and the divine runic symbol within had disintegrated.

But before Lin Ming left, he had used his divine runic arts to transform the Thousand Mile Heartlink.

Not only did Lin Ming draw up a new divine runic symbol but he also strengthened its function. In the past, Xiao Moxian had only been able to communicate with Lin Ming in a one-way channel, but now they could communicate both ways.

This was to avoid a situation like in the past, where Lin Ming wasn’t able to immediately locate Xiao Moxian after arriving at the wild universe. Otherwise if Lin Ming were to return to the wild universe and still had to look for her in the endlessness of space, then that would just be giving himself more trouble.

Just now, Xiao Moxian had felt a shaking within the Thousand Mile Heartlink. And to be able to commune through the Thousand Mile Heartlink, there was only one person – Lin Ming!

“Lin Ming… he… has returned!”

Xiao Moxian looked at the Thousand Mile Heartlink in her hands with disbelief, her voice filled with a hint of hesitation and uncertainty.

Everyone was startled. Before they could respond, the Thousand Mile Heartlink in Xiao Moxian’s hands began to glow with a dim light.

Everyone could see this light, but only Xiao Moxian could hear the sound that transmitted from the Thousand Mile Heartlink…

It really was Lin Ming!

Lin Ming had returned!

“Benefactor Lin, he has already come back?”

Emperor Shakya was stunned. He originally thought that after Lin Ming left, he wouldn’t return until he reached a level where he could contend with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Otherwise there was no meaning in returning.

But only two thousand years had passed; this was far too early.

“Father shouldn’t have encountered trouble, right…?” Lin Huang muttered, a bit worried.

“Perhaps Senior Lin was thinking of his family and was afraid that you were worrying over him.” The one who spoke was Sable Ink. Her voice was pleasant and her words warmed Xiao Moxian’s heart.

Indeed, during all these years, she was worried about Lin Ming.

“He is safe.”

Xiao Moxian happily said. She felt as if a giant stone had been lifted from her heart.

“Unfortunately, Divine Dream went into seclusion to impact the middle True Divinity realm, so we cannot rashly disturb her… mm… Hang Chi, you contact Vast Universe and Dark Demon Monarch to hurry here. Tell them to prepare a welcoming banquet for Lin Ming!”

Emperor Shakya excitedly said. Many important figures of humanity were gathered at this base. As for others, they could come from nearby bases.

The return of the Human Sovereign Lin Ming was an important event for humanity!

“There is no need to prepare a welcoming banquet for now, he has already arrived…” As she spoke, Xiao Moxian began to quickly hurry outside the hall.

“He’s already here?” Emperor Shakya said, a bit puzzled. It had to be known that there were layers upon layers of illusory magic arrays outside their base and these array formations were all personally laid down by Empyrean Divine Dream.

Because of the Thousand Mile Heartlink, Lin Ming was able to easily locate their position. But, he might need to spend some effort getting past the illusory magic arrays.

Everyone hurried to follow her.

As they flew outside the hall, they saw that around 10 miles away in the void, a black-clothed man stepped forwards. These ten miles was crossed in a single step; he arrived in front of them.

This man was Lin Ming!

“Lin Ming!”

“Father!”

“Senior Lin…”

Several people cried out together. Xiao Moxian’s breath quickened and her eyes began to glisten.

After a 2000 year parting, she was able to see Lin Ming stand safely in front of her. This was more important than anything.

“Mm, Senior Lin’s cultivation…”

Sable Ink was dumbfounded. When Lin Ming first returned, Xiao Moxian was too excited so she didn’t pay too much attention to this, but as for Sable Ink and Lin Ming’s other admirers, the first thing they noticed was his cultivation.

At this time, from Lin Ming’s body, she could clearly feel a terrifying aura that was still able to shake her mind and soul while being suppressed.

It was like the Lin Ming in the skies had become as deep as the universe, filled with overwhelming potential and strength that no one could fathom.

Could this be…

The True Divinity realm!?

“How is this…”

“True Divinity!!!?”

Everyone was shocked. Let alone Emperor Shakya, Dragon Fang, and Hang Chi, even Lin Huang who respected Lin Ming the most still couldn’t believe this.

True Divinity was an extremely harsh threshold on the road of martial arts. Before the great calamity of the Divine Realm erupted, humanity’s martial arts civilization had declined and they lost their methods to break into True Divinity. Because of this, for the last 3.6 billion years there hadn’t been a single True Divinity appear. No matter how talented a genius, they still fell before this threshold.

Although the road to True Divinity had been opened, two thousand years ago when Lin Ming left he had only been a lower Empyrean. To return as a True Divinity after this time was far too exaggerated.

This sort of cultivation speed couldn’t even be described as heaven-defying.

“Lin Ming, how could you break through so quickly?”

“If you break through at such a speed, will your foundation be unstable?”

“This isn’t a consideration of whether one’s foundation is steady. Even if he ignored his foundation he still couldn’t break through so quickly. Moreover, how could someone with an unstable foundation break into True Divinity?”

For a time, everyone was confused.

Moreover, several hundred years ago, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had imprisoned humanity’s destiny. Making breakthroughs had become even more difficult!

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by everyone’s responses. He explained, “When I left, although it was for 2000 years, I was in Tragic Death Valley for 500 years. Those 500 years were similar to 5000 years, so in truth I have been gone for 6500 years.”

6500 years?

Hearing this explanation, some people were less puzzled. But, this was still difficult to accept. To go from an Empyrean to True Divinity in 6500 years was far too short a time.

The Laws that Lin Ming cultivated in particular were incredibly complex and profound. Although they were potent, they required a great deal of time. Every breakthrough needed a massive accumulation of energy!

Chapter 2200 – Day of the Meeting

Within the Good Fortune Saint Palace, in a golden hall, a tall and powerfully built middle-aged man was sitting upon an opulent throne.

This throne was forged from eternal stone. The seat was 10 feet wide and as the man sat here, he seemed to sit upon all beings in existence, making it nearly impossible to look up to him.

His eyes were filled with a disdainful indifference, as if nothing in the world could possibly cause his heart or mind to waver.

This man was the ruler of the saints – the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was holding a jade slip in his hands, no joy or anger evident on his face.

He had already looked through the contents of this jade slip; it held a message that Lin Ming wished to set up talks with him.

And in this golden hall were many saint race powerhouses. Of those that could stand here, even the ones with the lowest cultivation were at the middle Empyrean realm.

Everyone could see the jade slip in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s hand. They originally thought that this was a meaningless message, but they never imagined that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would suddenly take it out at this time.

They didn’t say anything. The matter with the humans sending out these jade slips was puzzling, but since the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had already seen it, it was naturally up for him to make the decision on whether he would want to attend.

“Three days from now, you will all follow me to the Hidden Dragon Galaxy.”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign simply said. The Empyreans present were stunned. The Hidden Dragon Galaxy was the meeting place designated in the jade slip.

They never thought that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would really decide to attend.

“Your Majesty Saint Sovereign, you really intend to go?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t respond. He simply waved his sleeves and left, leaving the many saint Empyreans looking at each other with looks of dismay.

It seemed that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign truly planned on attending. But what if the humans didn’t come at that time?

However, no one dared to defy the orders of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Thus, three days later, the many saint Empyreans set off from the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

“Hahaha, Soaring Feather, I knew you would return too.”

Astral Vault had already guessed that Soaring Feather would come. Casting out his sense, he soon found her. They hadn’t seen each other for 2000 years.

Beside Soaring Feather God King was Fairy Blue Lotus. As for Astral Vault God King, he had also brought his two disciples – Darkmoon and Highsun.

“I naturally cannot miss such a grand occasion.” Soaring Feather faintly smiled.

“Let’s go first.”

“Great!”

Soaring Feather and Astral Vault only had a so-so relationship with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and didn’t plan on joining his group.

Like this, the Good Fortune Saint Palace, Soaring Feather, Astral Vault, as well as many other saint race influences all started to head towards the Hidden Dragon Galaxy.

When it came to this, the Empyreans of many influences weren’t willing to go. After all, no one wanted to be made a fool by others. However since this was the order of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, no one dared to not go.

But as they approached the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, all of these Empyreans were slowly silenced.

This was because when they spread their sense to the surrounding areas of the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, they discovered that there were human spirit ships in the vicinity.

“It’s a human fleet. Did Lin Ming really come?”

“What are the humans thinking? They want one final battle?”

Many saint martial artists were dumbfounded.

The Hidden Dragon Galaxy covered an incredibly large area, but by relying on the positions of the human spirit ships, they found the approximate location of the talks.

And as everyone saw what was before them, they were utterly shocked.

In the distant starry skies, they could see a small planet floating about.

This small planet was only several hundred miles in diameter. It was originally impossible for life to form on such a small planet, but it actually contained countless spirit trees and treasures of the heavens and earth.

These spiritual plants all casually grew over the planet, and above it was a pavilion floating in the skies.

This pavilion was far simpler. It only encompassed an area of several dozen feet, and sitting in it was a young man.

This young man had extraordinary features and a temperament as ephemeral as dust. Just by sitting there he was like a spear that shook the hearts of those who saw him!

In front of this man was a long table. The young man sat at one end of the table, and on it was a pot of wine as well as several cups.

As the many saint race martial artists arrived, the man waved his hand in invitation. His gaze was directed at the Saint Palace in the skies, his eyes bright and shining as if he could pierce through the palace walls and array formations to see the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

“Lin Ming!”

“It’s really him!”

Many saint Empyreans had seen Lin Ming before, and even if they hadn’t, they had at least looked at his portrait. This man sitting there was undoubtedly Lin Ming.

They never imagined that not only would Lin Ming show up but he would also be sitting there so calmly, as if he were attending a gathering with friends!

“It’s not just Lin Ming that came, but many human Empyreans are also here. They are in full battle array not too far away!”

The human spirit ships were here. As long as they traced back the position of the spirit ships, it wasn’t difficult to find that there were over 20 human Empyreans standing nearby.

These human Empyreans were all high level figures of humanity!

If Lin Ming as well as so many other Empyreans died here then humanity’s fate could be imagined.

“What is happening? Aren’t they afraid that they will die here?”

“Maybe the spiritas are involved!”

Doubt flashed in the hearts of many saint martial artists. But at this time, someone discovered Lin Ming’s cultivation.

Although there was a great distance separating them, when facing Lin Ming, they felt as if they were facing the endless starry skies. A powerful suppressive feeling fell over them.

The closer they approached the stronger this feeling became. Many Empyreans felt their breath catch in their throats. Moreover, even when Lin Ming casually moved, his movements seemed to contain indescribable concepts within, making them impossible to discern.

“True Divinity!”

“He actually broke into True Divinity!”

“It’s only been 2000 years, how is this possible…”

Many saint martial artists were panic-stricken. They never thought that in such a short period of time, Lin Ming would manage to break into True Divinity.

“True Divinity…”

Fairy Blue Lotus took in a deep breath. Lin Ming’s speed of growth was far too fast, so fast that she couldn’t muster the courage to take him as a goal...

She couldn’t help but glance at her master. Soaring Feather God King had once fought with Lin Ming in the past, and was likely the most qualified one here to estimate him.

Soaring Feather God King’s eyes sparkled. She was also incomparably amazed. “Strange… if Lin Ming could break through so quickly, he surely must have had a fortuitous encounter. But, I cannot imagine just what sort of fortuitous encounter can arrive at this level.”

“His breakthrough is too fast. I wonder what his foundation and strength are like…” Astral Vault God King commented from beside Soaring Feather God King. He licked his lips, looking forwards more and more to today’s events.

True Divinity Lin Ming against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

The saint race spirit ships all paused before the small planet. Many saint martial artists were completely silent. As they looked at Lin Ming in the distance, dread and awe filled their eyes

Lin Ming hadn’t laid down his hand yet; he was still reaching out in an invitational gesture.

At this time, a hearty laugh echoed out from the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

“Extraordinary, truly extraordinary! You actually broke into True Divinity! No wonder you found the courage to face me!”

This voice was faintly indifferent but it rolled forwards like a thunderstorm, resounding through the universe!

A middle-aged man in golden robes stepped out from the Good Fortune Holy Palace. With just a few steps, he fell atop the small planet where Lin Ming was.

This man was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

At this time, he was only 100 feet away from Lin Ming. For True Divinity level masters this distance was no different from being face to face.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyes blazed as he looked at Lin Ming, an incomprehensibly happy expression on his face. “Did you think that you could fight me after you broke into True Divinity? For your cultivation to grow so quickly, you likely entered some sort of special time enchantment where the flow of time can be increased without twisting the Laws so that a martial artist can safely cultivate within?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s words left the saint martial artists stunned.

This sort of time enchantment was exceedingly rare; only a small number of people here had ever heard of something similar.

The cultivation that one gained from bitterly secluding themselves in such a time enchantment was different from the cultivation which one gained from adventuring outwards and living through all sorts of slaughters. Even though both could be considered growth through fortuitous encounters, the combat efficiency developed through both methods were on completely different levels.

This was just like a flower cultivated in a greenhouse compared to the weeds that withstood the harsh weather outside.

If Lin Ming had used 2000 years of time and entered into such a time enchantment to rapidly increase his cultivation, then breaking into True Divinity wouldn’t be strange.

Thinking of this, many saint Empyreans felt much more relaxed.

In these sorts of special ancient time enchantments, the flow of time wouldn’t be too ridiculously exaggerated. 2000 years would be around 10,000-20,000 years.

With this in consideration, Lin Ming’s breakthrough was within reason. After all, his potential and foundation were evident to all.

But to become a True Divinity in a time enchantment, in particular when jumping past several small Empyrean boundaries, it was inevitable that one’s Laws and strength would be influenced!

Chapter 2201 – Talks Collapse

Amongst the saint Empyreans, whether it was the older generation or younger generation, they all held a deep sense of hostility and envy towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was far too blinding an existence. To break through to True Divinity at around 10,000 years of age and also set up talks with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign – this was already on a completely different playing field than them.

Ever since ancient times, those of the same profession always competed against each other. This was true for martial artists and especially if martial artists stood on opposite sides. No one wanted to admit that they were inferior, and no one was willing to destroy their own prestige to glorify the ambitions of others.

“What is His Majesty Saint Sovereign still waiting for? He should just strike right now. This Lin Ming relied upon a time enchantment to break into True Divinity and is nothing at all compared to His Majesty the Saint Sovereign.”

“The Saint Sovereign should deal with Lin Ming while we encircle the other human masters. In this battle today we can severely wound humanity!”

Many saint Empyreans began to rapidly calculate various scenarios in their minds. As for talks or anything like that, they simply didn’t care. For most of those present, today was a day of slaughter!

And at this time, on the small planet, Lin Ming reached out a hand in invitation once more.

“Your Majesty Saint Sovereign, how about taking a seat?”

Lin Ming said with a smile, his tone calm and without waves. To be able to remain so composed beneath the pressure of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, this wasn’t something that ordinary True Divinity level masters could hope to accomplish.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign looked at Lin Ming and said, “I actually want to hear you speak, and listen to just what you can say.”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign waved his sleeves. In the next moment he was already sitting in the seat. The table in front of Lin Ming was only 20 feet long, and the two sat at opposite sides of the table. Lin Ming slowly poured a cup of wine.

This caused the many saint Empyreans present to feel bewildered. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign held a supremely revered status within the saint race, and no one had the qualifications to sit at the same table and drink with him; this was true even for Soaring Feather and Astral Vault.

But now, the human Lin Ming was treating the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign as an equal, drinking wine at the table!

Woosh!

No one could see when, but a jade slip flew out from Lin Ming and towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t even move. The arrow-like jade slip automatically stopped in front of him.

Divine sense swept out. This was only an instant, but the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign immediately read through the information within the jade slip!

Within the jade slip, Lin Ming had described the Soul Emperor’s plot.

The abyssals would sooner or later swallow up the 33 Heavens. The ancient war that occurred 10 billion years ago would descend upon the world once more.

The contents of the jade slip would horrify anyone. Even the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign found it hard to remain calm after reading through it.

He looked at Lin Ming with surprise and said, “What did you say? You said that the Soul Emperor’s body has been seized?”

“His body was seized at least several hundred million years ago… the current 33 Heavens’ Soul Emperor is no longer a spiritas.” Lin Ming slowly finished his cup of wine and poured more.

The information that Lin Ming gave out caused a cold chill to creep down the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s back. But, there was no way he could fully believe Lin Ming’s words.

These events were far too world-shocking. If Lin Ming were intentionally deceiving him, there was no way he could know what was true and what was false.

“You said that Immortal Sovereign is sealed in the Dark Abyss’s Demon God’s Tomb, and also that the Demon God’s Tomb has developed a spiritual wisdom that wishes to enslave the entirety of the 33 Heavens. All of this is only said by you alone, so on what basis can I believe you?”

“On the basis of your own judgment.” Lin Ming simply replied.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign couldn’t help but sneer. “You might as well have said nothing at all. With just a single jade slip you want me to end the war between humanity and the saints, and then transfer all forces to resist the spiritas? That is simply too ridiculous!

“Moreover, the story you created has too many holes. If you say that this Demon God’s Tomb Master is so horrifying and is capable of seizing the Soul Emperor’s body and also controlling totem level abyssals, then let me ask you why he has never bothered with me. Since he can seize the Soul Emperor’s body then he can naturally take over me too. I control Famine, and controlling me is the same as controlling Famine; wouldn’t that even be easier? Moreover, something like me coming to these talks today would never have occurred if he did!”

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s words. He had already considered this matter before.

Lin Ming said, “No one has infinite strength. According to the view of Your Majesty Saint Sovereign, then I can ask you the same question. How come the Demon’s God Tomb Master doesn’t simply control all lives in the 33 Heavens and Dark Abyss, seizing the bodies of all abyssals and becoming the absolute ruler of them all? If he did that then no one would be able to oppose him!

“This is clearly impossible. He doesn’t possess such horrifying strength nor is his soul force strong enough. In other words, when it comes to controlling others or seizing the bodies of others, there is always a limit.

“In truth, this is the same for everyone. When a puppet master controls a puppet there will always be a limit, especially when this concerns formidable puppets!

“Then, there must be a limit to the number of upper True Divinities and peak True Divinities that the Demon God’s Tomb Master can control. This number surely cannot be too many. For instance, let’s say he can at most divide his soul into three, one part seizing the Soul Emperor’s body, one for Deep, and one for Flood, and by doing so he controlled the three most formidable existences in the world. But as for you… it’s regrettable, but you do not meet the standards.”

Lin Ming spoke at an unhurried pace, but as the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign listened to him, these words grated on his ears.

Plainly speaking, Good Fortune’s strength was too poor and wasn’t even worth a glance.

Lin Ming’s explanation was fair and reasonable. Famine had been wounded long ago and it was likely because of this that the Demon God’s Tomb Master gave up on controlling it.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion darkened. But, he didn’t lash out at Lin Ming’s taunting. “So what if your story can be justified? My saint race has been preparing for this war for far too long, and you want my saint race to call for a truce just because of a story alone and then transfer all forces to resist the Soul Emperor? Wouldn’t that be the greatest joke in the world?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign said, still not believing Lin Ming’s words. But, Lin Ming was already prepared for this. He slowly traced his spatial ring and drew out the Black Dragon Spear!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign narrowed his eyes, his body overflowing with killing intent.

The pressure of a peerless powerhouse completely erupted at this moment. Even the planet beneath the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign began to shake, as if it couldn’t withstand this pressure.

As this massive pressure fell around Lin Ming, he lightly stroked the Black Dragon Spear, not even lifting his head as he said, “In truth, the reason Your Majesty Saint Sovereign launched an all-out war against humanity was to swallow up humanity and obtain a massive amount of resources and blood vitality, all in order to help you complete your ambitions to swallow all of existence? You believed that your final opponent was the Soul Emperor and that the Soul Emperor was your greatest threat to dominating the 33 Heavens.”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t deny or confirm Lin Ming’s words. He only sneered and said, “And what are you trying to say?”

“All of your plans are based upon the premise that the saint race is stronger than humanity. But, if the saints cannot defeat humanity, then I believe there is no reason for you to continue such a mutually damaging war.”

“Mm!?” Lin Ming’s words caused the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyebrows to jump up, a cold light flashing in his eyes!

Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s conversation wasn’t isolated from others. The saint Empyreans that were standing hundreds of miles away could clearly hear everything.

Lin Ming’s provocation caused them to draw out their weapons and revolve their true essence!

“The saints cannot defeat humanity?”

“Hahaha, how funny!”

Some saint Empyreans laughed in anger. They wanted to fight here and prove just how silly Lin Ming’s words were!

Towards the responses of the many saint Empyreans, Lin Ming didn’t care about them at all. He faintly turned his head until his eyes came to a stop on Astral Vault God King and Soaring Feather God King.

When these two arrived, Lin Ming had already sensed their presence.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “Two God Kings, do you remember the agreement that we had in the past? I agreed to withdraw from the war between the saints and humanity with you two, but we also agreed that I have a personal grudge with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, an enmity of life and death. I will not attack any saint race subjects, and will only strike out at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, right?”

Soaring Feather and Astral Vault vividly remembered their past agreement with Lin Ming. Astral Vault nodded, “Indeed.”

“Mm… very good! If you two God Kings do not interfere, then I will prove that…” As Lin Ming spoke to here, he turned towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and slowly stood up.

“I will prove that my strength far surpasses that of His Majesty the Saint Sovereign. Then, on the battlefield, no one amongst the saints will be able to contend with Emperor Shakya and Empyrean Divine Dream! If so, then the saints will not be able to defeat humanity!

“At that time, is there still a reason for the war to continue?

“And under these same circumstances, will Your Majesty Saint Sovereign still believe that I am lying to you?”

As Lin Ming spoke, his right hand had already grasped the Black Dragon Spear.

In that instant, the surrounding air froze over!

Chapter 2202 – Battle of True Divinities

Peng!

The moment Lin Ming picked up the Black Dragon Spear, the table and all the chairs around him exploded, turning into dust!

Killing intent recklessly surged outwards. Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, two peerless masters, stood in sharp contention to each other!

For powerhouses on their level, in the world of the 33 Heavens just their auras alone were able to shatter space.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s clothes flapped in the wind. A sneer hung on his face. At this moment from within his body, a sound rose up, as if a dragon was howling into the heavens. This howl deafened the ears and impacted through the vastness of space, causing the world to lose its color and storms to stir up. Behind the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, a 10,000 foot high phantom of a spiritual god appeared.

This phantom grasped a lance in hand, its appearance like a towering mountain. Its eyes were like two blazing suns that illuminated the world as it looked down upon everyone with cold disdain.

“Ah…”

A series of stuffy coughs spread throughout the audience. The human and saint race World Kings were simply unable to look straight at this spiritual god phantom. Just from a single glance, they felt their bodies shake as if they had been struck by a hammer and were nearly forced to their knees.

Even the many Empyreans present felt a tremendous pressure as they faced this spiritual god phantom, as if a mountain were being pressed down upon them. The force nearly made them fall to their knees in worship, unable to withstand the excruciating pressure.

“You… you have decided to fight me?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign looked at Lin Ming, his tone filled with arrogant contempt.

At this time, with the spiritual god phantom behind him, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign seemed like a true living god; no one could defy him!

“Saint Sovereign immortal, 10,000 lives immortal!”

On the side of the saints, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s followers began to cry out.

“Those who dare affront His Majesty’s dignity – death!”

Many saint Empyreans were stirred into a frenzy as the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign revealed his strength!

This was the might of their ruler. Moreover, none of them wished to engage in these meaningless negotiations to begin with. What they wanted to do was watch the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign roll over Lin Ming and suppress him, and then the saints could rush forwards in droves to rip apart the human forces so that not a single one of them was left alive!

On the human side, as Emperor Shakya, Dark Demon Monarch, and the others saw this scene occur, all of them had dignified expressions. Xiao Moxian clenched her fists, her heart filled with worry for Lin Ming.

They all knew that Lin Ming wouldn’t be unreasonable with his decisions, but even though they knew this they still felt anxious. After all, Lin Ming was facing the most powerful Sovereign of the saints!

For humanity, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s infamy and influence had been gathered over far too long a time, and had become impossibly heavy. In fact, in the hearts of many human martial artists, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had become a god-like existence in the 33 Heavens.

This was an existence that could swallow the destiny of humanity and reverse the Heavenly Dao – if this wasn’t the methods of a spiritual god, what was?

This was a decisive battle that concerned the fate of humanity, so how could they not be worried? And now, this was especially true with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign exposing his strength, making it so the leaders of humanity couldn’t even bear to look towards him.

Time came to a standstill. Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were only several dozen feet away from each other. Due to the fierce pressure they exuded, the planet beneath them began to quiver. Cracks appeared in the earth, as if the world below them would soon disintegrate!

Lin Ming looked up at the spiritual god phantom behind the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. “It looks like we have now entered a life or death battle. If I lose then you will surely take my life. If so, then if I win, it’s impossible for you not to pay a price. I will take away your Grandmist Spirit Bead, seize your avatar of Famine and then liberate the destiny of humanity that you stole!”

In the chaos all around him, Lin Ming’s voice was like a rolling thunderclap that spread out for 10,000 miles in the void.

All of the saint martial artists were stunned as they heard this. This Lin Ming was crazy!

In this situation he was still so arrogant! Those three things he listed were all the most important treasures to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

The Grandmist Spirit Bead and avatar of Famine didn’t need an explanation – they were the reason why the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was able to cultivate to his present level. As for humanity’s destiny, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had gone into seclusion for 2000 years in order to swallow those Laws and integrate them into the avatar of Famine and further his own cultivation. If Lin Ming were to take that away, it would be the same as wasting 2000 years of time.

Without a doubt, these three things that Lin Ming mentioned each touched upon the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s reverse scale!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign cackled in anger. His long hair danced in the air and his eyes overflowed with killing intent.

“Good! Good! Good!” The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign said. “You desire my Grandmist Spirit Bead but I also desire the secrets on your body! You rose like a star, and in a mere 10,000 years managed to step into True Divinity! How could you not have secrets on your body? Today, I will tear you apart piece by piece and find out just what you are hiding!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s hair flew up. His body was tall and prominent and his eyes shined. He was like a naturally superior being, an innate sense of suppression gushing out from him.

“Any more words are meaningless. Let us compare our strengths. This will be my first battle since I stepped into True Divinity. I have been waiting for this for a long time!”

Lin Ming’s figure flashed and flew up from the pavilion. He stood above a vast expanse of mountains and rivers on the small planet.

As he looked at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, his gaze sharpened.

Weng!

Lin Ming flourished his spear. Time seemed to freeze. Everyone only saw a 10,000 foot beam of divine light cover their eyes, blinding them to what happened. Then, in the next moment, an earth-shattering roar deafened the ears!

Wild energy howled in all directions. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign also punched out his fist at this moment!

His fist was wrapped in divine light. Golden energy gathered around the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body, turning into astral essence war armor.

This fist could shatter the starry skies.

Fist light and spear light collided.

The pavilion on the small planet, the earth, the plants, everything began to disintegrate. Mountains and rivers began to break apart and collapse downwards!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s fist light contained a potential that rushed forwards like a monstrous tsunami. But in the center of the fist light, the Black Dragon Spear continued forwards with unstoppable momentum!

Like a waterfall that fell for thousands of miles, the fist light was split open from the middle. Thousands upon thousands of light beams flew past Lin Ming, radiating all around him.

Ca!

These light beams pierced through the void, tearing into the ground and splitting open the earth. Everything that the light beams touched was brutally annihilated. And, what bore the brunt of the attack was the small planet beneath their feet. As this planet was struck, it began to completely implode upon itself from the light beams that tore into it.

This was the terrifying strength of one of the strongest powerhouses in existence. A True Divinity powerhouse was originally a god of a great world. When Lin Ming had the strength of a True Divinity, most of his fights had been within the Demon God’s Tomb. The Demon God’s Tomb was like a spirit treasure that had been refined for 100 billion years and was indestructible in itself. In addition to the suppression of Laws within and the grand array formation that stabilized the entire world, it was impossible to display such heaven-destroying strength within.

But now, in the world of the 33 Heavens, in the battle between Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, their actions could cause planets to collapse!

“Be careful!”

The human forces and saint forces had already drawn back, but now they were forced back even more. If an Empyrean were to be sucked into a battle of this level, they would instantly be turned into ashes!

Both sides drew back 100,000 miles. Then, the Empyreans on each side joined forces to weave together barriers of astral essence and true essence to resist the shockwaves!

“How is this…”

“Lin Ming blocked His Majesty Saint Sovereign’s strike, and he even… broke through the Saint Sovereign’s fist light!?”

Many saint race powerhouses witnessed Lin Ming’s unstoppable spear light with their own eyes. They watched as that horrific energy broke through the fist light and reached the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

The Black Dragon Spear shimmered with cold light as it thrust forwards!

This spear contained the Laws of Life and Death. The spear point was like the scythe of the death god, reaping all life!

Facing this life-reaping strike, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign emitted a deep roar. His entire body released explosive crackling sounds as he displayed the saint race’s body transformation technique to its limits!

Bang!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign punched out his fist once more. This fist violently collided with the Black Dragon Spear, causing it to wildly curve!

But the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was also forced back from the impact of this spear strike.

Ka ka ka!

Faint cracks began to appear in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s protective astral essence. His complexion suddenly changed. In that moment, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had felt a pervasive energy rush through these cracks and wantonly attack his body!

Although this energy was weak it was extremely tenacious and desired to swallow up his blood vitality!

“Humph!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign coldly coughed. Astral essence erupted from within him as he destroyed this strength.

But by now, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyes as he looked at Lin Ming had already changed.

Although that had only been a probing strike just now, wasn’t Lin Ming’s strike also similar?

In just a single strike, Lin Ming had managed to break through his protective astral essence. How could the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign not be startled?

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was startled, but the many saint powerhouses were left completely bewildered.

Lin Ming’s short exchange with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had destroyed a massive area of the void and even caused a small planet to collapse. This actually wasn’t anything at all. But, what shocked them was that Lin Ming’s strike had forced the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign backwards!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had been forced backwards!

Forced backwards…

Backwards…

It was like a demonic spirit was chanting curses into the ears of the many saint race martial artists. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, an invincible god-like existence in the hearts of the saint race martial artists, an existence that none of them could look up to, had been forced 10 miles away by Lin Ming’s spear!

How could this possibly happen?

Many saint Empyreans glanced at each other with ashen faces of dismay. For a time, no one could believe what had happened. Both sides had exchanged probing strikes, but Lin Ming was the one who had gained the upper hand. This meant that at the very least, Lin Ming possessed strength that was equal to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

Chapter 2206 – Defeating Good Fortune

“This is… what is happening?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign began to panic. He wanted to recall the Grandmist Spirit Bead, but at this time he felt a strange strength cover it.

As Lin Ming hurtled towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign he used the world strength of the Emperor Bone Sea to block off the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Although he couldn’t seal it away forever, as long as he could delay it for even a tenth of a blink of an eye, that was more than enough time.

Lin Ming attacked.

His true self appeared. Grasping the Black Dragon Spear, he shot towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. As for Lin Ming’s demon avatar, he also thrust out the demon spine in his hands!

The two forces gathered together. A giant Asura wheel appeared in the air, creaking and humming as it spun.

At this moment, the Asura wheel seemed to become the heavens.

At the same time a seven revolution red lotus shot out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows. The red lotus bloomed and overflowed with the Life and Death Laws!

In this moment, the seven revolution red lotus was like the earth.

The Asura wheel and seven revolution red lotus unexpectedly fused together as one.

The Asura Heavenly Dao and Holy Scripture Laws had undergone a preliminary fusion; this was the result of the highest comprehension of Laws that Lin Ming had achieved in his 1500 years in the Demon God’s Tomb.

These two strengths were infused with all of Lin Ming’s power of divinity and demons as it all came hurtling towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was shocked. At this time the Grandmist Spirit Bead was temporarily blocked off by Lin Ming. Without the Spirit Bead, he could only resist his enemy with his two fists!

In this critical life or death moment, he bit down on the tip of his tongue and spat out a mouthful of blood essence. With a loud roar, this blood essence began to burn with blinding brilliance, erupting like a great rising sun. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign revolved his energy to its limits and punched out with both fists!

Bang!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s left and right hands roared out like two flying divine dragons, smashing into Lin Ming’s two great Laws.

This was a frontal collision between peak True Divinity powerhouses!

It was like two suns crashing into each other. Wild astral essence and the power of divinity and demons erupted. Golden light shot out into the void, illuminating the entirety of space!

100,000 miles away, the energy barriers laid down by the saints and humans began to wildly shake. Cracks began to form from the impact of energy. Everyone covered their eyes, feeling blinded from the light!

Whether it was the saints or humans, every martial artist was left speechless. Not to mention the younger generation, but even upper Empyreans, peak Empyreans, Emperor Shakya, Soaring Feather, and everyone else, was utterly dumbfounded by this battle between peak True Divinity level powerhouses.

This didn’t seem like strength that a person should possess, but the might of the universe itself. Perhaps only a giant star exploding in a supernova could emit such power.

Waves of light swept out; it was hard for anyone’s sense to pass through it.

“Lin Ming won?”

The human martial artists glanced at each other. In that final moment, it should have been Lin Ming who had the upper hand.

At the end, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had actually burnt his blood essence. Not only did he use the Grandmist Spirit Bead but he was also forced to burn his blood essence afterwards. It was clear from this just how terrifying Lin Ming’s strength was, to the degree where a person who nearly reached the peak of True Divinity had to go all-out in order to deal with him.

The light continued shining out for dozens of breaths of time before gradually fading away. Then, people could finally find out just what happened on the battlefield 100,000 miles away.

As they saw the scene appear, the faces of many saint martial artists turned pale white.

On the battlefield, space for 10,000 miles had completely collapsed, forming a giant black hole. All of the nearby martial artists had been disintegrated into dust and as for their king, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, his entire body was left covered in blood.

His wounds were extremely heavy and golden scales were broken all over his body. His bones were shattered in numerous places and he was covered in rags, looking like a corpse that floated in the void.

Not too far away from him, Lin Ming had already returned to his human form. His severely wounded demon avatar had stepped back into his inner world.

As a result, besides a pale expression, Lin Ming appeared completely unscathed on the outside.

They had already expected that Lin Ming would win in that final exchange. After all, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had to hastily defend, and even though he had burned his blood essence he might not have been able to fend off Lin Ming’s attack where he had gathered all his potential.

But they didn’t think the disparity would be so great.

This was simply a complete victory!

At this time, Lin Ming had taken hold of the Grandmist Spirit Bead and was slowly erasing the spirit mark within it.

When the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was in his weakest moment was the best opportunity to erase his spirit mark.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was something Lin Ming had wanted to obtain for a long time.

In fact, for Lin Ming, of the three great divine tools, the Grandmist Spirit Bead and Origin Amethyst Crystal were the most practical. Those two divine tools could directly increase his strength, since he mainly dual cultivated in the body and energy, and cultivated the soul as an auxiliary third.

“You…”

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was heavily wounded by Lin Ming, the moment that Lin Ming started to erase his spirit mark in the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he quickly felt it and regained consciousness.

He looked up, his eyes filled with murder as he glared at Lin Ming.

This was the greatest defeat in his life! And also the greatest shame!

In front of innumerable masters from the 33 Heavens, he had been utterly defeated by Lin Ming, a mere 10,000 year old junior! He had even used every possible method at his disposal.

Not only that but he had been beaten down like a dead dog and even the Grandmist Spirit Bead had been taken away!

All the effort he had put in for so many years had failed.

Lin Ming’s soul force was far greater than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s and his strength was also superior. And, with the Grandmist Spirit Bead not possessing an artifact spirit, Lin Ming started to slowly refine it.

To the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, this was no different than cutting off a chunk of his flesh. He wished he could tear Lin Ming to shreds!

Lin Ming could clearly feel the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s hatred and pure animosity towards him. But this was also reasonable. After all, to be beaten up into such an appearance and also have his treasure taken away, how could he not hate?

“I know that it doesn’t feel good to have your spirit mark erased by me… but this is a result you cannot change. If you don’t want your soul to be injured then I advise you to remove the spirit mark on your own initiative.”

Lin Ming’s words grated on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s ears.

He was a supreme ruler of the world, and yet he was being humiliated like this. Not only had he been defeated, but he even had to remove his own spirit mark to give his enemy his treasure.

How could there be such truths in the world!

However, even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign stubbornly resisted and refused to comply, he would merely be extending his own pain and damage to his soul. Lin Ming would simply expend a little more time and energy, and in the end the Grandmist Spirit Bead would belong to him anyways.

This was the suppression of absolute strength.

This was suppression, this was shame, but this was a situation where he could not fight back!

If he complied then his dignity would fall through the floor. But if he resisted, he would only be giving himself an even greater pain.

In the world of martial artists, strength was everything!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign grit his teeth, adamantly refusing to respond to Lin Ming. His eyes were blood red, as if he wanted to swallow Lin Ming alive.

Lin Ming looked at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s glare. His movements slowed down and a thoughtful look appeared on his features.

“Lin Ming, do you really plan on taking away the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s Grandmist Spirit Bead and avatar of Famine, and then after releasing the destiny of humanity, you will simply let loose this tiger to create trouble in the future?”

At this time, Sheng Mei’s voice echoed in Lin Ming’s ears.

“That was the original plan, but now I think my thoughts were too naïve…”

Lin Ming was also considering this.

Without a doubt, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign hated him to his marrow. Even if he released the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and allowed him to live, would he feel any sense of gratitude?

Perhaps the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would hide away to gather his strength, waiting for a day to stab him in the back!

The abyssal demons were natural enemies to the 33 Heavens. But, while the Soul Emperor wanted to swallow up the 33 Heavens, what if he didn’t exterminate all the races at once, but instead left some that he would allow to surrender instead?

When the Soul Emperor revealed his irresistible strength, there might be some races willing to degenerate into servants for the abyssals.

At that time, no one could tell whether or not the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would turn traitor.

His contradictions with the Soul Emperor were in truth not completely irreconcilable.

If he were to submit himself to the Soul Emperor, then the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign knew he would face a potential fate where he might be tossed away in the future, no different from a dog that had outlived its usefulness.

But, wasn’t this slightly better than joining forces to resist the Soul Emperor?

It might be!

In the eyes of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, even if he joined forces with Lin Ming to resist the Soul Emperor, the likelihood of defeat was still extremely high.

And even if he won, his strength was still inferior to Lin Ming’s; he would still worry about being eliminated.

Then, in this difficult dilemma with two hard choices to choose from, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign might switch sides and ally with the Soul Emperor to deal with Lin Ming. At the very least, since the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign hated Lin Ming so much, he might take this chance to kill him and soothe his thoughts and ego.

Moreover, what if the Soul Emperor truly took in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and allowed him to become one of his minions?

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign might have a master perching on top of his head, for better or worse, with his level of strength he could still take charge of several universes and continue his days of ruling over the life and death of others.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming hesitated. He originally hoped to join forces with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to fight back against the Dark Abyss; this seemed like the most reasonable outcome.

But once both sides had uneven levels of strength, and he was also stronger than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, then a subtle change would occur.

Lin Ming didn’t want to place his future destiny in the hands of others. To him, Ouyang Boyan had been enough of a lesson. In the future if he were to go into seclusion or go out seeking more lucky chances, or if the war were to carry on, what if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign decided to take action against his family and friends?

The consequences would be unimaginable.

Realizing this, Lin Ming gently rubbed his chin. He looked at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and suddenly grinned. “My apologies, but after further consideration, I have changed my mind.”

Chapter 2207 – Hold the Overlord

“Mm?”

For a time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign couldn’t understand what Lin Ming meant.

But at this time, Lin Ming attacked; his fist smashed into the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s chest.

Peng!

With a loud explosion, the already wounded and powerless-to-resist Good Fortune Saint Sovereign simply wasn’t able to withstand Lin Ming’s attack; his chest was smashed in and he vomited out a mouthful of blood.

“You!!!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was enraged.

But this punch was only the beginning. Lin Ming’s fists fell down onto the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign like a raging storm. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was covered in blood. His meridians tore apart and his golden scales began flying off!

His bones and organs were all shattered by Lin Ming; he could be said to be completely broken.

However, with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s powerful vitality, he didn’t die.

In the surrounding void, many saint race Empyreans and World Kings watched helplessly on as this occurred. All of them were left slack-jawed with shock and indignation, but none of them dared to speak out.

In the face of so many saints, their Saint Sovereign was being horribly beaten up and yet none of them could utter a single word or lift a single finger.

This was the suppression brought about by absolute strength.

There was not a single person that dared rise up against Lin Ming, because in front of him, any single one of them could be instantly killed!

“Your Majesty Saint Sovereign…”

The many martial artists of the Good Fortune Saint Palace felt their hearts quiver. Not too long ago, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had been a living god in their hearts, an unreachable existence that controlled the life and death of all beings beneath him.

Not to mention the ordinary disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace, but even the Empyrean level powerhouses rarely had a chance to see him.

And yet such a Saint Sovereign was being savagely ruined by Lin Ming.

“This should be enough.”

Lin Ming looked down at the mangled Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. After a brief probe, he determined that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had lost all strength to resist, and even a Great World King could freely handle him.

Then, Lin Ming’s hands began to move. Seals flew out from his hands and into the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body.

These seals were fused with the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra Laws; they were a fusion of both Laws.

Their effect was to completely imprison the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s cultivation.

After all, no matter how it was said, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was a powerhouse nearly at the peak of True Divinity. Out of all the races in the entire 33 Heavens, it was hard to find someone that could be a match for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

But now, with the great enemy looming on the horizon, killing the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would be incredibly inappropriate!

This was equal to ripping out the spine of the saints. Without the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, the cohesion and total combat strength of the saints would plummet precipitously.

But letting the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign go was impossible because it was likely that he would turn traitor. If so, it was best to just kill him here and end any troubles before they began.

Thus, Lin Ming decided to make a compromise. He would imprison the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and hold the overlord to control his vassals.

Of course, if he were able to control the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s thoughts and implant a slave seal in him then that would be for the best. But, with Lin Ming’s current level of strength, wanting to forcefully control the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was impossible. As for planting a slave seal in his body, that was even more unrealistic. To allow someone else to control their mind and heart, to completely hand over their life, that was something that not even low level martial artists would submit to, much less the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign who controlled his own race.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign seemed to understand Lin Ming’s thoughts. He looked at Lin Ming with hatred thick in his eyes, like the most sinister and deadly snake, wishing that he could tear Lin Ming to shreds.

“Humph!”

Lin Ming coldly snorted. He smashed a fist into the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s face.

Towards this man that had tried to take his life several times before, that had placed him in numerous precarious life or death situations, and had even killed or caused the deaths of numerous heroes of humanity and the ancient races, including Three Lives Old Man, Empyrean Primordius, Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, the primal god race’s old Patriarch, and countless others that Lin Ming owed gratitude towards, Lin Ming simply didn’t have a single shred of pity for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign still wanted to show off his strength after falling into his hands, then Lin Ming would simply use a greater strength to roll over him!

“You think that you are still that all-powerful Saint Sovereign? You are nothing but a captive!”

Lin Ming looked at Good Fortune with cold indifference. “In your heart, all lives are to be suppressed by you, humiliated by you, or even swallowed by you. All lives should be honored by this, and even obediently offer themselves up to you. As for those that aren’t willing to be suppressed, humiliated, or swallowed by you, they should be cut to pieces, completely exterminated! This is your mindset, your logic!

“Your logic may be overbearing, but it isn’t wrong. Because if you have the strength, you can control the life and death of all beings! But now, my strength is even greater than yours so you should be honored by me ruining you.”

As Lin Ming spoke he smashed his fist into the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s face. His punch cracked open the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eye sockets and caused him to bleed from his eyes!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign couldn’t even open his eyes anymore. His strength had been completely exhausted and even his wounds regenerated at an agonizingly slow pace.

Lin Ming’s fingers continued to flicker. Light striking sounds echoed in the air.

Lin Ming planted 12 Asura seals in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body, sealing up his 12 main meridians routes. Then, he formed 11 Holy Scripture seals, sealing up the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s organs.

Following that, the 36 death points, the 360 acupoints, the 36,000 pores, all of them were sealed up by Lin Ming!

These seals contained the highest Laws of Lin Ming’s life studies. Unless Lin Ming personally unsealed them, it would be impossible for anyone else.

Of course, if there was someone stronger than Lin Ming they could still rely on brute force to erase these seals. But even so, they would create calamitous damage to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body.

Lin Ming carefully probed the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. After feeling that everything was about right, he summoned Primordius Heavenly Palace and tossed the half-dead Good Fortune Saint Sovereign inside like a sack.

The truth was that there was also a space within the Grandmist Spirit Bead. But, since Lin Ming had yet to fully refine the Grandmist Spirit Bead he didn’t want to recklessly use it.

Then, Lin Ming turned towards the many saint race martial artists.

A void of 100,000 miles separated them. Lin Ming took a single casual step forwards, instantly utilizing a great void transfer to arrive in front of them.

At this time, a cold chill crept into the hearts of all the saint martial artists.

The pressure that Lin Ming exuded was too great!

They had all personally witnessed the sad and tragic scene of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign being completely suppressed by Lin Ming!

As long as Lin Ming wanted to, he could slaughter them like chickens and dogs.

Moreover, none of them had the courage to escape from Lin Ming’s hands. Perhaps Lin Ming only needed to summon a force field to cage all of them inside this space.

“All of you…” Lin Ming opened his mouth to speak. The saint martial artists all felt their hearts skip a beat. They regretted following the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign here to set up these ‘talks’.

Just what kind of ‘talks’ was this? This was simply a grand slaughter festival!

“Most of you have hands stained with the blood of my people!”

Lin Ming’s first few words caused the many saint martial artists to feel a cold chill creep up their backs. It was over! They were all done for! It was time for all debts to be settled!

Lin Ming simply didn’t care about the ugly expressions of these saint martial artists. “Because of you, humanity has suffered countless casualties. They have been forced to leave their homelands to roam through the wilderness!

“How many families have been broken up? How many children have starved to death? How many people, because of this war, don’t even have their bones left behind? There have been many humans born in the chaos of war, born in the wilderness, that have never been able to see their homeland even before their deaths!

“If I were to kill any one of you, it would be perfectly justified!”

As Lin Ming spoke to here, the saint martial artists all held their breath. Many of them felt a cold sweat dripping down their backs and their minds tremble.

“However… I will not kill you all. First, it is because I once swore an oath that I would withdraw from the war between humanity and the saints, only dealing with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign alone! Secondly, and most important, the reason I do not kill you is because I do not want humanity nor any other race of the 33 Heavens to experience the chaos and turbulence of war. I do not want lives to be wasted away like coal in the flames…

“Life, is innocent. Even amongst the saints, there are naïve little children, there are kind-hearted subjects. This war was never their intention.”

As Lin Ming spoke to here, he suddenly looked towards Soaring Feather God King.

“Soaring Feather!”

Soaring Feather’s thoughts stirred. On this day, Lin Ming had become the ruler of the 33 Heavens. With his status he could give orders to any person here!

Looking at her master being called out by her name by Lin Ming, Fairy Blue Lotus felt her heart tighten. She looked at Lin Ming with complex light in her eyes.

After 2000 years, Lin Ming now stood at a completely incomprehensible height.

Now, she and Lin Ming could be said to exist in two different worlds. She was only worried for her master. She wondered why Lin Ming had called out to Soaring Feather at this time.

“You follow me!”

Lin Ming’s tone brooked no refusal. With a wave of his hand, a force field isolated out the world.

Soaring Feather hesitated for a moment and then stepped into Lin Ming’s force field.

She had already faintly guessed just what Lin Ming was going to say to her.

Chapter 2211 – The Soul Emperor Emerges

As Sheng Mei’s steps came to a halt, that voice disappeared, as if it had never appeared at all.

However, Sheng Mei knew that this couldn’t have been an illusion.

She closed her eyes, quietly sensing the origin of that voice. After a long moment of silence, that summoning call appeared once more. It was still weak, but this time, Sheng Mei was able to keenly sense which direction it came from.

With some anticipation, with some unease, with some fear, Sheng Mei silently walked forwards.

She passed through a graveyard and finally arrived atop a vast field of ice.

The cold energy was rich atop this field of ice, and snow billowed in the wind.

This cold energy came from the strength of Laws, and Sheng Mei felt that these Laws were somewhat familiar. This was because she also cultivated the Ice Laws, and her Laws seemed to be interlinked in many places to the Laws in the Asura forbidden land, as if they came from the same origins.

Sheng Mei remained pensive. Then, atop this field of ice, she saw a giant rift, a valley of ice. And below this rift great waves rolled and tumbled; this was an icy river.

Although the river waters hadn’t frozen, the freezing chill in the air was countless times colder than the frost of the mortal world.

However, Sheng Mei was someone who cultivated the Ice Laws to the extreme. In such an environment, not only did she not think it was too cold, but she actually felt somewhat comfortable.

She walked down this ice rift for a long time. Then, at the end of this rift she could see the smooth, ice-like surface of a giant mirror.

This ice mirror towered into the clouds. The light blue surface faced Sheng Mei, reflecting the entire world upon it.

It seemed that within this cold ice, there was another world.

Sheng Mei understood that this great piece of ice was the Cold Ice Mirror mentioned by Lin Ming!

And it seemed that a wisp of remnant soul from her past life was within the Cold Ice Mirror.

Sheng Mei used a long period of time to slowly walk in front of the Cold Ice Mirror. As she looked into it, she saw winds and ice obscuring everything.

“Is it here…”

Sheng Mei softly thought out loud as she stood before the Cold Ice Mirror for a long time.

Her only reply was silence.

Sheng Mei patiently waited for several dozen breaths of time. Then, on the surface of the Cold Ice Mirror, light ripples suddenly appeared.

A gentle and deep voice, one that had slumbered for unknown billions of years, suddenly woke up and echoed in Sheng Mei’s ears –

“My child, you’ve come…”

Sheng Mei’s heart trembled!

This voice had been that faint call which summoned her. Feeling it near, there was an inexplicable kindness and familiarity, as if it came from somewhere in the deepest parts of her soul. This sort of feeling was completely unlike her past life.

“You are…” Sheng Mei’s voice quivered.

“I am your last life’s mother…”

Mother?

Sheng Mei shook, like she had been zapped by lightning. Whether it was a father or mother, these were extremely distant matters to Sheng Mei. Even when she was in the Demon God’s Tomb where she experienced the memories of her past life, she rarely had memories of her parents. In her childhood, what she knew of were struggles, tribulations, slaughter!

There was likely only a single reason for this. That was because when she was a child, she rarely came into contact with her father and mother.

But today, the mother of Sheng Mei’s past life had appeared. This was a bloodline connection, a communion that caused her soul to beat. Unknowingly, tears fell down her eyes.

Her mother was actually in the Asura forbidden land…

Sheng Mei could feel that her mother had already died; all that was left was a wisp of her remnant soul.

Sheng Mei knelt down and silently bowed.

Originally, Sheng Mei had taken the peak of martial arts as the goal she would chase after all her life. She never sought out her own parents but she didn’t think she had a father or mother.

In fact, to the Sheng Mei of that time, kinship, family, those ideals were nothing but floating clouds in her eyes. Moreover, she never had family so she never knew what that felt like; she didn’t even have friends. Those she recognized were only those of the same sect or race, as well as the Soul Emperor who passed down orders to her.

But during the long flow of time, Sheng Mei’s character underwent subtle changes. This was particularly true for when she gave birth to Jiu’er. It was at that time she first realized what it was like to have another person in her life whose life she valued more than her own…

It was also at that time she understood the significance of family. But, when she finally became aware of this meaning, she discovered that her father and mother had already perished and all that was left over of them were their remnant souls.

“Child, rise…”

That gentle voice reverberated in Sheng Mei’s ears once more. Sheng Mei bowed again before standing up and stepping into the world of the Cold Ice Mirror.

In this world, she could slowly sense the existence of her mother. This was a light feeling of blended bloodlines that flowed through all directions of the Cold Ice Mirror’s world.

She suddenly understood what this was. “Mother… your remnant soul is the artifact spirit of the Cold Ice Mirror?”

“Yes… this is a spirit treasure refined by Asura. I have already become used to being in here…”

This gentle voice was continuously weak and faint. Sheng Mei realized that her mother’s remnant soul would not be like those in the Emperor Bone Sea, remaining in a state of everlasting perpetuity. There would be a day when her mother’s remnant soul would become so weak that it would eventually dissipate into the void.

This left Sheng Mei’s heart aching.

She could guess what had happened. 10 billion years ago, the Asura Road Master couldn’t bear to see her mother vanish into nothingness. Thus, he had protected her mother’s remnant soul within the Cold Ice Mirror…

But this also meant that her mother had withstood 10 billion years of loneliness here. Of course, there might have been some people who accompanied her.

Sheng Mei had a feeling in her heart. She turned and saw that a thousand feet away, on a glacier, a blue-clothed woman wearing a veil was silently standing.

Cold winds swayed about her and her black hair danced in the wind. The feeling she gave off was like that of an ice lotus blooming atop a snowy mountain, untainted by mortal hands.

Although this woman wore a veil, Sheng Mei could instantly confirm something – this… was her past self.

It was like staring at the mirror, both reflecting each other.

Sheng Mei wasn’t sure what to say. Her mind was left in chaos.

In truth, Sheng Mei was a complete ‘self’ born from her tenth life. But, because of some unknown reasons, she had been severed from her first nine lives. There were many riddles in her mind as well as many doubts.

If possible, Sheng Mei didn’t want to bother with these things. What she wanted the most was to break away from the turmoil of the world with Lin Ming, bringing Jiu’er with them. Although they couldn’t experience a life of eternal happiness, it would still be a long, happy, and simple life.

However, as for her past life, Sheng Mei in truth didn’t want to fuse back together with her previous personality. She just wanted to remain the pure her that she was.

However…

There were many things in life that couldn’t be just because she hoped for them.

Destiny was like a great wheel. Whether or not one was prepared for it, whether or not one could withstand it, it would still come rolling towards you.

Just like the present…

As Sheng Mei was lost in thought, she suddenly felt a stabbing pain in her chest. Her face instantly paled.

A cold sweat began to fall down from her forehead. An inexplicable racing of her heart left her feeling anxious.

It was at this time that Sheng Mei’s mother discovered something strange occurring to Sheng Mei. She asked with worry, “My child, what is wrong? Have you been injured?”

Sheng Mei gasped for breath, a hand pressed against her chest. “I… I don’t know… suddenly feel anxious, as if I can’t catch my breath…”

This feeling came suddenly and inexplicably. It left dark clouds hovering over Sheng Mei’s heart.

………….

At this time, across unknown layers of time and space, in the vast chaos, there was a sea that extended outwards for countless miles.

For there to be a sea in the starry skies was simply inconceivable. And this sea was filthy and yellow, with innumerable bones floating within.

Faintly, one could hear the bitter cries of souls in the sea breeze, agonized wails that left one feeling dread and apprehension.

At some unknown time, atop the originally calm sea surface, a storm suddenly rose up. The storm grew larger and larger and the seawater was like two waterfalls rising into the air. Countless skeletons were smashed apart by the turbulent sea waves.

And in this raging sea, a youth appeared, stepping through the void as he emerged from the seawaters. He had long hair as white as snow and a face that was paper white.

He slowly rose upwards until he flew 100,000 feet into the air. Then, he looked at the sea in the starry skies and casually waved his hand.

The vast and limitless sea began to rapidly shrink. From millions of miles, to hundreds of thousands of miles, to thousands of miles, to hundreds of miles, to several feet, to several inches, and finally it shrank into a single drop of water.

This drop of water flew into the pupil of the white-haired youth’s eye, moistening it like a single tear.

However, after this youth’s eye was moistened with this drop of water it still remained as old and dirty as before, emitting the death energy that only a corpse would have.

The great sea that contained endless bones had turned into a single water drop and then fused into a youth’s eye. Anyone who saw this would feel their scalp tingle with dread.

The youth fell deep into thought. He looked into the distant starry skies, a happy expression on his face. But, this happy smile caused one to feel an inexplicable sense of fear.

“I never thought that there would be some people so impatiently wishing to see me…”

The youth spoke out loud. He stepped up into the void, as if there were invisible stairs that only he could see. Like this, his figure submerged into the void, sinking in silently and leaving behind only light spatial ripples.

Chapter 2214 – The Power of the Soul Emperor

Hu –

Hu –

Hu –

Souls cried and demons wept. The sea of the Soul Emperor’s tear was flooded with countless suffering souls and bones.

Lin Ming felt the energy within his body turn stagnant and his strength be suppressed by a great deal. There was even a feeling of tight breathlessness in his chest; it was clear that this sea was the Soul Emperor’s force field domain.

“This is the sea of suffering. Those who enter have no way to leave, and today, you will die here.”

As the Soul Emperor spoke he lifted a finger and pointed it outwards. His skin was as pale as paper and one could even see the blood vessels beneath. However, a normal man’s blood vessels were blue, but the Soul Emperor’s were gray, as if the blood that flowed within them was also filled with death.

This finger amplified to infinite proportions in Lin Ming’s eyes. He was simply unable to resist, unable to dodge. The spiral fingerprint was clearly visible, each circle like a vortex. Because the Soul Emperor’s finger seemed as large as the heavens, each circular fingerprint was like a ring-shaped mountain range!

Lin Ming’s eyes shot open and he grasped the Black Dragon Spear in his hands. He felt that in his entire life he had never encountered such a terrifying attack before!

The finger possessed enough pressure to break down the skies. Lin Ming exploded in a thunderous roar as strength erupted within him to the limits. Around him, eight Dao Palaces opened and the two highest Laws also fused into his inner world. The Asura blood began to burn!

Lin Ming aimed at the center of that giant finger and thrust out his spear. Spear light as thick as a mountain hurtled forth, like a pillar that lifted the heavens!

However, facing that giant finger, even the mighty spear light was nothing but a tiny needle that crashed into it.

Kacha!

Spear light shattered. However, even though the giant finger was also pierced through, it continued to crush down as before!

Bang!

With Lin Ming as the center, the entire cosmos seemed to fall down. A massive fingerprint formed in the endless void. Lin Ming coughed out as his joints emitted loud cracking sounds. His bones broke all over, his organs shattered, and he spat out a mouthful of blood.

He was sent flying backwards. Like a bag of blood that had been ripped open, blood rained down.

So strong!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. This was the first time he experienced the strength of the Demon God’s Tomb Master, and this was only his avatar!

If the avatar was so horrifying, just what would the complete form of the Demon God’s Tomb Master be like?

Lin Ming held his breath, revolving the power of divinity and demons in his body. His broken bones and shattered organs began to rapidly repair. A look of faint surprise flashed in the Soul Emperor’s eyes.

“You seem to have opened the eighth Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, attained a higher level and rebirthed your body. In addition, you have absorbed a totem level abyssal into your body. With the two forms fused together, this gave you the body of a heavenly demon. Now, your body’s tolerance capacity and recovery abilities far surpass those of any martial artist on the same level… but, how many of my attacks do you think you can withstand?”

The Soul Emperor said with a smile. His smile caused one to feel a chill creep down their back.

Lin Ming was aware that what the Soul Emperor said was true. If he hadn’t opened the eighth Dao Palace, allowing the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and Nine Stars of the Dao Palace to connect and commune at a higher level and giving his body a qualitative leap upwards, then perhaps the Soul Emperor’s attack just now would have sundered him in half. Even if he didn’t die, he would have lost most of his life and basically been left helpless.

But even like this, with his current condition, he wouldn’t be able to withstand many of the Soul Emperor’s attacks before exhausting all of his strength!

This was because no matter how powerful his regenerative abilities were, if he wanted to recover from severe wounds he would have to consume a massive amount of energy. And, the more powerful the body, the more energy that would be used!

He couldn’t allow the Soul Emperor to freely attack him again!

Lin Ming bit down on the tip of his tongue and burnt the Gate of Life’s blood essence.

The strength from the burning blood essence caused Lin Ming’s blood vitality to seethe within his body!

He clenched his teeth, his eyes blazing at the Soul Emperor.

However, the Soul Emperor merely curved his lips upwards slightly. “Burning your blood essence? You have opened the Gate of Life, and if you burn a little bit of blood essence you can still restore yourself. But, this will only make your strength pass away that much faster, and bring you nearer to death that much quicker.

“Let me help you along!”

This time, the Soul Emperor stretched out his entire palm. This palm seemed to hold a great universe as it came crashing down upon Lin Ming!

At this time, Lin Ming’s strength had already been gathered to the limit. He cried out into the heavens, his mortal body nearly fusing together with the Black Dragon Spear!

Spear and man as one!

Weng!

Lin Ming’s body and the Black Dragon Spear turned into a divine dragon that danced through the air. The divine dragon roared as it shot towards the Soul Emperor’s palm.

However, no matter how mighty and majestic the divine dragon was, in front of this hand that seemed to command the heavens and earth, it was actually no different from a bug. The divine dragon was about to be pinched by the hand!

Lin Ming roared out, burning another 10% of his blood essence!

“Hahh!”

A loud cry broke through the skies. In this crucial moment, Lin Ming’s speed rapidly rose up once more and he forcefully pushed out from between the fingers of that giant hand.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The heavens and earth collapsed and stars were torn apart. In the surrounding trillion miles, the meteorite belt turned into powder. The countless meteorites and asteroids disintegrated to dust!

The explosive shockwave swept through the entire galaxy. This feeling was as if the galaxy itself had been cut in half!

“What is that!?”

A trillion miles away, several human World Kings saw the apocalyptic scene occurring before them.

“Is that the supernova of a super star?” A World King mumbled, shocked. They were stationed in this part of the galaxy but didn’t know that Lin Ming’s hidden world was within their guarding area.

“No, this is two super existences fighting!”

A World King said, his complexion grim. “Hurry and send the news, immediately inform Senior Emperor Shakya!”

“Yes!”

……….

“Mm? You actually managed to escape my palm at the last moment?”

The Soul Emperor watched as Lin Ming ran about from between the creases of his fingers, hurtling towards him without stop. A flash of surprise appeared in his filthy eyes.

“My attack seems to have stimulated the potential within your body. Still, nothing has changed.”

The Soul Emperor wanted to take back his hand and attack once more. But at this time, the rapidly soaring Lin Ming changed his attack trajectory.

From hurtling straight towards the Soul Emperor, he forcefully turned himself a sharp 90 degrees!

Ca!

The Soul Emperor’s sea of suffering force field was torn apart by Lin Ming without end!

The sea of suffering didn’t hinder the Soul Emperor’s strength and attacks, but, it would suppress Lin Ming. However at this time, with Lin Ming fused together with his spear as one, this force field was torn open by him instead!

With Lin Ming’s body as the center, seawater curled up into a storm as he opened up a whirlpool passage!

“You want to flee? An intelligent decision!”

A playful look crossed the Soul Emperor’s features. Lin Ming’s strike was not aimed to injure him but to break through the sea of suffering and escape!

If one faced an enemy that far exceeded themselves, and knew perfectly well that fighting the enemy meant certain death, then continuing to fight was not bravery but stupidity. Moreover, Lin Ming also had his family with him right now.

He didn’t want his family to be buried with him.

Bang!

The boundaries to the sea of suffering were ripped open. Lin Ming overdrew his blood vitality. With the massive backlash of doing so, he spat out a mouthful of blood. However, Lin Ming ignored his injuries and flew non-stop into the depths of the universe!

He ripped open a space channel and shuttled through the void!

In a battle between martial artists, one only needed to be slightly stronger to defeat someone else. But to kill the other party, that was actually far more difficult.

In particular if the other party was attempting to escape with all their might.

Since Lin Ming knew he couldn’t contend with the Soul Emperor, he chose to temporarily run away.

“You… think you can escape?”

The moment that Lin Ming broke into the void, an ancient rune flashed out from between the Soul Emperor’s eyebrows. This was a spirit mark; it directly fell upon Lin Ming’s body.

In the past, Lin Ming had already suffered enough losses and experienced enough pain thanks to a True Divinity mark. Now, another mark appeared on his body…

Lin Ming’s thoughts darkened. He could feel the mark that stuck onto his body and knew what he faced now was a great life and death crisis.

He seemed to have returned to the time when he was being chased down by Soaring Feather God King. No matter how much he tore through space and transferred through the void, the Soul Emperor still followed tightly behind!

Chapter 2215 – Moth to the Flame

Transferring through the void again and again, the Soul Emperor’s True Divinity mark was no different from a life-reaping symbol. With Lin Ming’s strength, if he were given enough time then he could erase it. But now the Soul Emperor would never give him this time.

Lin Ming didn’t know how long he spent racing through the starry skies. From the edges of the wild universe, he flew towards the central region.

At this time, just as Lin Ming underwent another great void transfer and left the space channel, he could see that not too far away there was a planet. This planet was filled with life and beautiful scenery. There were some people who lived simple farming lives and there were also martial artists who had gathered to form small sects. This was a common human planet in the wild universe.

2000 years ago, the mortals of humanity had already begun to spread out and develop throughout the wild universe. Afterwards the Saint Sovereign left seclusion, but because there weren’t many saint Empyreans who rejoined the war effort, the saints no longer had the ability to engage in a large-scale slaughter and encirclement like they did in the past. Because of this, the common people of humanity weren’t much affected.

Just as Lin Ming saw this planet of the human race and before he could pass through the void again, he could see that in the skies above, a giant hand came crashing down, rolling over the planet.

Lin Ming’s heartbeat nearly came to a stop. Without any suspense, the planet blew apart, turning into endless stones. A massive energy storm formed which turned the countless lives on the planet into nothing but space dust!

This was the hand of the Soul Emperor!

Lin Ming’s mind was filled with pure hatred. Just like that, all life on an entire planet had been snuffed out, no different from someone stepping on a crowd of ants.

And presently he didn’t have the ability to defeat the Soul Emperor. He could only grit his teeth and continue escaping.

But at this time, from that crushed planet, endless ghosts and suffering souls flew out. From the summoning powers of the Soul Emperor, these souls weren’t destroyed in the energy storm but began to rapidly gather together in a range of tens of thousands of miles.

Everything within Lin Ming’s field of vision was flooded with a suffocating dark gray. Death energy rose up, fusing into space. The space channel that Lin Ming began to tear open seemed to be caught in a swamp and he was unable to open it any further.

Lin Ming’s heart sank. The Soul Emperor had fused this death energy into the void of the universe, changing the nature of space itself so that it was impossible to undergo a great void transfer in this area!

If he wanted to continue shuttling through space, he would need to break past this domain!

Lin Ming didn’t even give it a thought. He no longer tried to transfer through space and instead bit down on the tip of his tongue, erupting with the limit of speed and strength, wanting to rush out from the domain. But at this time, the Soul Emperor’s overwhelming pressure came crashing down over Lin Ming.

“You, cannot escape.”

The Soul Emperor’s palm came slapping down, striking Lin Ming as he tried to flee. The slap exploded behind Lin Ming and a shockwave rushed out like landslides and tsunamis. Lin Ming was caught in the waves. Like a bird shot down by an arrow , he began tumbling away!

His original speed and savage momentum had been scattered by the Soul Emperor. With it, raging death energy gathered towards Lin Ming, causing him to feel like he fell into a mire!

The Soul Emperor thrust out a finger. This finger didn’t fall onto Lin Ming, but pointed somewhere in the void. The void began to twist, and beneath the strength of the Soul Emperor, a space gate opened.

Wu! Wu! Wu! Wu!

Mournful roars echoed from the space gate. Four black rakshasas walked out.

These four rakshasas were formed from remnant souls; their bodies overflowed with the ancient aura of kings.

This sort of aura wasn’t something that could be possessed by ordinarily refined soul puppets, but was an aura that only genuinely supreme powerhouses could have, true rulers of the world.

This meant that these four rakshasas weren’t made from ordinary remnant souls, but from ancient god kings who emerged from the 33 Heavens billions of years ago.

After they died, their souls had been refined by the Soul Emperor and they became his soul puppets.

“Your mortal body is formidable. You’ve done everything in your power and can even withstand several of my attacks. However… I am done waiting.

“Explode!”

The Soul Emperor’s gaze was indifferent. He flicked his finger and the four rakshasas hurtled towards Lin Ming.

At the same time, the Soul Emperor thrust out a palm at Lin Ming. A black hand appeared, so large so it could hold a planet. This hand emitted infinite death energy as it came smashing down onto Lin Ming!

As for those four rakshasas, they revolved their energies to their limits. Their eyes turned red and cracks began to run over their bodies from the terrifying percolation of energy in them.

Recalling the word ‘explode’ that the Soul Emperor had just said, Lin Ming understood that these four rakshasas wanted to rush over and explode on him!

The Soul Emperor didn’t plan on using the rakshasas to divert his attention, but to blow him up instead!

Lin Ming was originally able to rely upon his deep abilities to fight back as he ran away, delaying the Soul Emperor as long as possible. But, if the Soul Emperor were to discard these four rakshasa puppets and blow them up and also attack himself at the same time, then it would be impossible for Lin Ming to resist this attack!

And to the Soul Emperor, these four rakshasa puppets that were formed from ancient God Kings weren’t anything at all.

The Soul Emperor’s attack blocked all directions that Lin Ming could evade in. The black hand came crashing down and the four rakshasas blocked all directions! With this, Lin Ming had been placed in a great life and death crisis!

In this critical moment, Lin Ming smashed a fist into his own chest. He spat out a mouthful of blood essence and burned it without hesitation!

A black bead appeared in front of him. It completely absorbed all the burning blood essence and emitted a blood red brilliance!

Lin Ming had used the Grandmist Spirit Bead, and even allowed it to drink its fill of his blood essence!

Lin Ming had opened the Gate of Life, and even if he burned blood essence he could still restore it. But, there was actually a limit to burning his blood essence. If he burned over 30% of his blood essence then he would be left weakened for many days. If he burned over 50% of his blood essence then it would cause permanent damage to his body. If he were to burn over 70-80% of his blood essence, then this might be a fatal wound!

But now Lin Ming could no longer care about such things. Facing the Soul Emperor’s attack, if he didn’t burn his blood essence then he would undoubtedly die!

Lin Ming attacked. The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace appeared behind him and the strength of his demon avatar fused into his true self.

Scales enveloped Lin Ming’s body and fierce bone spikes drilled out from his elbows. Lin Ming roared out aloud, and together with the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he hurtled forwards, turning into a meteor that shot towards the Soul Emperor's black hand!

Lin Ming knew that even the combined force of the four exploding rakshasas couldn’t compare to the might of the Soul Emperor's palm. If he were to be struck by this palm then he would immediately disintegrate into dust and ashes!

Bang!

With a deep explosion, the black hand was forcefully pierced through by Lin Ming. But, Lin Ming’s recently regenerated body broke down once more. His meridians were torn apart and his joints cracked open. As he held his spear, his arms were twisted at a strange angle and bones jutted out from his flesh and blood.

This was a completely disparate battle. Facing the Soul Emperor, even though he was only an avatar of his true form, Lin Ming still wasn’t able to resist him.

Lin Ming was sent flying backwards. And at this time, the four rakshasas flew towards him!

Lin Ming’s thoughts sank; he could feel rising despair!

If Lin Ming was in his peak state and stimulated his protective power of divinity and demons to the limit, then he could forcefully withstand these four exploding rakshasas.

But now, his strength was exhausted, his organs broken, and he was wounded all over. He was barely able to pour energy into his shattered meridians and his crushed skeleton wasn’t able to mobilize the power of his mortal body. He was nearly defenseless, and in this completely spent condition, he could only stare helplessly on as these four rakshasas were about to explode around him!

This was a strike he absolutely could not withstand!

Without a single pause, the four rakshasas revolved their energies to their limits and then exploded together!

Bang!

It was like four suns erupting. A blinding divine light swallowed everything. In that violent storm of energy, Lin Ming blinked as a shield of white energy shrouded his body.

A warm feeling covered him, energizing his body that was nearly completely broken down, and seemed to even be accelerating his healing.

But such a situation left Lin Ming’s mind tensed.

Who!?

Although the four rakshasas exploding together was still inferior to the Soul Emperor’s strike, if one had to look throughout the entire 33 Heavens, who could withstand it?

The light faded away. A white figure hovered in front of Lin Ming, guarding him. She was the one who had forcefully propped up that protective energy shield just now.

She, was Divine Dream!

At this time, Divine Dream’s chest was already dyed completely red with blood. The flexible armor formed from her energy had torn apart. Her arms that supported the protective shield fell down, limp, as the bones in them had already been crushed to pieces.

Not just that, but blood streamed out from her eyes, nose, and ears. Her originally star-bright eyes had dimmed and had lost their luster.

Divine Dream was the first human to break into True Divinity. When Lin Ming returned, she had long since gone into seclusion for 2000 years to break into middle True Divinity. Besides Lin Ming, she was the greatest powerhouse of humanity.

And today was her first battle since stepping into middle True Divinity.

Or perhaps, this couldn’t even be called a battle at all, but a moth flying into the flames…

Chapter 2216 – Heaven and Man as One

From when Lin Ming first started fighting with the Soul Emperor, the human race headquarters had already obtained news of it. Even though they knew perfectly well that they couldn’t play any effective role in Lin Ming’s battle, they still couldn’t stand idly by and ignore the danger that Lin Ming was in.

Even disregarding the fact that Lin Ming had rescued them several times, if Lin Ming died then humanity would soon follow.

Lin Ming and the Soul Emperor did not conceal the location of their battle at all; wherever they went, the earth would shake and the heavens would crumble. It wasn’t difficult for human True Divinities to use their sense and lock onto the path that Lin Ming fled in and where the Soul Emperor was chasing him. With this, the high level figures of humanity started to rush towards Lin Ming, and the first one to arrive was naturally the strongest of them all; Divine Dream, who had just left seclusion.

“Senior Divine Dream!”

Lin Ming’s body flickered and he arrived at the side of Divine Dream and helped support her. After being heavily wounded by the Soul Emperor, Divine Dream couldn’t even stand steady.

As he watched Divine Dream bleed from her head and her spiritual sea darkening, Lin Ming bit his lips, rage filling his heart!

As his life was hanging by a thread, Divine Dream had overdrawn her life in order to block that catastrophe for him. Now, he could feel Divine Dream’s life aura rapidly weakening. This left Lin Ming burning with worry!

“There is actually someone who came to rescue you without a care for their life… and to give you a chance to catch your breath. Since this is the case, let me fulfill your wishes and allow you to die together.”

As the Soul Emperor spoke, he stretched out his palm. The surface of his palm tore open and a bone staff drilled out from the flesh and blood.

The bone staff was 10 feet long and glossy, as if it were made from black agate.

This was the Soul Emperor’s weapon!

The Soul Emperor had the appearance of a youth and wasn’t too tall. This bone staff that was hidden in his body was actually a good deal longer than his height.

It was genuinely crafted from the bones of the Demon God from 100 billion years ago; it had already reached an unimaginably high grade!

As the Soul Emperor brandished this bone staff, his aura became far more terrifying.

Seeing this weapon and feeling the immense pressure of the Soul Emperor, Divine Dream shivered; this was not a level of strength that a True Divinity could contend with.

“Lin Ming… I will give you the final measure of my strength…”

Divine Dream struggled to say with a true essence sound transmission. She had already been severely weakened. The difference between her and the Soul Emperor was far too great. In order to block his strike she had to overdraw her blood vitality, and the injuries she sustained in the process were far too deep. She was almost only managing to support herself with her will alone.

Now, it was impossible for the strength she had left remaining to pose any threat to the Soul Emperor. The only thing she could do to play a role in this battle was to burn her blood vitality and divine soul and pass that strength on to Lin Ming.

With the strength of her divine soul as the conductor, she could pass the last dregs of her power into Lin Ming’s body. Then, combined with Lin Ming’s Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and True Divinity strength, he could reach the peak of essence, energy, and divine. With this, he might have a possibility of blocking the Soul Emperor’s next attack.

But by this time, Lin Ming’s eyes had already turned blood red.

He was well aware that if Divine Dream were to burn her blood vitality and divine soul in such a state, she would undoubtedly die!

“Senior Divine Dream, I know that you want to bet everything in order to preserve my life as well as preserve the future of humanity and the 33 Heavens. But, I cannot borrow your strength. I do not want others to die for me. Moreover, my body has already been marked by the Soul Emperor’s True Divinity spirit mark. While I can escape one catastrophe, I cannot escape the second. There is simply no path left for me to retreat. In truth, ever since the first day I stepped onto the road of martial arts, there has never been any retreat for me. In my lifetime I have been defeated, I have fled, I have been schemed against, and once I even fell from the highest mountain peak to the lowest valley and experienced true death. But, I never thought of admitting defeat! If the Soul Emperor wants to kill me, then let me face him!”

As Lin Ming spoke, he burned his blood vitality without reserve! A horrifying strength rushed through him, so intense that his meridians and mortal body were barely able to withstand it. His skin began to crack apart and tear open from the pressure.

But at the same time, Lin Ming’s martial arts will rose straight up and then rose again. That invisible martial arts will seemed to turn into a peerless spear that pierced into the vastness of the universe!

The change occurring within Lin Ming left Divine Dream startled. At this time, the heavily wounded her found it hard to resist the pressure created by Lin Ming’s eruption of strength.

Bang!

With the Soul Emperor at the center, a storm of energy erupted, covering Lin Ming and Divine Dream. This energy storm was only the Soul Emperor’s opening move, but this opening move was already able to disintegrate any Empyrean level martial artist!

Beneath the tearing strength of this storm, the severely wounded Divine Dream was naturally unable to resist it.

Lin Ming opened up a protective shield of the power of divinity and demons, stimulated his strength to the limit!

“Strength! Give me strength! More strength! Strength beyond strength!”

Lin Ming roared in his mind. The demon spine buried in Lin Ming’s flesh and blood was pulled out by him. With the support of the Grandmist Spirit Bead, it was forcefully swallowed into his body!

Such a Demon God bone would be difficult to digest if it were fused into his flesh and blood, and it would even have side effects. But at this time, Lin Ming couldn’t care about such things!

“Mm?” The Soul Emperor’s complexion changed for the first time. As Lin Ming wildly combusted his blood essence, he could feel that Lin Ming’s divine soul had reached an unprecedented peak!

This was a transformation that could only occur on the precipice of life and death. The Soul Emperor’s expression became several points more dignified. “This child cannot be allowed to remain alive!”

In this battle, the Soul Emperor was able to feel just how terrifying Lin Ming actually was. He had to take advantage of this time to destroy him!

The Soul Emperor attacked. The bone staff shot forwards, crashing towards Lin Ming and Divine Dream like the collapse of the world!

At this time, Lin Ming lifted his hands and placed the weakened Divine Dream into the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

Lin Ming lifted his arms evenly. A blood red lotus appeared in his right hand and an Asura wheel appeared in his left.

These were the two highest Laws that Lin Ming cultivated – the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra!

Then, Lin Ming brought his hands together. From between his eyebrows, his Eternal Soul blazed like an inferno, like a blinding sun!

With the support of that incredible divine soul, the originally incompatible Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra began to thoroughly fuse together at this moment!

Lin Ming had already started the initial steps in fusing together the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra in the Demon God’s Tomb. And in order to completely fuse the two together, what he needed was a turning point!

And today, Lin Ming fused together the universe of the world and the universe of the body. At this moment, his mortal body, inner world, and divine soul, completely fused together with the universe of the 33 Heavens!

Lin Ming’s body was like a star, like all things in existence. The energy in his body was like the origin energy of the universe, and his soul was like the Heavenly Dao Laws!

The strength of the 33 Heavens’ universe flowed towards Lin Ming!

Lin Ming’s strength climbed at a maddening pace. This was no longer just his strength, but strength that came from all lives and all worlds in the 33 Heavens!

Lin Ming attacked. He didn’t use the Black Dragon Spear again. At this time, his flesh and blood body had turned into a spear; his will was the sharpest spear point!

Lin Ming’s figure turned into a dazzling beam of light that thrust straight towards the Soul Emperor and collided with that bone staff!

With a silent collision, the world lost all color. All that remained was a heaven-destroying divine light that lit up the entire wild universe.

Great worlds shattered and rivers of stars were cut apart. In this horrifying impact, Lin Ming’s mortal body cracked apart and his arms were nearly reduced to bones!

However, the Soul Emperor’s body shook and he was thrown hundreds of thousands of miles away!

“How… is this possible?”

The Soul Emperor steadied his body and came to a stop, his features completely frozen.

He looked at Lin Ming and then lowered his head. With a dazed expression, he could see a shocking hole in his body!

His snow white robes were dyed crimson with fresh blood. This wound nearly passed through his chest. He couldn’t remember just how long it had been since he had received such a heavy wound.

“You actually… wounded me?”

The Soul Emperor felt this unbelievable.

He was a Beyond Divinity existence! And even amongst Beyond Divinity level powerhouses, he was still an outstanding individual!

Now, although he was only an avatar and only had a fraction of his main form’s strength, it still wasn’t a level that a True Divinity could contend with.

The Soul Emperor covered his chest. His flesh and blood crept about, wriggling as it tried to regrow. However, this wound contained the strength of the Great Dao Laws and was equal to a scar created by the Great Dao; it wouldn’t regenerate for a short period of time.

Not just that, but the Soul Emperor also felt an agonizing pain wrack his spiritual sea. Lin Ming’s attack had not only pierced through the Soul Emperor’s mortal body but also injured his divine soul.

The strength of the Soul Emperor’s divine soul far surpassed anyone’s in the universe, and yet he had actually been wounded by Lin Ming!

“You have really… surprised me! But even so… you cannot change your fate.”

The Soul Emperor moved forwards one step at a time. At this time, not too far away, Lin Ming had already become a completely blood-drenched person. The arms that held the Grandmist Spirit Bead had nearly turned into white bones.

Chapter 2218 – The Soul Emperor’s World

What the Soul Emperor cultivated was to fuse the super world of the Demon God’s Tomb into himself, turning it into his own strength. Finally, his body would become one with the world, and if the world was indestructible then he would also be immortal!

Now the Soul Emperor had opened up an eye between his eyebrows, and the endless starry skies contained within that eye was the world of the Demon God’s Tomb!

This meant that the Soul Emperor was already putting his full effort into this battle. This technique was also one that the Soul Emperor had yet to fully control because he hadn’t finished his seclusion. After all, he had yet to thoroughly refine the Demon God’s Tomb.

“Be careful, this old bastard is ready to go all-out!”

“Lin Ming, eat this pill!”

Ink and Clear nearly spoke at the same time. A round pill suddenly appeared in Lin Ming’s hand.

Lin Ming glanced down. This pill was a deep green and it was unknown how it was refined. It seemed a bit soft, but it was a hard as jade. The surface of this jade bead was covered in circular traces, making it seem particularly special.

Although he was puzzled, now was not the time to speak. He immediately swallowed down the pill and felt it melt within him, turning into a warm strength that revitalized his body.

Lin Ming burning his own blood essence had originally caused permanent damage to his body. However, after eating up this pill, Lin Ming felt his own blood vitality surge through his body once more. Although it was impossible to completely cure the side effects created from overdrawing upon his life, it would increase his combat strength and extend it for that much longer.

This sort of pill could immediately display effects after eating it and wouldn’t need one to meditate and digest it. Moreover, it could help someone whose strength far surpassed most peak True Divinity powerhouses; it could be imagined how precious it was.

“You rest first. Clear, let’s attack!”

Ink and Clear look at each other. Both of them had lived for a long, long time, and had already formed a tacit understanding with each other. If they joined forces then their combat strength would rise to another level.

The two people stood in the void and a golden array diagram appeared beneath their feet. Ink and Clear were positioned in the two eyes of this array diagram. This array diagram was Clear’s array disc. At the same time, a giant furnace floated above their heads, constantly revolving and emitting beams of light.

Rah!

With a loud roar, two Asura phantoms appeared behind both Clear and Ink.

These Asuras seethed with killing intent and gradually fused with Ink and Clear’s mortal bodies.

The Asura phantoms were sucked into their bodies!

Seeing this, Lin Ming was startled. Ink and Clear obviously cultivated the Asura Heavenly Dao, but their combat method in utilizing it was completely different from his own.

After the two of them displayed their arcane techniques, their combat strength rose to an all new peak! With it, their old and wizened appearance began to change. Their bodies rose and their expressions became grim and resolute. Their wrinkles vanished and their hair turned pitch black; they had rejuvenated themselves from their old age, restoring the appearance of their youths.

Their muscles grew and their blood vitality rushed through their bodies; they had been reborn!

Neither of them remembered when the last time they used this secret technique was. There were far too many limits on it, and for them it would exhaust a tremendous amount of their energies and even cause their lifespans to plummet. However, facing the Soul Emperor, they could no longer worry about such things.

“Attack!”

Ink and Clear shouted out together. The golden array disc and Galaxy Void Furnace that swirled above and below also shot out, ruthlessly smashing down towards the Soul Emperor!

Ink and Clear and struck out with all their strength. Seeing this, the Soul Emperor merely chuckled. From between his eyebrows, the void within that third eye rapidly expanded. The world of the Demon God’s Tomb turned into a visible wave that rushed out and swallowed all!

For a time, the Soul Emperor seemed to stand in a separate space-time dimension. As for Ink and Clear, their attacks were all sucked into this different space-time dimension!

Bang! Bang!

Energy exploded, an explosion with enough power to compare to a supernova. A storm of energy swept out. However, that separate space-time remained stable to an unbelievable degree. Everything else was crushed by the storm of energy, but that space-time remained undamaged.

Like this, Ink and Clear’s all-out attack had inexplicably vanished. All that remained were the golden array disc and giant furnace that slowly flew back into their hands. However, the array disc and furnace had lost a great deal of their spirituality by now.

As the two of them saw their own respective weapons return, their bodies froze. From the start, their enemy the Soul Emperor had only stood not too far away in the void, not even taking a single step forwards.

“How is this possible!?”

Ink and Clear were bewildered. Their joint attack was enough to instantly and overwhelmingly kill the vast majority of True Divinities. Even though it would be impossible to kill the Soul Emperor like that, their attack still shouldn’t be so weak and pathetic that they couldn’t even touch the hem of his robes!

“He shifted away Seniors’ attacks!”

Lin Ming suddenly said, a dignified expression on his face. He was clearly aware of what cultivation method the Soul Emperor trained in and what that technique was just now.

The problem was in the third eye that appeared between the Soul Emperor’s eyebrows. Just now, the space of the Demon God’s Tomb had expanded to an infinite degree from between his eyebrows and swallowed up Ink and Clear’s joint attack.

“Shifted…”

After listening to Lin Ming’s words, Ink and Clear gradually realized a possibility, and this possibility caused their complexions to change.

“What is withstanding your attack is not the Soul Emperor himself, but the world of the Demon God’s Tomb!”

Lin Ming’s said, his words confirming Ink and Clear’s guess. As they realized this, their hearts sank and despair surged in their mind.

To use a world to withstand their attacks?

They could heavily wound the mortal body of the Soul Emperor, but what about destroying a world?

Although it was said that a True Divinity possessed the ability to destroy worlds, that was only true for low level worlds. When it came to worlds like the 33 Heavens or Dark Abyss, these super universes were worlds that True Divinities simply didn’t possess the ability to destroy.

And the Demon God’s Tomb was equivalent to a compressed super universe; it had even managed to withstand the great Shattering of the previous universal era!

How could the power of man possibly destroy such a world?

If the Soul Emperor could freely shift their attacks into the world of the Demon God’s Tomb, then how could they continue fighting with him? He was already standing in an invincible position!

Without a doubt, the space of the Demon God’s Tomb was the most perfect and most indestructible defense in existence!

“Could this move have no limit?” Ink asked, unwilling to admit defeat like this.

The more powerful a technique, the more restrictions it had; this was true for all abilities. But, this might not be true for the Soul Emperor, because the Demon God’s Tomb was part of his body and what he did just now was equal to using a part of his body to resist their attack.

Lin Ming said with a sound transmission, ”Seniors, the Soul Emperor had already started the initial fusion with the world of the Demon God’s Tomb. This move shouldn’t have a limit in what it can shift away, but perhaps there is a limit in how long the Soul Emperor can maintain this state…”

Lin Ming speculated. The basis of this conjecture was that the Soul Emperor hadn’t completed his seclusion and hadn’t thoroughly fused with the Demon God’s Tomb. Moreover, when he fought with him, the Soul Emperor hadn’t used this technique and he even managed to wound the Soul Emperor because of it.

This shouldn’t be because the Soul Emperor underestimated him but because there was some sort of limit. The Soul Emperor wasn’t willing to use the space of the Demon God’s Tomb from the start, so Lin Ming believe there must be some price involved in order to maintain this space.

“As long as there is a limit then we just have to last until the end.” Clear said, gritting his teeth. He also had some cards left hidden in his hands.

Lin Ming said, “I remember that in the Demon God’s Tomb, Senior Immortal Sovereign advised me to never fight with the Soul Emperor in the Demon God’s Tomb unless I possessed the ability to tear apart the world of the Demon God’s Tomb. We naturally don’t have this ability. And just now, the Soul Emperor used the space of the Demon God’s Tomb to absorb your attacks, and I don’t know whether or not he can also suck us into the space of the Demon God’s Tomb…”

Lin Ming’s words were like a cold gale drifting up from the nine nether abyss, causing a chill to creep up Ink and Clear’s back.

To suck everyone into the space of the Demon God’s Tomb?

This was the same as being a turtle in a jar; anyone who was drawn in would undoubtedly die!

What should they do?

Ink and Clear were at a loss. And, all they faced was the Soul Emperor, an avatar of his true form.

If this were the complete form of the Soul Emperor then he would have an even deeper level of control of the world of the Demon God’s Tomb. If so, just how formidable would he be?

“Form the array!”

Ink said, his complexion solemn. He didn’t know whether or not the eye between the Soul Emperor’s eyebrows could suck them in as Lin Ming said, but if he did use such an ability, the consequences would be unimaginable!

“You think this can stop me? Then, it should be my turn to attack.”

As the Soul Emperor spoke, his strength began to climb without limit. The eye between his eyebrows expanded to an infinite degree. A black vortex appeared, swallowing in the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy. At the same time, Ink, Clear, Lin Ming, and Sheng Mei all felt a massive suction force pull upon their bodies.

A horrifying force field fell over them, blocking out their surroundings. This suction force made them feel as if they would soon be drawn into the space of the Demon God’s Tomb.

Their complexions changed. If the Soul Emperor truly possessed the ability to draw them all into the space of the Demon God’s Tomb, then there was no need to continue this battle.

All of them would surely die; this was the only outcome.

Chapter 2221 – Sudden Change

An overwhelming inferno of rage surged in the Soul Emperor’s heart.

He hated!

He hated Lin Ming, hated Sheng Mei, hated Immortal Sovereign!

Even with that last strike he had still failed, and now it would be incredibly difficult to kill Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s life force had reached unbelievable heights. His Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were opened to the eighth Dao Palace, his acupoints and meridians were thoroughly connected and linked, and with him having swallowed a totem level abyssal and dual cultivating divinity and demons, as well as comprehending two of the highest Laws, whether it was his body, inner world, or divine soul, they had reached mind-boggling levels.

Everyone knew that Lin Ming had contributed the most strength to this battle. He had consumed the most blood vitality and had fought for the longest time. And as the fight continued on, Lin Ming still had strength left.

Rather, it was more accurate to say that Lin Ming had already overdrawn his strength, but his powerful mortal body allowed him to recover some energy in a short period of time.

As for Clear and Ink, they had already returned to their old and wizened appearance and their strength had precipitously weakened; they might have even dropped boundaries. As for Sheng Mei, her spiritual sea had split open and her consciousness was blurred; she had lost any power to resist.

The Soul Emperor gripped his fists. With his face torn open by the black flames from within, he looked fierce and hideous.

With the near collapse of the Emperor Bone Sea, he no longer dared to transfer any of his own strength.

But at this time, from far off in the void, rainbow-hued energy beams soared towards him. This was an energy attack condensed from a multitude of Laws.

“What!?”

Feeling this energy hurtle towards him, the Soul Emperor glanced over. He saw that the many human Empyreans had gathered into an array formation under Emperor Shakya’s leadership and had actually attacked him!

“Just a bunch of ants that have no idea of death or danger!”

The Soul Emperor fumed. In his most glorious state, Empyrean level attacks were no different from scratching an itch. With a thought he could have tuned all these Empyreans into ashes.

But now, after being severely wounded and facing a situation in which the Emperor Bone Sea had almost collapsed, the great attack formed from the human Empyreans was now actually a threat to him!

If the chain reaction of energy were to rush into the world of the Demon God’s Tomb, then it might become the final straw that broke the camel’s back and cause the Emperor Bone Sea to utterly collapse.

“All of you, remember me!”

The Soul Emperor said, so angry his eyes nearly popped out of his head. He grabbed the bone staff and poured in energy one more time before firing it towards Lin Ming!

Hum - !

The bone staff was like a meteor that contained the world strength of the Demon God’s Tomb. It pierced through the energy wave sent out by the numerous Empyreans and thrust towards Lin Ming’s chest.

“Protect Lin Ming!”

Emperor Shakya roared out. Many Empyreans immediately shifted their target. For a time, all sorts of different weapons and Law lights shot towards the bone staff shot out by the Soul Emperor.

If there were enough ants, even an elephant could be bitten to death. Moreover, the bone staff shot out by the Soul Emperor didn’t have much strength behind it to begin with. In the mighty waves of energy, the bone staff was like a fish caught in a swamp, rapidly forced to a slow crawl.

But at this time, the Soul Emperor had turned around and was rapidly flying towards Sheng Mei!

“Damn!”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken!

At this time, everyone’s attention was turned towards Lin Ming. They were well aware that the Soul Emperor’s goal was Lin Ming and he was the greatest threat to the Soul Emperor.

As everyone was guarding Lin Ming, they never thought that the Soul Emperor would also change targets, instead focusing on Sheng Mei!

In the final moments, in order to help Lin Ming block the Soul Emperor’s all-out attack, she had risked her life and had now fallen into a half-unconscious state; she was powerless to resist the Soul Emperor.

Hum –

A black vortex swirled and Sheng Mei was sucked into a black space by the Soul Emperor.

“Let her go!”

Lin Ming’s eyes turned red with rage. He didn’t have much strength remaining, barely enough to protect himself, much less attack the Soul Emperor!

“Die!”

Lin Ming recklessly attacked. He lifted the Black Dragon Spear and threw it with all his recently restored strength.

However, the might of Lin Ming’s current attack couldn’t even compare to the attack formed from the condensed power of Emperor Shakya and the numerous Empyreans.

Bang!

With a loud ring, the Black Dragon Spear crashed into the Soul Emperor’s protective energy. It was only able to pierce halfway through the energy shield before being drained of all energy and no longer able to pierce in.

The Soul Emperor turned towards Lin Ming. What dwelled in his eyes was a hint of contempt, a hint of hatred, and a hint of sinister ruthlessness.

“I will make sure you always remember today! Since this bitch is so desperately willing to rescue you, then I will have her die for you!”

As the Soul Emperor spoke he ripped open the void and stepped into a space channel.

“All of you, will die…”

The Soul Emperor’s final words were like a demonic curse that reverberated through space.

Lin Ming rushed forwards as if he had gone crazy. Even the many human Empyreans moved at this time. However, they were too slow. They could only stare blankly on as the space channel ripped open by the Soul Emperor sealed itself up.

“Ahhhh!”

Lin Ming roared out in unwillingness. In the final moment he shot out a True Divinity mark onto the Soul Emperor.

The Soul Emperor only coldly sneered, allowing the mark to fall onto his body.

“Damn it all!”

Lin Ming’s fist smashed into the void. His arms shivered with rage and his eyes were red with anger, his blood nearly frozen in his body!

He never thought that at the end, Sheng Mei would be captured by the Soul Emperor!

Without Sheng Mei risking everything to defend against the Soul Emperor’s last strike, he feared he would have already perished.

And if Sheng Mei hadn’t tried to save him then her spiritual sea wouldn’t have been torn apart and she wouldn’t have fallen into a stupor, thus being captured by the Soul Emperor without any resistance at all!

“It’s all my fault. What do I say to… Jiu’er!”

Lin Ming clenched his fists together and fell to his knees. Because of anger and worry, his nails had already dug into his flesh and blood.

Lin Ming knew of Sheng Mei’s past and also knew of how sad her fate and life experiences had been. Because of these things, Lin Ming had always felt a sense of pity for Sheng Mei. After their relationship had been clarified, Lin Ming had resolved that he would protect Sheng Mei. But, he never imagined that today it would be her protecting him instead.

She had overdrawn her life in order to block that final strike, and in the end was captured by the Soul Emperor, her life or death unknown…

What he felt was hate!

“The Soul Emperor took away Sheng Mei, but his final goal is still me. He captured Sheng Mei because he is waiting for me to rescue her!”

Lin Ming had already guessed the Soul Emperor’s goal. Since the Soul Emperor wouldn’t be able to kill him for some time, then he would simply wait for Lin Ming to personally deliver himself to his door.

To keep Sheng Mei hostage was the same as holding onto his fatal weakness!

He needed to restore his wounds as quickly as possible and rescue Sheng Mei!

“Lin Ming…”

Emperor Shakya spoke up. He could feel how turbulent Lin Ming’s mood was. His tone was hesitant and somewhat remorseful. During this battle, he hadn’t been able to play any role.

Divine Dream, Clear, Ink, Sheng Mei, they had paid a great price in order to preserve Lin Ming’s life, but Emperor Shakya had only managed to lead a crowd of Empyreans here and send out a not-too-powerful attack at the end.

In the end, they hadn’t even been able to save Sheng Mei, causing the situation to deteriorate even further.

“Lin Ming, do you plan on going to rescue her…?” Emperor Shakya didn’t know who Sheng Mei was, but he could see that she was extremely important to Lin Ming.

“If I don’t…”

Lin Ming gripped his fists together. He understood that this was a trap!

But even though he knew it was a trap, he still had to jump in.

Emperor Shakya opened his mouth to speak but hesitated. He didn’t want Lin Ming to go, but he also felt that he didn’t have the qualifications to persuade Lin Ming to do anything.

“You… will die…”

An old voice sounded out – the one who spoke was Clear.

Lin Ming turned, all sorts of complex emotions on his features.

Thousands of years ago when Lin Ming first saw Clear and Ink at the Asura Road’s final trial, they had both been overflowing with life, glowing with boisterous health.

But today, their beards and hair had gone white and their eyes had become as filthy as the Soul Emperor’s, overflowing with a faint death aura…

Seeing Clear’s appearance, Lin Ming felt an inexplicable pain clutch at his heart!

Clear and Ink had become like this because of him!

Before, he had said to Divine Dream that he didn’t want anyone to die for him. But he never imagined that even after he stopped Divine Dream from burning away her life, Sheng Mei would also fall into a crisis for him and Clear and Ink would exhaust their lives.

“That old demon has certainly set up a trap to wait for you. In our home ground, all of us are here and yet we were beaten into such a state by just an avatar. If you were to fight in a place that he set up instead, you would surely die…”

Ink also said.

How could Lin Ming not understand his words?

If he were to try and rescue Sheng Mei, it couldn’t even be described as a slim chance of survival!

“Senior, I know this, but I…”

As Lin Ming spoke to here he fell silent. No matter what, he couldn’t finish those final words of ‘I must go’.

In particular, as he looked at Clear and Ink who had lost a great deal of their life force, who had placed all their hopes in him, he couldn’t bear to face their dirtied eyes…

Chapter 2222 – Choice

Lin Ming’s mind trembled. He clenched his fists.

He knew that his life was no longer entirely his own.

His was a life that Divine Dream, Clear, Ink, and Immortal Sovereign had desperately risked themselves to save from the clutches of the Soul Emperor.

Not just that, but on Lin Ming’s road of growth, he had encountered many teachers and benefactors. They had pushed him forwards, pouring of all their hopes into him so that he could inherit their legacies.

If he were to risk his life to Sheng Mei and was ultimately killed by the Soul Emperor, then how could he answer to them?

Realizing this, Ink said, “We aren’t only saving you, but also saving ourselves. Without you, there is no one else capable of stopping that old demon. When the great catastrophe descends upon this world, I fear that there might no longer be any lives left existing in the 33 Heavens…”

“In truth, I don’t have any qualifications to ask you to do anything; your choice is your own to make. However, I don’t wish for you to send yourself to die. The key question here is, if you die, can you exchange your life for hers?”

Clear sighed. These words caused Lin Ming’s thoughts to darken. Indeed, if he went to rescue Sheng Mei, then not to mention the disparity in strength between them, if the Soul Emperor were to be a little bit despicable and threaten him with Sheng Mei then he would have no choice but to be cautious around him in fear of hurting her. In such a situation, how could he possibly win?

His chances of defeating the Soul Emperor could be called near impossible. And if he didn’t kill the Soul Emperor, how could he rescue Sheng Mei?

Even if he offered his own life, would the Soul Emperor even consider this and be gracious enough to release Sheng Mei?

The Soul Emperor’s hatred towards Sheng Mei was enough for him to refine her soul and marrow a thousand times over!

But, if he didn’t try to rescue her…

As Lin Ming thought of Sheng Mei’s fate having fallen into the Soul Emperor’s hands, he felt as if his heart was being pulled out; it was almost unbearable to breathe!

He was lost.

On one side, he was the hope of humanity and perhaps even the hope of all life in the 33 Heavens. On the other side was a woman who had been through life and death with him, who had risked herself to save him…

On one side was the great cause of his race, the legacy of his seniors. On the other side was what his heart wanted, as well as the love between a man and a woman.

To Lin Ming, this was an extremely agonizing choice.

Lin Ming took out the Grandmist Spirit Bead. In a daze, he released Divine Dream, Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, and the others.

Divine Dream was also incomparably weak. Within the Spirit Bead space, Xiao Moxian had exhausted every method at her disposal to stabilize Divine Dream’s weakening fires of life.

“Divine Dream!”

Seeing Divine Dream appear, Empyrean Vast Universe was immediately moved and thrilled. Out of those here, he had the deepest feelings for Divine Dream.

Divine Dream’s body was stained with blood. Her face was pale and her life force was constantly draining from her.

“Seniors, do you have a pill that can make up for blood vitality?”

Lin Ming asked, finding it a bit difficult to say. He could guess that Clear and Ink likely didn’t have too many precious pills with them.

“We do, but the grade is inferior to the one we gave you.”

Ink took out a pill bottle from his spatial ring. With a faint movement, a green medicinal pill tumbled out from the pill bottle.

“Seniors, you won’t take any?” Lin Ming asked with worry; he could sense Clear and Ink’s weakened life force.

Clear shook his head. “These are pills from our master’s pill furnace. These pills are suited to the races of the 33 Heavens. As temple spirits, the strength of our blood vitality is different from yours and eating these pills would be useless.”

“Master…” Lin Ming’s heart shook. He remembered that Clear and Ink had said that the Asura Road Master had yet to die, but he simply didn’t know where the Asura Road Master had gone. When he asked Clear and Ink about this, their reply had been that once Lin Ming possessed the strength to become a chess player instead of a chess piece, then that was when he would be informed of the Asura Road Master’s whereabouts.

And now, Lin Ming believed he had this strength.

But now was not the time to ask such questions. Lin Ming quickly passed the pill to Divine Dream.

No matter how precious this pill was, it could only hasten Divine Dream’s ability to restore her blood vitality. To completely make up for all the side effects that Divine Dream suffered was actually incredibly difficult.

After Divine Dream swallowed the pill, a hint of red finally appeared on her face.

Lin Ming let out a sigh of relief. He looked towards Clear and Ink, “Seniors…”

Clear and Ink glanced at each other; they already guessed what Lin Ming was about to say.

Clear said, “It is time that we lead you to see our master…”

“See Senior Asura?”

Lin Ming asked, his thoughts shaken. He found it difficult to compose himself. For the majority of his life he had been hearing of the legends related to the Asura Road Master. This was the greatest powerhouse to exist in the history of all races in the 33 Heavens, an existence that surpassed Immortal Sovereign!

He was formidable and mysterious. However, what Lin Ming didn’t understand was why hadn’t he made his move yet?

Could the wounds he suffered in the past truly be so severe that not even 10 billion years was enough time to recover?

Some wounds could be restored after a period of rest or by eating up a pill.

But there were some wounds that couldn’t be recovered from. For instance, if one’s body were cut in half, and that cut off half was destroyed. Or for instance, if one’s soul or inner world was divided and destroyed.

The mortal body, inner world, and soul were the three most important parts of a life. When a martial artist practiced martial arts, it was to enhance and temper these three parts; this was the ultimate manifestation of a martial artist’s cultivation.

If the body or soul was split in half and destroyed, then although one could reform themselves, that would be equivalent to reducing one’s cultivation by half. One’s talent and potential would suffer injury and this sort of wound would also cause one’s cultivation to drop. From that point on, one’s cultivation would come to a standstill and it would be difficult to recover from this.

This was particularly true for a Beyond Divinity existence like the Asura Road Master. There might not be any True Divinity spirit treasure in existence that could help restore his wounds.

Or, it could be like when Lin Ming was at the Sky Spill Planet and his soul source was sucked out of him without anything left remaining. Such wounds were even more serious. They were similar to someone burning all of their blood essence or soul essence, and eventually their life force would run dry and they would die.

“You also come, as well as the rest of you. We will meditate for a time to restore our wounds and then leave.”

Ink said to Divine Dream as well as Lin Ming’s family members.

Divine Dream had recovered a great deal by this time and Xiao Moxian and the others had just emerged from the Grandmist Spirit Bead. They were all startled to hear this; they never thought that Clear and Ink would call on them.

Clear and Ink meditated for a period of time. Then, Ink took out an Asura Command. Joining together with Clear, they opened up a space channel leading to the Asura Road.

The wild universe was a long distance from the Asura Road and it would take some time to open the space channel. During this time, Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, as well as Lin Ming’s children, flew to his side and held his hands.

“Big Brother Lin…”

“Lin Ming…”

“Father…”

“Daddy…”

The calls of his family echoed in Lin Ming’s ears, touching his heart.

When a person was in their most helpless moments, the care of their family could dispel this helplessness and confusion.

Lin Ming looked at his family. At this time, they already learned what happened to Sheng Mei and how it happened.

“Jiu’er…”

Lin Ming traced Jiu’er’s face, unsure as to what he could say.

Jiu’er tightly gripped Lin Ming’s hand. “Mother will be alright.”

Jiu’er bit her lips and spoke in a slow and clear tone, as if she were not only telling Lin Ming this, but also herself.

“Lin Ming…”

Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, and Qin Xingxuan held onto Lin Ming’s hand. They could naturally feel the pain in his heart.

There was nothing they could do to help him with this burden. They could only hold his hands and transmit their comfort to him.

Xiao Moxian said with a sound transmission, “If you have decided on something, then go and do it. There is no need to consider us…”

Lin Ming’s heart warmed. He knew that his decision was likely to mean that he would fall into further danger in the future. If anything happened to him, it was hard to imagine what his family would experience.

Xiao Moxian didn’t want to distract Lin Ming, but how could he completely ignore his family’s thoughts? The situation he faced was far too difficult.

“I will return safely. I promise this to you all!”

Lin Ming grit his teeth and said. After that period of impulsiveness, Lin Ming had finally calmed down. If he rashly rushed out to look for the Soul Emperor, then not only would he not be able to save Sheng Mei but he would also die in vain; there would be no meaning to this.

He wanted to rescue Sheng Mei not just so he could live with a clear heart and mind, but also because he wanted to truly save her.

At this time, the space channel to the Asura Road opened.

“Let’s go.”

Ink and Clear said. They flew towards the Asura Road together. Lin Ming, Divine Dream, and Lin Ming’s family followed close behind.

After flying through the space channel for an unknown period of time, the scenery around them changed and they arrived upon a wild plain.

This was the Asura Road’s Great Desolate.

Seeing this scene before him, Lin Ming was filled with a myriad of emotions. He had returned to the Asura Road once again.

This world had accompanied Lin Ming for the majority of his life.

Chapter 2223 – Seeing Asura

“Senior Asura, is he in the Asura Road?”

Lin Ming originally had many guesses as to just where the Asura Road Master was. He even thought that the Asura Road Master might be in the Dark Abyss, perhaps even the Demon God’s Tomb.

It was only now that he learned the Asura Road Master had never left the world he created.

Ink nodded, “Master dwells here. He has been waiting all this time, waiting for a full 10 billion years. Once you see the master, you will know the whole story and the doubts in your heart will also be explained.”

As Clear and Ink spoke they began to fly towards the Asura Sea. They didn’t pass through a transmission array but directly tore through the void and crossed towards the Great Desolate.

The Asura Road had an extremely strange shape; it was very narrow and very long, just like a road, thus the reason for its name. The two ends of this ‘road’ were the outer Asura Road and the inner Asura Road with the Great Desolate acting as the dividing line. Even an Empyrean level martial artist couldn’t cross safely

But for Clear and Ink, crossing through the Great Desolate was actually easy.

As the two of them continuously opened space channels, the group only required half a day to reach the Asura Sea.

The Asura Sea was the entrance of the final trial. During every opening of the final trial, all the heroes from the various influences across the Asura Road would gather here at the Asura Sea.

This sea was unfathomably deep; even a star could be submerged within it!

The rumors said that deep in the Asura Sea there were many space labyrinths and turbulent whirlpools; there were even True Divinity level vicious beasts dwelling there. Thus, the martial artists of the Asura Road had never dared to enter the Asura Sea.

As for how deep the sea was, no one knew.

But today Lin Ming realized that he would have to go to the very bottom of the Asura Sea.

In front of him, Ink and Clear revolved their energies, forming a channel in the Asura Sea. Lin Ming passed through this channel, flying down with the group.

Their speed was incredibly fast. Lin Ming had no idea how deep down he dived; it seemed as if this sea was bottomless.

“Senior Asura is at the bottom of the Asura Sea?” Lin Ming asked.

Clear shook his head. “That isn’t completely accurate. But, you will soon know; we’ve almost arrived.”

Clear and Ink slowed down. At this time, within the thick and heavy darkness and the highly pressured seawater, Lin Ming finally saw the seabed of the Asura Sea.

The dark gray seabed was without any life at all. A massive mountain range that extended for a thousand miles lay at the bottom.

Seeing this giant mountain range, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. With his sharp senses he found that there was something unusual about this seabed.

Although it was quiet, it actually possessed faint life fluctuations.

This wasn’t a mountain range but a giant snake covered in dust!

“A True Divinity level vicious beast…” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed.

“Yes, its name is Darkness. It is the guardian of this part of the Asura Sea and if a martial artist from the Asura Road really comes down, it is responsible for chasing them away. Let’s continue forwards.” As Ink spoke, he lightly stabbed his finger towards somewhere deep in the sea. In front of them, the quiet seawater began to roll with undercurrents. A distorted space stretched and grew, forming an underwater whirlpool that sucked in Lin Ming.

Then, the seawater vanished.

The pressure deep within the Asura Sea was originally at a terrifying level. Now, Lin Ming felt his body lighten as he arrived in a strange space.

This space wasn’t too large. It was only several hundred feet in width and length. As Lin Ming saw what was around him, his heart shook.

“This space… this is…”

Lin Ming looked around him. Everything was carved from purple crystal.

Crystal furniture, crystal ground, crystal bed…

This sort of crystal shimmered with translucent light, similar to quartz. Lin Ming had never seen anything like it before. Just by gently touching it he could feel a vast sea of energy within, as if the purest energy in existence was gathered in these crystals.

“Amethyst?”

This thought inexplicably appeared in Lin Ming’s mind. More than purple crystal, it was more appropriate to call this amethyst.

Amethyst, Amethyst Origin Crystal…

“Could this be…”

As Lin Ming was deep in thought, a faint voice reverberated within this amethyst space.

“The place you are in is a cave dwelling that I refined in the past using the Amethyst Origin Crystal as the foundation. I named this place the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, but because the energy and heavenly materials required to refine it were far too much, I had to repeatedly shrink it in size. At the end, the final refined product was only several hundred feet in size.”

This sudden voice possessed an ancient majesty, making one feel something inexplicable within them. Listening to this voice, Lin Ming felt his own soul faintly resonate with it. He knew that this came from a sympathetic echoing of the Asura Laws.

This voice could cause the Asura Laws in his body to vibrate.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and fell to his knees, deeply bowing. He knew that the one who spoke was the person he came to see today.

“Junior Lin Ming greets Senior Asura!”

Lin Ming said, excited. This legendary character would finally appear before him!

He was the leader of the ancient races from 10 billion years ago, and 10 billion years ago he was already the number one character of the 33 Heavens!

Lin Ming bowed for several breaths of time before lifting his head up. What he saw before him was simply emptiness. Within this cave dwelling forged from amethyst, he still didn’t see the Asura Road Master, not even his shadow.

“There is no need to look. The majority of my body has already integrated into the Asura Road itself. This Amethyst Heavenly Palace is the cornerstone of the Asura Road, thus I had you come here…”

This ancient and majestic voice echoed in Lin Ming’s ears once more. The body had merged with the Asura Road?

Lin Ming was bewildered. The Asura Road Master had actually fused together with the Asura Road!

“Senior, since your body has fused with the Asura Road, then does this mean you cannot leave the Asura Road?”

If this was the reason then it could be explained why the Asura Road Master had yet to move against the Soul Emperor. But, why would the Asura Road Master do this?

“I know you have many questions in your heart. I also know that the reason you came here today is not just to ask these questions, but to ask me to help you in saving a woman…”

The Asura Road Master’s words caused Lin Ming’s mind to shake.

Lin Ming deeply bowed once more. “Senior Asura, junior’s beloved wife has been captured by the Soul Emperor. I ask for Senior to guide this junior onto the correct path!”

Lin Ming was well aware that no matter what he tried to do it would be difficult for him to save Sheng Mei. All that lay in front of him was a dead end, and only the Asura Road Master had a slight chance of being able to give him a guiding light.

However, Lin Ming’s question caused that majestic voice to fall silent.

Lin Ming grit his teeth, quietly waiting on.

After a long time, the Asura Road Master sighed deeply. He said, “Perhaps… the situation is different than how you think it is… the Soul Emperor may have captured your wife, but it isn’t to threaten you and have you walk into a trap. Instead, there are other reasons…”

“Other reasons?” Lin Ming was startled. Could the Soul Emperor have captured Sheng Mei just for the sake of revenge?

The Soul Emperor should know that if he killed Sheng Mei, then besides enraging Lin Ming, it wouldn’t help his great cause at all.

With the Soul Emperor’s temperament, he wouldn’t waste even a single breath for something so insignificant.

“I ask Senior to clarify the matter.” Lin Ming asked, his voice a bit anxious.

The Asura Road Master replied, “I can now sense vibrations of the Amethyst Origin Crystal. It is likely that… the Soul Emperor already stands atop the Eternal Wall…

“From what I sense of the Amethyst Origin Crystal, it makes me think of a possibility. Perhaps the Soul Emperor trained your wife because he had a goal in his mind all along. If what I think is true, then you are doomed to be unable to save her…”

The Asura Road Master’s words caused Lin Ming’s heart to fall. His hands couldn’t help but tremble.

The Soul Emperor’s goal…

Eternal Wall…

Amethyst Origin Crystal…

When the Soul Emperor first captured Sheng Mei, Lin Ming’s first thought was that he had done so to threaten him. But now, he realized that his thoughts might have been wrong from the very start!

The Soul Emperor had trained Sheng Mei with a goal in mind, a goal that even Sheng Mei didn’t know about!

The Soul Emperor had left seclusion not just to kill him, but also to find Sheng Mei!

He had misunderstood everything from the start, and he simply… couldn’t save Sheng Mei…

Couldn’t save…

Couldn’t… save…?

Lin Ming was left in a daze. He had come with hopes that the Asura Road Master would be able to guide him in the right direction, but the answer he obtained actually left him wallowing in despair.

……….

At this time, across layers of space, the Dark Abyss –

This was a vast and endless earth, one that extended beyond the horizon.

The ground was covered with countless shattered bones, dark gray ashes, and deathly stillness.

These bones were left behind by the great war 10 billion years ago between powerful abyssals and overlords of the 33 Heavens. Even though they had been eroded by the passing of time, they still shined with the light of Laws.

Darkness, killing intent, death, this was the atmosphere of this land – this was the Dark Abyss’s Eternal Wall!

The Soul Emperor stood atop the Eternal Wall, feeling the surging power of this world, deep in thought.

After a number of days, his appearance had become even more aged. The sudden changes in the Emperor Bone Sea had caused him heavy losses.

Originally only the Soul Emperor’s eyes were old and dirty and his eyes overflowing with death. However, his face remained as fine and beautiful as that of a youth, except just slightly more pale.

But now, due to the changes in the Emperor Bone Sea, his face was mottled with wrinkles and the skin on his neck had withered and cracked; he seemed like someone on the verge of death.

Behind the Soul Emperor stood a black-clothed woman. This woman was Sheng Mei; she had been captured by the Soul Emperor.

Sheng Mei’s face was pale. Her blood vitality, true essence, and Laws had all been sealed away. She was completely powerless to resist.

The Soul Emperor’s back faced Sheng Mei. He looked at this ancient battlefield from 10 billion years ago and sighed with emotion. “This land hasn’t changed even after 10 billion years…”

He turned his head and looked at Sheng Mei, a smile curving up his lips.

“Do you know why I trained you in the past?”

The Soul Emperor continued to say, “I already knew that you wanted to rebel against me in your heart and I also knew of your last life. You were the daughter of my blood enemy from 10 billion years past!

“Even so, I only planted my spirit mark in your spiritual sea to track you, and didn’t place a slave seal within you. I controlled your freedom but I didn’t control your thoughts. I allowed you to hate me, disrespect me, and I tolerated it all. I wanted your heart and mind to be unhindered. Even in the past when you wanted to save Lin Ming’s life and allow him to live the rest of his years as a mortal, I allowed you to do so…

“And all of these things, have you never considered why I did so?”

Chapter 2225 – Twists and Turns

Space locked up and slowly came drawing in. World strength surged outwards, completely covering Sheng Mei. Facing the Soul Emperor’s strength, Sheng Mei didn’t even know how to begin resisting him. She closed her eyes in pain. The sounds of bones cracking from beneath the Soul Emperor’s feet echoed in her ears like the pained howls of lost souls.

The Soul Emperor’s hand drew close. His deathly pale palm was withered and dry, a horrible sight to behold. Yet, those ten nails were sharp and cruel, shining with a cold luminescence.

Sheng Mei couldn’t even revolve her true essence right now. From half a foot away, just the cold wind coming from the Soul Emperor’s nails were enough to cut Sheng Mei’s skin.

Blood flowed out. On top of Sheng Mei’s snow white neck, it was like a red plum had fallen into the snow.

“What a beautiful color.”

The Soul Emperor’s eyes lit up with a feverishly frantic light.

As long as the Eternal Wall was opened then he could gather together his three bodies, and his strength would rise even further.

At that time the Soul Emperor could fully control the Emperor Bone Sea and complete his incomplete seclusion. Then, he would thoroughly fuse together with the world of the Demon God’s Tomb!

This was the final goal that he had plotted for 100 billion years – now, it would finally be realized!

Pata! Pata!

Sheng Mei’s blood dripped onto the black earth and was slowly absorbed. Meanwhile, the Soul Emperor reached out his other hand towards his own decrepit, firewood-like chest.

Puff!

He forcefully dug his claw into the pit of his chest. Pitch black blood, thick and viscous, slowly flowed out.

Even though his mortal body felt pain, the Soul Emperor didn’t seem to sense this at all. He continued to diabolically grin as he reached in to break off a rib and then pull it out!

Blood flowed out from the corners of the Soul Emperor’s lips and his eyes glowed with an increasingly strong death aura. If he wished to open the Eternal Wall and unravel the great array formation within, not only did he need Sheng Mei’s blood sacrifice but he also needed to pay a certain price.

The Soul Emperor crumbled his own rib. The half-foot long rib turned into shards of inch-long bone that resembled broken glass. The shards flew into the skies, forming a great array formation in the world.

World strength gathered, the flow becoming ever stronger.

“The grand feast has been prepared. Now, give me your life!”

The Soul Emperor reached out to grasp Sheng Mei. But at this time, from behind the Soul Emperor, light ripples appeared in the space behind him.

Although this was the most important ritual that the Soul Emperor had carried out in his life, his senses remained incredibly sharp. He immediately sensed these strange spatial fluctuations.

“Who is it?”

The Soul Emperor’s first thought was that someone wanted to sneak attack him and ruin his ritual.

In this critical point, if someone were to sneak attack him then although the Soul Emperor could deal with it, the event would still bring about many troubles and unknown variables. The Soul Emperor did not like unknown variables, particularly after his failed attempt to kill Lin Ming.

With spatial fluctuations, the greatest possibility was that someone would appear from a spatial channel and launch attacks against him.

The space on the surface of the Eternal Wall was inferior to the stability of the Demon God’s Tomb. But, because of the energy storm here, wanting to find accurate spatial coordinates and appear behind him wasn’t easy at all. This was proof that this new opponent was incredibly strong!

“No matter who you are, since you have appeared here, then die!”

The Soul Emperor stepped forwards, slamming his palm at that blurry space channel!

Kacha!

The space channel exploded. Beneath the Soul Emperor’s attack, no one would have escaped unscathed. Even an outstanding True Divinity like Lin Ming would have been wounded!

However, as this palm struck out, the Soul Emperor was left startled. The space channel was only a space channel; there was no one inside.

But if no one was inside, why would a space channel suddenly appear?

As these doubts flashed through the Soul Emperor’s mind, the power of turbulent space began to stir behind him once more. Another space channel had appeared!

The Soul Emperor turned and saw that the powerless Sheng Mei was being sucked towards that suddenly-produced space channel vortex!

“What!?”

The Soul Emperor was sent into a furious rage!

What angered him was that whether it was in training Sheng Mei or seizing her from the 33 Heavens, he had paid a great price in order to do this. Now, just as he was about to offer Sheng Mei in a blood sacrifice and complete the final necessary step, someone decided to use this key moment to save her.

And what was shocking was that he had locked his sense onto his surroundings all this time and had sensed no one. Just who had such great abilities that they could locate him and then open two space channels without him knowing, using one to divert his attention and then opening another beneath Sheng Mei’s feet to take her away!

“You are seeking death!”

The space channel was drawing in Sheng Mei at an incredible speed. However, the Soul Emperor’s reaction was even faster. He thrust out his palm, world strength surging around him!

In this moment the Soul Emperor could have killed Sheng Mei ten times over already. However, there were too many complex steps required in the blood sacrifice ritual, and if he didn’t complete then before killing Sheng Mei then that would cause all his plans to fail.

Thus, the Soul Emperor didn’t aim at Sheng Mei – his goal was the space channel.

Whoosh!

Sheng Mei was drawn into the space channel. But, as the space channel was attempting to close, the boundless world strength of the Soul Emperor blocked it from doing so, keeping it from closing!

“I want to take a good look at who has such great abilities!”

The Soul Emperor wanted to pursue Sheng Mei. He had branded her with his True Divinity mark and he could near-instantly reach her side.

However, just as he was about to enter the space channel, he felt a massive amount of pressure emerge from it!

This pressure squeezed out his world strength, wanting to crush it and forcibly close the space channel!

“What!?”

The Soul Emperor was bewildered. Someone existed who could resist his world strength!?

“No, this is wrong! This strength… comes from the Eternal Wall’s great array formation itself! Could the Eternal Wall be coming to save Sheng Mei? How is this possible?”

The Soul Emperor was left shocked. In this world, there was no one who possessed the ability to contend with him directly. However, the Eternal Wall was different. This was something which possessed an array formation that the Asura Road Master had poured his source energy into. In addition, Sheng Mei’s previous life had offered herself in a blood sacrifice, fusing all of her life essence and even pouring in the inherited strength that Immortal Sovereign had passed down to her. Moreover, the main body of the Eternal Wall was also one of the three divine tools – the Amethyst Origin Crystal.

With these three factors combined together, the Eternal Wall had a strength that even the Soul Emperor feared.

As he felt his own world strength being squeezed out, the Soul Emperor was enraged. He used his hands and forcefully grabbed at the edges of the space channel, wanting to tear it apart!

In his heart he knew that no matter what, he couldn’t allow this space channel to close.

He had already confirmed that this space channel originated from the inner space of the Eternal Wall. The Eternal Wall was a wholly complete self, and the Soul Emperor wasn’t sure why it would open a channel to suddenly rescue Sheng Mei.

However, he knew that once the channel opened, it was equal to tearing an opening within an originally complete wall.

With this opening, the Eternal Wall was no longer perfect.

As long as he could continue to rip open this tear then he could surely completely open it!

With this in mind, the Soul Emperor poured more and more strength into the space channel to resist the Eternal Wall’s pressure!

And at this time, within the space channel, Sheng Mei had arrived in a purple space.

“This place is…”

Sheng Mei was shocked. She thought her death was assured but the moment she was about to be turned into a blood sacrifice by the Soul Emperor she had been sucked into this space. And what stood in front of her was a little girl that seemed to be 13-14 years of age.

“You… saved me?”

Sheng Mei felt this all inconceivable. A little girl like this had the ability to save her?

She could not see through the little girl’s cultivation at all. This was strange, because she was sure that this little girl wasn’t too strong herself, so how could she possibly save her from the Soul Emperor?

“Who are you?”

Sheng Mei asked, puzzled. At the moment before her death, a little girl she had never seen before with such a low level of strength had managed to transmit her into this space; it was no different from a dream.

“I… my name is Yan Littlefish, you can call me Fishy. Do… do you know Big Brother Lin Ming?” Fishy timidly asked. When she listened in on the conversation between the Soul Emperor and Sheng Mei, she had heard the Soul Emperor mention Lin Ming’s name. It seemed as if this mysterious big sister had some sort of relationship with her big brother Lin Ming.

“Lin Ming… you called him your big brother?”

Sheng Mei was lost. A strange little girl had used completely inconceivable methods to rescue her and also knew of Lin Ming? Just who was this little girl and what was her background?

Chapter 2226 – Prelude to the Final Battle

“Fishy, how did you meet your Big Brother Lin Ming?” Sheng Mei asked Fishy.

Fishy related her experiences about how she met him in True Martial City, and also told Sheng Mei how she ended up here. When Mo Eversnow tried to cross into the Dark Abyss in the past, she had been sucked into this place.

From that point on she had stayed in here. She didn’t know how many years she had been here for but she slowly discovered that she had completely merged with the amethyst space around her. She was able to control this space, as if doing so was a part of her most natural instincts.

Fishy’s words startled Sheng Mei. She realized that this amethyst space was the inner space of the Eternal Wall. In other words, the inner space of the Amethyst Origin Crystal!

The little girl in front of her could control the Amethyst Origin Crystal. Just how was she related to the Amethyst Origin Crystal?

As Sheng Mei was left confused by all of this, she suddenly felt this amethyst space tremble around her.

The fierce trembling continued, leaving Sheng Mei and Fishy shaken. Immediately, a violent and evil strength came pouring down onto them.

Soul Emperor!

Sheng Mei’s complexion paled. Fishy opening and closing a space channel into the amethyst space had all been done in front of the Soul Emperor. Although the three divine tools were powerful, they were by no means invincible. Upon reaching the level of the Soul Emperor, one already possessed the ability to resist the strength of a great world.

As the amethyst space wished to seal itself again, the Soul Emperor poured his strength within to forcibly prevent it from doing so.

Not just that, but the Soul Emperor was trying to slowly rip open the space channel a bit at a time!

“This is bad!”

Sheng Mei’s heart sank. Once the Soul Emperor tore open the space channel and entered the amethyst space, the consequences would be inconceivable!

The Soul Emperor continued to pour in his strength, becoming increasingly formidable. But, his actions also aroused the resistance of the Eternal Wall.

Sheng Mei sensed that the Eternal Wall’s energy started to gather from all around; it wanted to push out the Soul Emperor’s energy!

In a moment, both sides reached a mutual balance, neither side able to take an advantage.

However, Sheng Mei was increasingly worried as she saw this.

It had to be known that the energy of a great array formation tended to be self-circulating and insulated. Although it could absorb energy from the outside, in normal situations the energy it absorbed was only sufficient to continue revolving the array formation.

For a grand array formation to achieve perfect energy balance, this was a splendidly amazing array formation. Such an array formation could continue for billions of years without fear of lacking energy.

The Eternal Wall was one such grand array formation. It had a balanced level of energy and even had a little bit extra. In addition to a divine tool as its foundation, this grand array formation could stand tall for 10 billion years without breaking.

But no matter how perfect a grand array formation was, once a flaw appeared then it was no longer perfect. It was like a bag of air with a small hole stabbed in it, slowly deflating.

Time passed, a minute and a second at a time. The energy within the Eternal Wall was like a vast sea smashing forwards again and again. However, the Soul Emperor’s evil energy within the space channel was incomparably tenacious and refused to disappear.

This process continued for many days. The Soul Emperor’s energy was slowly compressed into an energy mark within the amethyst space. At this time the space channel finally sealed itself back up.

The amethyst space fell quiet once more, its calm restored.

However, Sheng Mei didn’t feel any joy at all. She could faintly feel that the Soul Emperor’s energy mark had already melted into the Eternal Wall’s grand array formation, and was blending into its energy structure.

It was like a malignant tumor, slowly absorbing energy and growing stronger.

The Soul Emperor had finally found a breaking point through the Eternal Wall!

The Eternal Wall had already existed for 10 billion years. The Soul Emperor had studied it for an incredibly long period of time and likely understood the energy structure behind it.

An array formation was inanimate but the Soul Emperor was alive. Sooner or later, the Eternal Wall would be broken through by him.

But the Soul Emperor didn’t want to wait. What he needed was one final straw to crush the camel’s back.

His original choice had been Sheng Mei. Even though his plan had failed… the result would not change.

In the past, when the Asura Road Master and Sheng Mei’s previous life laid down the Eternal Wall, they had already expected that it would be impossible for this Eternal Wall to block the steps of the abyssal race for eternity. There would come a day when the Eternal Wall was torn down and the 33 Heavens would face the invasion of the Dark Abyss once more.

This was the destined flow of history. Although it might be delayed or hastened by one or two accidental events, the final result would still move towards an established direction.

It was an accident that Fishy rescued Sheng Mei, and it was this accident that allowed the Soul Emperor to plant a seed within the Eternal Wall.

With a flaw in the Eternal Wall, it was no longer indestructible.

This was just like an adult male being unable to crush a complete egg in his hand. But once there was a crack in this egg, even if it were a small crack that one couldn’t even see, then the integrity of the egg would be compromised and even a small child could crush it then.

“Fishy…”

Sheng Mei looked at Fishy, her gaze filled with guilt. Fishy had rescued her, yet all she brought to Fishy was nothing but bad luck.

………….

Asura Road, Amethyst Heavenly Palace.

Lin Ming sat in meditation for several days within this space. His injuries had already healed by a great deal. Normally, when a martial artist overdraw their life force like Lin Ming did then they would have already dropped boundaries. Yet, Lin Ming actually didn’t suffer many losses. This terrifying resilience and regenerative ability was all thanks to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

In his battle with the Soul Emperor, it was unavoidable for his cultivation to be reduced. But in the final moments, he had fused together his inner and outer universes, becoming one with the heavens. He had made great strides in his Laws, and these harvests surpassed the losses to his blood vitality and cultivation.

During these days, Lin Ming worried over Sheng Mei. He had a faint spiritual connection with her and could sense that she had yet to die…

Lin Ming didn’t know what was occurring but he was left impatient and anxious. But he also knew that trying to rescue Sheng Mei in his current state was impossible.

“Lin Ming, I can feel the Amethyst Origin Crystal’s energy weakening… the Demon God’s Tomb Master should be attempting to break through the Eternal Wall… your wife has not died, but as for what happened specifically, I do now know…”

Asura’s voice suddenly echoed in the void.

“Senior, what should this junior do?”

Lin Ming knew that once the Eternal Wall opened, then the Soul Emperor, Deep, and Flood, would fuse together as one, perhaps even finally thoroughly refining the Demon God’s Tomb. At this time, it was unimaginable how strong the Demon God’s Tomb Master would become.

That moment would be the apocalypse for all life in the 33 Heavens.

The Asura Road Master fell silent for a long time. Then, he slowly said, “It is time to start the arrangements that I’ve planned for all these years. It is only that the day came far sooner than I thought it would…”

“The arrangements you’ve planned in these years?” Lin Ming asked, stunned.

“10 billion years ago when I and the previous life of Sheng Mei joined together to lay down the Eternal Wall, I had already been considering this day.

“My Asura Road and Immortal’s Akashic Dream Universe had both been prepared for this day… I split apart my body, divine soul, and inner world, and fused together with the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe, and the reason I did all of this was in order to protect these two lands.

“For all these years, under my protection, the Demon God’s Tomb Master was not able to destroy the Asura Road or Akashic Dream Universe. But at the same time, I was also unable to prevent the Demon God’s Tomb Master from slowly restoring his strength. All I could do was quietly wait…”

Listening to the Asura Road Master’s words, Lin Ming was left stunned.

Asura Road, Akashic Dream Universe…

When Lin Ming first stepped into the Asura Road, he had already been speculating about the reasons for why the Asura Road Master had spent so much effort and energy to create the Asura Road. If this great world was merely created so that the Asura Road Master could choose his descendants, then it seemed a little bit overdone.

This world formed a complete system and there were also many unique Laws that existed here. There were guardians that tended to this world as well as the final trial that was wrapped in mysteries. All of these things were planned so that the Asura Road Master could resist the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s schemes?

As for the Akashic Dream Universe, Lin Ming had once entered that place too. He knew that after the Demon God’s Tomb Master had seized the body of the Soul Emperor, he had slowly obtained the complete Holy Scripture from the Akashic Dream universe.

This was also an inevitable matter. After all, for the last 10 billion years, all parts of the Holy Scripture had been slowly searched for and collected by spiritas martial artists. With the Soul Emperor’s time and energy, it wouldn’t be difficult for him to piece together the complete Holy Scripture.

But Lin Ming also knew that many trials in the Akashic Dream Universe had corresponding rewards that were various golden pages of the Holy Scripture. But when he went into the Akashic Dream Universe, many of these golden pages had yet to be taken by others.

When Lin Ming had learned of the Soul Emperor’s true identity and his plans, he had also been left a bit puzzled. With the Soul Emperor’s absolute strength, it shouldn’t have been difficult for him to forcibly seize these golden pages. But now he understood that all of this was prevented by the protection of the Asura Road Master.

10 billion years ago, the two peerless characters of the past had created two great worlds in order to resist the Demon God’s Tomb!

Of the two of them, one had perished with nothing left but a remnant soul. Even then, he had waited in silence within the Emperor Bone Sea to give the Soul Emperor one final heavy strike. As for the other person, he still lived and had been quietly protecting these two great worlds for 10 billion years, waiting for the final battle to arrive!

Lin Ming’s heart was shaken beyond words. He didn’t know what he could say or what expressions he could make to describe what Immortal and Asura had done. All he could do was inherit their legacies and face this final great calamity.

Chapter 2228 – The Times Change

Time passed. At the entrance of the Dark Abyss, Sheng Mei and Fishy had stayed together in the Amethyst Origin Crystal’s inner space for 30 years already.

Every now and then during these 30 years, Sheng Mei could feel energy passing from the Eternal Wall.

After the Soul Emperor left his energy within the Eternal Wall’s inner energy structure, it took root and began to germinate, tenaciously growing.

Sheng Mei didn’t know what method the Soul Emperor used, but the energy mark he planted actually wasn’t able to be recognized by the Eternal Wall. It grew like a malignant cancer, spreading outwards. If this continued then a small part of the Eternal Wall’s energy structure would fall under the control of the Soul Emperor. At that time, by joining forces within and without, the Eternal Wall would sooner or later fall.

After another five years, the Soul Emperor’s energy mark exploded for the first time.

This matter occurred suddenly and without any hint at all. At the time, Sheng Mei was closed up in cultivation and Fishy was lackadaisically eating the energy crystals condensed in the amethyst space. But then, a sudden shaking within the amethyst space caused Sheng Mei to awaken from her meditation. These vibrations were far more violent than when the Soul Emperor first attempted to tear open the space channel.

Sheng Mei blanched. She reached out her sense to probe the Eternal Wall’s situation, and her complexion became increasingly solemn.

During these years, Sheng Mei had managed to slowly flush out the various seals that the Soul Emperor had placed within her. After all, most of these seals only had short term effects, and with her strength she could always push them out of her body as long as she slowly erased them with her energy.

Now her strength had been restored to its peak state and she could clearly feel the internal state of the Eternal Wall’s grand array formation.

The Soul Emperor had allowed his energy mark to grow for 30 years. What the Soul Emperor should have done just now was lay down a great array formation outside, and combined with this energy to explode it, blowing up a part of the Eternal Wall’s energy structure.

After the explosion, there was still a part of the Soul Emperor’s energy left within that would survive in the Eternal Wall’s array formation. This should be an attempt by the Soul Emperor to study the energy he left behind and how he could use it to completely break open the Eternal Wall.

“Fishy, the Eternal Wall cannot stop the Soul Emperor. He has studied the Eternal Wall for innumerable years, and now because of me, a flaw has appeared in this originally perfect wall. At the least we have a thousand years and at the most we have several thousand years, but the Eternal Wall will most certainly be shattered open by the Soul Emperor…”

Sheng Mei sighed. Even with Fishy’s sudden appearance she still wasn’t able to change her fate.

Fishy tilted her head, unsure of what to do. For these past 30 years, the two of them had spent their time within the Amethyst Origin Crystal together and they had extremely good sentiments towards each other. Since Fishy couldn’t figure out what to do, she simply held Sheng Mei’s hand to comfort her.

Holding Fishy’s hand, Sheng Mei wasn’t sure what she felt in her heart. She gently traced Fishy’s cheek and said with sadness, “Fishy, you tried to rescue big sister, but big sister only managed to drag you into this mess.”

Fishy grabbed Sheng Mei’s hand, saying, “It’s fine. Didn’t Big Sister say that we have several thousand years left? Perhaps there is still something we can do. If Big Sister can make another breakthrough, then we might be able to escape. And even if all our efforts come to nothing, that doesn’t matter anyways.”

Fishy earnestly said.

“Breakthrough…” Sheng Mei shook her head. In the Asura forbidden land she had fused with the remnant soul of her past life and had awakened the majority of her past memories. With it, she obtained many precious experiences, Laws, and cultivation methods.

These comprehensions and experiences needed time to be digested. If she were to go into seclusion for several thousand years then her strength would surely rise up to a whole new level.

If there wasn’t an accident, she could easily reach the peak of middle True Divinity and even the upper True Divinity boundary.

Even so, she wouldn’t be a match for the Soul Emperor. The Soul Emperor was simply too formidable; he was absolutely invincible amongst True Divinities!

“Fishy, are you afraid of dying?” Sheng Mei softly asked, looking into Fishy’s eyes.

Fishy shook her head. In truth, she had already lived for a long, long time, and there were many matters she couldn’t remember from her glorious past. She didn’t fear death; what she feared was loneliness and slowly forgetting the past.

“Mm… then listen to big sister. From this point on, big sister will go into seclusion to try and break through to the next boundary. As for you, you can begin saving your energy so that the Amethyst Origin Crystal is in its most powerful state.

“The Soul Emperor still needs a long period of time before he can open the Eternal Wall; we will have enough time to make preparations. And when the Soul Emperor opens the Eternal Wall, the truth is that this will be the Soul Emperor’s weakest moment.”

Sheng Mei knew that two of the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s avatars, Deep and Flood, should be staying in the Emperor Bone Sea to suppress the changes that were occurring there. Thus, they shouldn’t be facing them.

As long as she faced the Soul Emperor alone then she was fine.

If the Soul Emperor was in his peak state, Sheng Mei was naturally far from being his match. But the moment that the Eternal Wall broke open, the Soul Emperor would surely have consumed a tremendous amount of energy.

When the Soul Emperor tried to open the Eternal Wall in the past, he had captured her as a blood sacrifice. And when he was carrying out the final ritual, he had dug out one of his ribs, combining his bone’s blood essence with the array formation he laid down to complete the last steps.

Now the Soul Emperor didn’t have Sheng Mei to use as a blood sacrifice and could only depend on the energy mark that he had planted in the Amethyst Origin Crystal. If he wanted to open the Eternal Wall using that then he might need to pay an even greater price.

If so, then this would be her only chance!

She would nurture her strength while biding her time. When she reached the peak of middle True Divinity, she would face the exhausted Soul Emperor and even have Fishy and the Amethyst Origin Crystal supporting her.

With the Amethyst Origin Crystal, she could give the Soul Emperor a disastrous blow!

This was Sheng Mei’s plan. But, she also knew that the chances of her plan succeeding were near zero.

But no matter how unlikely her chances were, she still had to attempt it and put forth her full effort in doing so!

Because this was her last chance!

Although she might not be able to avoid her own death in the end, before she died she would tear off a chunk of meat from the Soul Emperor and heavily wound him once more. She might be able to delay his fusion with the Demon God’s Tomb and give Lin Ming and Jiu’er a long period of time to grow stronger.

………..

Time flew forwards like an arrow, ruthless shooting towards one direction. Sometimes it was fast, sometimes it was slow, but it would never turn back.

Within the Asura Sea’s Amethyst Heavenly Palace, the flow of time was sped up.

One year outside was equivalent to ten years within the Amethyst Heavenly Palace.

Upon reaching the boundary of the Asura Road Master, one could definitely create a perfect time enchantment where the Laws within weren’t twisted and was still suitable for cultivating. Tragic Death Valley was one such example.

However, this increased pace of time didn’t work for everything.

Lin Ming’s cultivation of his reincarnations, his breakthrough in the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, these things could be done within a time enchantment.

But to simultaneously refine the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe, this could not.

This was because fusing together the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe required a height of Laws that even surpassed the comprehensions of the Asura Road Master. In this situation, if the Asura Road Master wished to create a time enchantment and have its Laws continue in their originally perfect and complete state, that was just impossible.

Thus, when the time truly came for Lin Ming to refine the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe, time would pass at an equal speed to the outside world.

He would be placed in a race against time with the Soul Emperor!

At this time, in the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming had already experienced 5000 years. But only 500 years passed in the outside world.

For these 500 years, the human Empyreans and True Divinities did not idly waste their time away.

They had established a new base in the skies above the Asura Sea.

All important figures of humanity had moved to the Asura Sea. The outstanding individuals amongst them were able to enter the final trial.

The end times were approaching. Ink and Clear opened up all resources within the Asura Road’s final trial, and how much one could obtain would depend on their respective abilities.

Afterwards, even the elites of the saints came to the Asura Sea.

Beneath the guidance of the current leader of the saints, Soaring Feather God King, many saint influences began to establish themselves in the Asura Sea. They created large array formations, opened their own minor worlds and brought in their Heavenly Palaces.

The geniuses of the saints – Fairy Blue Lotus, Highsun, Darkmoon, all entered the final trial to seek out their own lucky chances.

Everyone who entered the final trial was able to obtain their own corresponding completion percentage. These geniuses were all incredible individuals that possessed their own pride and arrogance. In particular, with two races living together, they all chased towards the highest completion percentage, pushing each other further up through competition.

Slowly, the Asura Sea became the core focal point of the children of the 33 Heavens. However, the humans and saints knew that these prosperous times couldn’t continue forever. Probably in 10,000 years or less, the great calamity would arrive.

Whether or not they could continue onwards or be annihilated here, everything would depend on the man deep in seclusion within the Amethyst Heavenly Palace.

He was the final bet of the 33 Heavens. And what he faced was a gamble he could not afford to lose.

Chapter 2230 – Changes

The truth was that 10,000 years ago before the great catastrophe arrived, whether it was humans or saints, they slacked on their cultivation after reaching the Empyrean realm.

The first reason was because the Empyrean realm was far too distant from the True Divinity realm. Even if they cultivated diligently their efforts were likely to come to nothing.

The second reason was because their resources and inheritances were lacking. 10 billion years ago when the martial arts civilization of the 33 Heavens was at its most glorious and prosperous times, it was far less difficult for an Empyrean to reach True Divinity, and many True Divinity influences would help those with potential complete this final step as long as they put in their due diligence.

But afterwards, when the various races of the 33 Heavens fell into steep decline, the total number of True Divinities within the 33 Heavens could be counted on two hands and this was divided amongst the different races. In this situation, if an Empyrean wished to cultivate to True Divinity they would basically have to rely on themselves, and no matter how much effort they put in, their work wouldn’t come to fruition.

But the present was different. Around the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, there was the personal teachings of Ink and Clear. Moreover, in these past years all of the Asura Road Master’s accumulated resources, everything that the previous guardians of the Asura Road had collected, it was all taken out without reserve for the many Empyreans and True Divinities to use.

There was no need to speak of cultivation method inheritances. Not to mention the vast accumulation of inheritances gathered in the Asura Road, the various human and saint influences also put forth their own inheritances so that everyone could share and exchange.

Inheritances were indeed precious, if one’s race didn’t even exist, what was the point of defending these inheritances so fastidiously?

With all of these factors added together, the martial artists of humanity and the saints began to cultivate with an unprecedented level of heated enthusiasm. Naturally, their cultivation speed also rose by a great deal. There were even some outstanding individuals who had high hopes of breaking into True Divinity.

This was the True Divinity boundary! Once, it had been nothing but a wistful dream that that could only look on from afar, but now that they realized they could break through these shackles and attain it themselves, how could they not be excited?

As the human and saint race Empyreans put forth their full hearts and minds into cultivation, Jiu’er had already ridden the great Black Dragon into the skies above the Great Desolate.

Jiu’er held onto the Black Dragon’s neck. Facing the howling desert winds, her long black hair flew about her like strands of silk.

The blood red glow from the sun covered her skin like an intoxicating blush. But beneath that blush, her delicate face was filled with a grim and hardened determination.

“Little Black, fly into the deeps!” Jiu’er shouted out loud.

Ao - !

The Black Dragon roared. Its two wings stretched out as it cut through the skyline. One girl, one dragon, the two of them soared through the fire-red clouds, slowly blending into the crimson setting sun and disappearing from sight. All that was left over was the distant howl of the dragon, echoing into the horizon for a long time.

………

Time passed, marching forwards without pause.

Ever since Lin Ming began his seclusion, 2800 years had passed. No one knew what Lin Ming’s situation was but they didn’t dare to waste time in their cultivation.

And at this time, a great change was occurring within the spiritas. Overnight, the entire spiritas race descended into chaos. Two spiritas True Divinities led ten peak Empyreans to go to the Dark Abyss.

As this news spread out, the human and saint martial artists felt their hearts sink.

In the past the leader of the spiritas had his body seized. Then, the Demon God’s Tomb Master appeared with the identity of the Soul Emperor to rule over the spiritas. The several strongest masters of the spiritas race were controlled by the Soul Emperor, and if it wasn’t for the Soul Emperor being limited in the number of people that he could control, then he likely would have taken control of every Empyrean amongst the spiritas.

The changes occurring amongst the spiritas left a dark cloud of gloom hovering over their hearts. This was especially true for the spiritas martial artists. For instance… Empyrean Divine Mist.

Empyrean Divine Mist had awoken around the time that Lin Ming went into seclusion. Then, he began restoring his soul around the Heavenly Amethyst Palace and now his soul had become increasingly stable. He came from the Asura Road but when he learned of the changes occurring within the spiritas of the 33 Heavens, he still sighed deeply with emotion. In these chaotic times, what would the future of the spiritas be?

“Divine Mist, in these past years your soul has become stable enough with the aid of appropriate soul recovery items. At the time, Young Master had instructed us that after your soul has stabilized, we should give you an appropriate body and also help you seize it!”

After Lin Ming went into seclusion to refine two great worlds, Ink and Clear had already changed the way they called Lin Ming to Young Master.

Empyrean Divine Mist had shown graciousness to Lin Ming in the past. And since it was impossible for Lin Ming to reform Divine Mist’s mortal body, he could only help him seize a similar one.

After seizing a body there would be many drawbacks, but it was still much better than remaining a soul form.

“You have two choices. One is Soul Emperor Divine Void! And the other is the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!”

Ink and Clear’s words caused Empyrean Divine Mist’s heart to shake. These two bodies were both at the True Divinity level, in particular the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign – he had reached the peak of True Divinity!

Soul Emperor Divine Void was Divine Mist’s enemy. A hundred years ago, Ink and Clear had captured Soul Emperor Divine Void and had sealed up his spiritual sea and cultivation.

As for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, there was even less to mention. After his great battle with Lin Ming he had suffered severe losses and also had his avatar of Famine and Grandmist Spirit Bead taken away. His cultivation boundary had dropped one level, and after being controlled by the Asura Road Master, his cultivation dropped even further. Now, he was somewhere between an upper and middle True Divinity.

Originally it would have been impossible for Divine Mist to seize the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body. But, because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s soul had been controlled, it was not possible for Divine Mist to slowly refine the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spiritual sea.

After listening to Ink and Clear’s words, Divine Mist sighed. He said, “I will choose to seize the body of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign… as for Divine Void, let him go…”

After so many years passed, the hatred in Divine Mist’s heart had already faded away, becoming a shadow of what it had been.

With the great calamity imminent, Divine Mist didn’t want to sentence a master who was on the side of the 33 Heavens to death, just because of some past enmity. In fact, this was also hard for Ink and Clear.

“Good!” Ink and Clear faintly smiled. “Then we will assist you in seizing the body. After you seize his body it will require you a great deal of time to thoroughly refine the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s divine soul. Even when you manage to do so, it will be impossible to further increase your boundary in the future. Do you understand all of this?”

“Mm.” Divine Mist calmly said. To be able to obtain a mortal body and also one that was so formidable, he no longer had any wild dreams. If it weren’t for him luckily meeting Lin Ming in the past within Tragic Death Valley, he feared he would have long since exhausted himself and died.

…………

Three years later, some spiritas martial artists also arrived at the Asura Sea.

Ink and Clear welcomed all of these new arrivals.

Slowly, three thousand years passed from when Lin Ming entered seclusion. From this point on, beneath the planning of Ink and Clear, the mortals and low level martial artists of the Asura Road began to evacuate.

Everything was being done in preparation for the final war that would occur once Lin Ming left seclusion. And in the Dark Abyss, Sheng Mei and Fishy were also preparing for their final stand.

Three thousand years ago the Eternal Wall had already started to break apart. Horrifying cracks appeared in the boundless black earth. These cracks were like the maws of wild beasts, capable of swallowing everything into the endless abyss.

The Soul Emperor stood above the devastated and cracked earth, his hair scattered and his filthy eyes overflowing with killing intent…

Chapter 2232 – A Different World

One’s fighting spirit was aroused by the first call, faded by the second, and then exhausted by the third. If the first strike wasn’t able to heavily wound the Soul Emperor then the following battle would become far more difficult!

“You have really left me surprised…”

In the distant void, the Soul Emperor’s hair was scattered all about him. A macabre smile spread across his features. In these years of seclusion Sheng Mei’s strength had risen by an astronomical degree. In addition to Fishy and the Purple Card, when they gathered all of their potential to attack together, even though the Soul Emperor was prepared he had still been injured.

The arm he used to block the Purple Card had already broken and was now hanging limp at a strange angle. But although the Soul Emperor had been wounded, a happy expression spread wildly across his face.

“I expected you to take advantage of my weakest moment to risk your life in a desperate attack, but I didn’t expect your strike to be so powerful. You have progressed far too quickly. In the past I only wanted to train you to open the Eternal Wall, but I never imagined I would create such a perfect work of art. If you didn’t betray me, just how wonderful would that have been?”

The Soul Emperor’s voice overflowed with killing intent. Although he thought it was a pity that he would have to destroy Sheng Mei, he didn’t have any intention of showing mercy or forgiveness.

And, ruining the most perfect thing could also bring him pleasure.

Ka ka ka!

The Soul Emperor’s broken arm was rapidly regenerating.

At the same time, beneath the Soul Emperor, the Eternal Wall continued to break down and explode. Violent flows of energy smashed into his body, but the Soul Emperor seemed mindless of it all. His gaze and sense were still completely locked onto the Amethyst Origin Crystal that was not too far away. He knew that Sheng Mei still had strength remaining and wouldn’t give up here; she would continue attacking.

But her attacks wouldn’t have any great effect on him.

This was the disparity between their boundaries.

The Soul Emperor moved towards the Amethyst Origin Crystal, one step at a time. With the Soul Emperor as the center, a force field projection of the Demon God’s Tomb shot out, blocking the surrounding void.

Bang!

The explosions all around the Soul Emperor became increasingly fierce and crazy. Beneath his feet, the Eternal Wall was falling downwards. Without the support of the force field, the dark earth collapsed beneath its own weight. It began to fall into the Dark Abyss in massive chunks. This apocalyptic sight was as if the end of times had come!

A terrifying energy erupted from the Eternal Wall. Originally, the Eternal Wall was linked together with the void. And now because the Eternal Wall had collapsed, a massive chunk of space was torn apart and an unexpected scene occurred.

A spatial fissure over a thousand miles long appeared after the space tore. And within this spatial fissure, the aura of the world was hazy and ethereal, as if… it were a completely different world.

“Mm?”

Seeing this massive spatial fissure, the Soul Emperor was stunned.

This is…

This world was clearly different from the world of the Demon God’s Tomb, and the Soul Emperor also felt that this wasn’t the 33 Heavens.

Such a world was hiding within the Dark Abyss? How could this be possible?

But at the same time, as Sheng Mei saw this within the amethyst space, tumultuous waves rose up in her heart.

She had seen this piece of world before!

She didn’t know what this world was or where it had come from. But over 10,000 years ago, she had discovered the entrance to this world by accident.

Within this world, all rules were different. These rules seemed completely independent from the system that constituted the 33 Heavens and Dark Abyss.

In truth, the Dark Abyss and 33 Heavens came from the same roots. The Dark Abyss was the predecessor of the 33 Heavens, the remains of the previous universal era. From this aspect, the two worlds were originally one body.

But this other world was actually completely different!

Sheng Mei didn’t know why the entrance to such a world would appear in the Dark Abyss nor did she know what it was. After she accidentally discovered this world, she hid away this secret.

This world’s mysterious Laws caused Sheng Mei to have a foreboding feeling the first time she saw it.

That was… she felt that the entrance to this world only went one way, and after leaving to enter this world, there was no coming back.

Sheng Mei’s original plan was to use this world as her escape route. If her contradictions with the Soul Emperor truly rose to an irreconcilable level, then she would simply leave. At that time, Sheng Mei hadn’t known of her dark and dire fate, nor did she know what the Soul Emperor was planning to do with her. Although she and the Soul Emperor were like water and fire, that wasn’t a good enough reason for her to flee to a different world which she wouldn’t be able to return from.

But afterwards, Sheng Mei discovered that the entrance to this world was slowly closing. It wouldn’t be long before it completely disappeared…

Thus, she mentioned this world to someone, and that person was… Lin Ming!

12,000 years ago, Lin Ming was at the Holy Lord realm. He had just defeated the Good Fortune Saint Son and humanity would soon face a great war with the saints.

In order to save humanity, Lin Ming ventured out in all directions in search of all possibilities. He even held onto the faintest glimmer of hope that he could come to the Soul World to look for Sheng Mei and negotiate with her. If possible, humanity could ally with the spiritas to deal with a ‘common enemy’ in the saints.

At that time, Sheng Mei already knew the truth that the Soul Emperor was an abyssal. In her eyes, humanity’s war with the saints was basically meaningless, and even weak. And as she saw Lin Ming toiling so hard for a race that didn’t have any ability to resist the great calamity they were about to suffer, she simply sighed. She sympathized greatly with Lin Ming and even felt… pity.

Lin Ming asked why Sheng Mei sighed, and her reply was – “Sighing for your destiny.”

Lin Ming was puzzled. However, Sheng Mei didn’t fully explain anything to him. Instead, she simply asked him whether or not he wanted to follow her to some place. They wouldn’t go to the Divine Realm nor would they go to the Soul World. Once they left, they would go for a hundred million years!

The so-called hundred million years was in truth a lifetime. They would go far away from the great vortex of the great calamity, leaving everything behind so that they could pursue the road of martial arts with all their hearts.

At that time, Sheng Mei still had her own ambitions. She hoped that one day she would be able to step Beyond Divinity and create her own world.

She thought that Lin Ming was a suitable companion as he had enough talent to grow to such heights. If they could cultivate to the peak of martial arts together then they could imitate the Immortal Sovereign and his wife from 10 billion years ago, stepping Beyond Divinity together.

Moreover, once they went to that mysterious world that was about to be sealed up, they could rid themselves of the Soul Emperor’s control just like that, completing everything in a single swoop!

Of course, going to a completely unknown world already meant tremendous risks. These risks didn’t come from the original dangers of that world, but whether or not that world was suitable for them to cultivate.

But, when Sheng Mei asked Lin Ming, his reply had actually been…

Refusal.

Sheng Mei wasn’t surprised. She believed that her and Lin Ming’s fate would end there, and if they met in the future it would only be as enemies.

She never thought that all sorts of things would happen between her and Lin Ming in the future, and the two of them would even have a daughter…

Life was like a dream and perhaps fate was already an established road. But for those that continued to look forwards into the future, everything still seemed too inconceivable and incredible…

All of these thoughts instantly flashed through Sheng Mei’s mind. In the next moment, she instantly sent Fishy a sound transmission.

“We’re rushing over! Give everything we have and fly into that world!”

Chapter 2233 – The Soul Emperor Returns

Hearing Sheng Mei’s shout in her ears, Fishy didn’t hesitate. She immediately poured the entirety of her strength into the Amethyst Origin Crystal.

Chi - !

The Amethyst Origin Crystal flared up with a blazing divine light; it flew straight towards that other world.

The Soul Emperor’s eyes flashed with a cold light. Just now he had been immersed in surprise at the appearance of such a mysterious world. Why would such a strange world be in the Dark Abyss? But as he saw Sheng Mei about to escape, how could he allow them to do as they wished?

Bang!

The Soul Emperor’s world strength transformed into a giant black hand that grasped towards the Amethyst Origin Crystal!

At this time, Sheng Mei was already in desperate straits, recklessly pushing forwards. This was her last chance!

To defeat the Soul Emperor in a frontal battle was naturally impossible, and trying to flee from his grasp was also a mission with innumerable difficulties and risks. But, if it were only to fly into a space crack that was 10,000 feet away, that was far easier.

“Hold!”

The Soul Emperor’s palm thrust outwards. All around him, the Demon God’s Tomb force field tightened up. The black hand grasped onto the Amethyst Origin Crystal!

The energy collision caused the Amethyst Origin Crystal to wildly tremble. The impact force that spread through caused Sheng Mei to shake and spit out a mouthful of blood.

However at this moment, she didn’t care about this at all. Disregarding all consequences, she overdrew her blood vitality, overdrew her life, and continued to hurtle towards the entrance to that other world!

Chi chi chi!

The Amethyst Origin Crystal began to spin. Its edges were as sharp as knives as it split open the black hand of world strength created by the Soul Emperor.

Although the Soul Emperor’s world strength was formidable, the Amethyst Origin Crystal was actually the ultimate nemesis for all forms of energy. At this time, the Amethyst Origin Crystal was cutting through that black hand with unstoppable force!

“What!?”

The Soul Emperor was shocked. He disregarded his exhaustion and consumed a massive amount of world strength to send a palm reaching out for the Amethyst Origin Crystal, but this attack was still cut apart. It was like the Amethyst Origin Crystal was a heated blade of iron and his attack was a chunk of fat, directly pierced through, impossible to block!

Whoosh!

The Amethyst Origin Crystal sank into the entrance to that different world. It rapidly flew into the space storms that roiled within and vanished from sight.

The Soul Emperor was stunned. He thought that the might of the Amethyst Origin Crystal had slightly exceeded his expectations.

10 billion years ago, the Soul Emperor had fought with the Asura Road Master and had encountered the Amethyst Origin Crystal. At that time, the Amethyst Origin Crystal hadn’t seemed too terrifying.

Was it possible that in the 10 billion years that the Amethyst Origin Crystal had been the incarnation of the Eternal Wall, there had been some sort of change to it due to the massive accumulation of energy?

Or, could it be that 10 billion years ago when the past life of Sheng Mei sacrificed herself and poured her strength into the Amethyst Origin Crystal, her actions had served as a catalyst to hasten this change?

All sorts of theories passed through the Soul Emperor’s heart. He could feel that the Amethyst Origin Crystal had likely evolved somehow. If Sheng Mei hid in the Amethyst Origin Crystal and tried to flee with all her might, it would indeed not be easy to keep her here.

If it were the Dark Abyss then he would have a much greater assurance. But in this different world…

The Soul Emperor looked at that gradually shrinking entrance that seemed as if it would soon disappear. He hesitated for a moment and finally chose not to chase after them…

This different world caused the Soul Emperor to feel particularly strange. The space storms within were far fiercer than those in the Dark Abyss and the entrance seemed as if it would vanish at any time. Going to this different world would be easy, but to capture Sheng Mei and return safely before the entrance vanished might not be possible.

The Soul Emperor estimated that if he wanted to capture Sheng Mei he would need to expend a considerable amount of effort. If things went smoothly it would take an hour, and if things didn’t go smoothly then no one knew how long it would take.

If he were to enter this different world and the entrance vanished before he captured Sheng Mei, then could he return?

The Soul Emperor wasn’t confident he could do this.

Whether it was the 33 Heavens or Dark Abyss, the Soul Emperor was fully confident he could freely wander about as he wished. But to go into a completely different world that had never been discovered before, there were just too many uncertainties involved. He might lose track of the space coordinates in this different world and be unable to find his way back.

“I never thought that something like this would occur… it seems that the heavens haven’t yet abandoned you…” The Soul Emperor took a deep breath. Although he was filled with unwillingness, he decided to give up his pursuit of Sheng Mei.

The appearance of this different world should have happened because of the shattering the Eternal Wall. The energy that had accumulated for 10 billion years erupted all at once, piercing through space and making this entrance visible.

However, the Soul Emperor thought that this might be Sheng Mei’s destiny. If fate truly existed, then with Sheng Mei’s destiny her life shouldn’t come to an end.

In this situation where he had to go to a completely unknown different world to chase down Sheng Mei who had such a great destiny upon her, this wouldn’t be the wise action to take, especially since the Soul Emperor had so many other matters to attend to.

Slowly, that giant space fissure that spread out for over a thousand miles shrank to several miles in length. Then, after a mere 10 breaths of time, it completely vanished.

From beginning to end, Sheng Mei and the Amethyst Origin Crystal didn’t reappear.

The Soul Emperor sensed that after the entrance to this different world was sealed up, it wouldn’t be easy for Sheng Mei to return. She might be forever trapped in this different world.

Although his heart was filled with simmering resentment, he didn’t delay any further. He flew directly into the depths of the Dark Abyss.

Besides the Soul Emperor, his other two avatars were still in the Dark Abyss. Now that the Eternal Wall had disappeared after so many years of effort, he had to take advantage of this time to fuse together with the Demon God’s Tomb and also deal with the nearly collapsed Emperor Bone Sea. With so many matters to deal with, he couldn’t afford to delay!

Just the Eternal Wall had taken him 3000 years to deal with. This was equal to allowing Lin Ming to grow for another 3000 years!

In addition to the Soul Emperor’s future seclusion, everything might add up to over 10,000 years. The Soul Emperor didn’t know what heights Lin Ming had grown to, but he knew that he absolutely could not allow Lin Ming to continue growing.

Every year that the Soul Emperor was delayed meant that Lin Ming would grow that much stronger. In the Soul Emperor’s mind, the danger that Lin Ming represented was far greater than the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign from 10 billion years past.

When Asura and Immortal encountered the Soul Emperor, they had already cultivated for countless years. They were existences that could be described as old monsters.

Their ages were too great. Even though they were strong, their potential had shrunk to almost nothing. The Soul Emperor wasn’t afraid of them because of this. Whether it was Asura or Immortal, the Soul Emperor could allow them to freely cultivate as they wished without any worries.

But Lin Ming was different. He had only cultivated for a small number of years. Compared to Asura and Immortal, this time period was simply negligible.

But in such a short period of time he managed to attain a True Divinity level cultivation and have strength equal to a peak True Divinity master. Moreover, he still managed to make another breakthrough. He could be said to have reached the limits of True Divinity.

In just 10,000 some years, with an initial True Divinity cultivation, Lin Ming possessed strength at the limits of True Divinity. This was something that the Soul Emperor could hardly believe. 10 billion years ago, whether it was Asura or Immortal, neither of them had managed to reach such heights.

If the Soul Emperor were to allow such an enemy to freely grow then this enemy would surely surpass Asura and Immortal in the future, perhaps even surpassing himself.

Sooner or later, this enemy would send him to hell.

The Soul Emperor naturally had to prevent such things occurring.

The Soul Emperor quickly flew deep into the depths of the Dark Abyss.

At the same time, in the 17th level of the Dark Abyss, in Deep King Road Demon Palace, a low and sonorous voice reverberated throughout the entire palace.

“All Elders of Deep King Road, come see me at once!”

This voice carried with it a great majesty and imposing aura. It rang through the ears of every True Divinity level abyssal. As these abyssals of the Dark Abyss heard this voice, they felt the blood quicken in their veins and their hearts begin to race, as if resonating with this sound.

Many higher abyssals directly fell to their knees. “We obey.”

With the summoning of this voice, all True Divinity abyssals of Deep King Road hurried deep into the Demon Palace.

At this place there was an independent world. This was Deep King Road’s forbidden land. Without express permission, no one was allowed in.

But now this forbidden land was opened and the True Divinities of Deep King Road began to enter, one after another.

The moment they entered this forbidden land they felt a terrifying pressure fall down upon them. All the True Divinity level abyssal knelt down.

Before them, not too far away, there was a giant demon head. This demon head seemed forged from metal. It floated in the skies, over a thousand miles large, hanging above like a small star.

This demon head was – Deep!

In front of Deep, these abyssal overlords didn’t dare to take a single breath. They absolutely did not dare to look up into Deep’s face.

They respectfully knelt on the ground, their heads touching the floor as they waited for Deep’s orders.

Deep was silent. All abyssals awaited his command.

And something similar was occurring in the Great Flood Demon Kingdom. In the Great Flood Demon Kingdom’s capital city, a 1000 mile long life form, similar to a python, was perched atop a divine mountain. Its amber pupils flashed with icy light as it stared at the countless abyssals kneeling at the base of the divine mountain.

This giant snake had a pair of wings on its back and four claws. There was also a single horn jutting from its head. It resembled a Flood Dragon a little, and was also the true ruler of the Great Flood Demon Kingdom – Flood!

The Great Flood Demon Kingdom had existed for 2 billion years already. Very few abyssals ever saw Flood. Most of the time, no one even knew where Flood was. In fact, for the last several hundred million years, Flood seemed to have completely vanished, and some abyssals even suspected that Flood had died.

But today Flood had appeared. Moreover, Flood appeared on the Great Flood Demon Kingdom’s divine mountain, in the presence of the trillions upon quadrillions of subjects that lived in the capital city. All the abyssals within hundreds of thousands of miles were able to see this scene.

Their expressions were filled with excitement and awe.

Flood, their hearts’ Demon God, had actually appeared!

All abyssals had a premonition that something important was about to occur in the Dark Abyss.

Chapter 2235 – World Destroying Light

Lin Ming slowly sank to the bottom of the divine pool, feeling the waters gently brush against his body. This feeling was like a mother’s touch, each drop of water the most precious celestial nectar. This water entered Lin Ming’s body through his nose and mouth, flowing into his meridians and discharging from his 360,000 pores, constantly transforming and renewing his body as it went.

At this time, beams of strange blood red light began to gather from all around. Beneath the control of the Asura Road Master, this light flowed into the pool, causing the entire divine pool to be covered with a faint blood red glow. The strength within this pool became increasingly rich, so thick that it made one’s heart race.

At the same time, the Asura Road Master took out a demon bone. This demon bone had been the Soul Emperor’s staff, but when the Soul Emperor abducted Sheng Mei he had thrown it towards Lin Ming and didn’t have enough time to retrieve it.

The material used to forge this demon bone staff was undoubtedly from the true Demon God that existed 100 billion years ago. Now, the Asura Road Master threw it into the divine pool so that Lin Ming could refine it.

“Lin Ming, you will reach perfection of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace in the divine pool, and after that you will completely refine the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe…”

The Asura Road Master’s voice suddenly turned murky and somber. Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He looked up and saw that on the edges of the divine pool, as the Asura bloodline was being poured in, the strength of the Asura Road Master’s incarnation was actually weakening…

Lin Ming could even see that in the Asura Road Master’s originally pitch-black hair, several strands of snow white hair appeared.

Lin Ming’s heart shook. Was this because the Asura Road Master was giving him the strength of his bloodline?

“Senior Asura, you…”

As Lin Ming spoke, the number of threads of white hair on the Asura Road Master’s head began to increase at a visible speed. Lin Ming couldn’t sit still upon seeing this and directly stood up from the divine pond.

At this time, the bloodline strength within the pool was incredibly rich, but Lin Ming was left stunned.

The Asura Road Master calmly said, “Lin Ming, there is no need for you to worry about me…”

“Senior, my training has just begun and might need to continue for 10,000 years. Will you be continually weakening throughout?”

Lin Ming could feel the Asura Road Master’s strength gradually fading away.

He suddenly remembered that the Asura Road Master had already merged into one with the Asura Road. Then, if he were to refine the Asura Road then wouldn’t that mean the Asura Road Master’s strength would be affected? Wouldn’t he become increasingly weak?

The Asura Road Master shook his head. “For these years I have been deeply slumbering within the Asura Road, using every method at my disposal to prolong my life. Even so, I do not have much time remaining. I have lived for far too long. In more than 10 billion years, I went from possessing nothing at all to slowly growing and leaving my mark, from a Holy Lord to World King to Empyrean, and to True Divinity, I became an overlord in my own right and even stood upon the highest peak of the 33 Heavens.

“In my life, I have experienced and possessed everything. But 10 billion years ago I witnessed the great calamity with my own eyes. I watched as my allies, my disciples, and even a woman that I loved deeply above all but did not choose me, slowly die, one after another. The only one who remained was me, and I have been shouldering all of this, continuing until the present.

“Slowly, I have become jaded to everything, all that I see is pale. I no longer chase after that eternal life I was obsessed with, and if I have any desire then it is to finish what I didn’t finish in the past…”

As the Asura Road Master spoke he seemed to become several points older. But, his eyes remained as bright as stars.

Looking at the Asura Road Master, Lin Ming felt an indescribable grieving in his heart.

“Although I have weakened, I won’t completely exhaust myself. It’s only that my abilities to protect the Asura Road will become increasingly weak, thus you must complete your training as soon as possible before the Soul Emperor catches up to you.”

As the Asura Road Master spoke, his expression remained serene throughout. Lin Ming clenched his fists. He could feel just how heavy the burden was that the Asura Road Master carried on his shoulders, but saying anything now was meaningless. What he needed to do was completely refine the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe.

But, plans never went as smoothly as one wished for…

Another 2000 years passed. Within the Divine Conversion Pool, as Lin Ming reached the critical moment in his training, from the vast skies, a black pillar of light abruptly appeared and came smashing down!

This divine light was like a giant black dragon. It passed through a space channel, howling as it fell. It was terrifying, possessing a formidable pressure that caused the blood vitality of all Empyreans in several hundred miles to tumble about, making it impossible for them to look directly at it.

This was like a world destroying light that could annihilate all of existence. It shot straight towards the Amethyst Heavenly Palace where Lin Ming was!

“Lin Ming!”

“Your Majesty Human Sovereign!”

“Senior Lin Ming!”

From the three great races, numerous martial artists saw this scene and cried out in alarm. But, there were also many of these people that couldn’t even respond in time; this world destroying light was far too fast!

“This is bad!”

Divine Dream stared helplessly on as this destructive strength poured unto the Amethyst Heavenly Palace. They were simply powerless to stop it. It was beyond formidable, a power that surpassed the limits of those present.

Deep in seclusion, Lin Ming was in a state where he couldn’t be disturbed. How could he possibly withstand such a strike?

Could this be… an attack from the Demon God’s Tomb Master!?

This thought flashed through Divine Dream’s mind. But in this critical situation as everything hung by a thread, a giant purple hand rose up from the Amethyst Heavenly Palace and struck out at the world destroying light.

This hand was a thousand miles wide. It blocked out the skies, capable of grasping a star!

Bang!

The world destroying divine light exploded within the purple hand. Terrifying shockwaves swelled out in all directions, ruining great tracts of blue skies.

That heaven-covering hand had forcefully blocked the world destroying divine light!

This sudden change left everyone stunned speechless and dumbfounded. Then soon figured out what had happened. This world destroying light was likely the attack of the Demon God’s Tomb Master!

The Demon God’s Tomb Master had come? Could it be that he had already completed his seclusion?

Everyone felt their hearts tighten. If the Demon God’s Tomb Master truly arrived at this moment, then the consequences would be unimaginable.

“Don’t panic! That old demon hasn’t come, he is only making an attack across space-time!”

Divine Dream’s voice echoed out for thousands of miles, calming the minds of the nervous martial artists. The Demon God’s Tomb Master still needed a long period of seclusion. He had been heavily wounded in that great battle 5000 years ago and with all the problems that had occurred in the Demon God’s Tomb, how could he recover so quickly? Moreover, he also had to refine the Demon God’s Tomb.

Since the Asura Road Master dared to allow Lin Ming to go into this final closed door seclusion at this time, then he must have some degree of assurance. Otherwise, it was equal to allow Lin Ming to freely come under attack.

“That old demon hasn’t come?”

“He didn’t come himself yet he was able to make such a dreadful attack through multiple realms of space; that was too horrifying!”

As the martial artists thought of the might behind that world destroying light, all of them felt a lingering fear in their minds. If they were sucked into that light then they would have disintegrated into ashes!

“The Demon God’s Tomb Master is truly fierce, but Senior Asura is also exceptionally strong. That heaven-blocking hand must have been formed by Senior Asura. Without even moving he was already able to block that horrifying black light, how amazing!”

“That’s right, he’s amazing! Hahaha!”

Many martial artists recalled that giant heaven-blocking hand and felt much more cheerful. They knew that the Asura Road Master was guiding Lin Ming in the Amethyst Heavenly Palace and with the protection of the Asura Road Master, it wouldn’t be easy for the Demon God’s Tomb Master to disturb them with long-range attacks.

However, as Divine Dream heard these martial artists proudly speak of the Asura Road Master, a dark cloud of gloom covered her face.

That world destroying light… was it really blocked so easily?

She anxiously looked towards the Amethyst Heavenly Palace. She had a dark foreboding premonition that this attack was only the opening act…

How could the Demon God’s Tomb Master freely allow Lin Ming to complete his seclusion and reach heights where he could pose a threat to him?

“Everyone, listen to me. Do not depend on Senior Asura sheltering you. To survive this calamity, we must depend on ourselves. Hurry up and begin cultivating again.” A delicate and dignified voice called out. The one who spoke was Soaring Feather God King. She floated high in the skies, her white dress floating about her.

5000 years in the time enchantment was equal to 50,000 years outside. With Ink and Clear’s guidance, Soaring Feather God King had broken through to the next boundary and reached the middle True Divinity realm.

Moreover, her strength was decent even amongst middle True Divinities. In this alone she was far stronger than Astral Vault God King. Astral Vault God King was mired in the lower True Divinity realm and hadn’t been able to make his breakthrough yet.

Soaring Feather’s thoughts were similar to Divine Dream’s. This sort of attack would likely continue onwards. The Asura Road Master could block the first, but could he block every one after?

Chapter 2236 – In the Face of Catastrophe

Within the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, the Asura Road Master’s incarnation sat before the divine pool, his complexion slightly pale.

Compared to two thousand years ago, a tremendous change had already occurred within him. His face was still bright and as beautiful as jade and he was still filled with a daring heroic spirit, but his head of black hair had turned silver!

The Asura Road Master’s eyes remained as vibrant as before. Even though he had helped Lin Ming refine the two highest Laws and even though the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s attack had consumed his blood vitality just now, his expression was still one of pure serenity.

“Senior Asura… you…” Lin Ming could feel that the Asura Road Master had been injured in the brief collision with the Demon God’s Tomb Master just now!

Originally, cultivation here already forced the Asura Road Master to expend a tremendous amount of energy. Now in order to resist the attack of the Demon God’s Tomb Master, the pressure placed on him could be imagined!

“Do not be distracted. The greatest help you can offer me right now is to single-mindedly complete the refinement as soon as possible. If you can finish a hundred years earlier then that is a hundred fewer years of pressure that I must face. I hope that when you finish your cultivation, your boundary will be equal to mine!”

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat. “My boundary will be equal to Senior’s?”

The Asura Road Master’s boundary was naturally that of Beyond Divinity!

But Lin Ming thought that even if he were to seclude himself for another 10,000 years, then although his strength would greatly increase, wanting to step Beyond Divinity was actually unlikely.

Even with another potential 10,000 years added on, Lin Ming would only have cultivated for around 40,000 years. But, compared to those martial artists that had lived for hundreds of millions of years, 40,000 years was nothing at all.

The Asura Road Master said, “In terms of cultivation, you are a bit worse. But when it comes to the boundary in Laws, you actually surpass me… the so-called Beyond Divinity is in truth not some orthodox boundary. In the road of martial arts, every legitimate great boundary is divided into smaller realms – early, middle, late, peak… but Beyond Divinity does not possess these. This is because Beyond Divinity is not a large boundary at all, but a state of being, such as totem level abyssals that have reached the limits of True Divinity. When a martial artist comprehends their own perfect system of Laws, the state he achieves is called Beyond Divinity!

“Beyond Divinity. That is when one’s cultivation reaches the peak and one’s Laws reach the peak, and these two dual peaks cannot be surpassed. This is the highest realm of martial arts!”

The Asura Road Master’s words were gentle, but what he said left Lin Ming shocked. This was the first time Lin Ming had heard someone describe the Beyond Divinity realm.

“Junior understands!”

Within the Divine Conversion Pool, Lin Ming deeply bowed to the Asura Road Master. He also understood that Beyond Divinity martial artists were still divided into varying degrees of strength. Who was weaker and who was stronger, all depended on how strong a martial artist had been before they stepped Beyond Divinity and also the heights of their Laws.

Though his cultivation hadn’t reached the peak of True Divinity, none of that mattered. At the early True Divinity realm he was able to compare to a peak True Divinity already! 10,000 years from now, if his cultivation rose to the upper True Divinity realm and his Laws reached perfection, then he might be able to defeat the Demon God’s Tomb Master!

……….

Divine Dream and Soaring Feather’s speculations hadn’t been wrong. That world-destroying light was only the beginning of the nightmare…

Two thousand years later, the divine light reappeared!

Moreover, this time it wasn’t just one, but two together!

Two beams of divine light fell from the clouds like two pillars that held up the heavens. They crashed down onto the Amethyst Heavenly Palace!

From within the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, the heaven-blocking hand appeared once more and brutally collided with those beams of light!

For a time, the earth shook and mountains rocked. The Asura Sea sagged down from the horrifying pressure, forming a giant hollow ‘water bowl’ a thousand miles deep. All the clouds above the Asura Sea were blown away by the shockwaves.

Looking at this apocalyptic scene before them, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were bewildered. “If… if this continues, what can we do…”

The last attack had also been blocked by the Asura Road Master. They didn’t know how difficult it had been for the Asura Road Master to block that world-destroying light, but this time it seemed that it wasn’t easy for the Asura Road Master!

After these two beams of divine light blasted down, the hand created by the Asura Road Master was forcefully torn apart!

Some energy even poured down from the seams of the palm and fell onto the Amethyst Heavenly Palace like waterfalls. Luckily, the Amethyst Heavenly Palace was protected by array formations, so that energy was eventually unable to reach it…

“The situation is worsening!” Divine Dream frowned.

There was an attack after 2000 years, and it seemed as if the enemy’s strength was increasing!

This meant two things. The first was that the Demon God’s Tomb Master was in seclusion and couldn’t leave the Demon God’s Tomb nor could he freely launch attacks as he wished. He could only take advantage of small breaks or use excess energy to attack Lin Ming. And the second was that as time passed, the Demon God’s Tomb Master was constantly growing stronger.

But in the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, the Asura Road Master would clearly not grow stronger; he might even weaken with time.

If so, then the situation would only deteriorate from here on out.

Whether it was Divine Dream or the high level figures of humanity and the saints, all of them were nervous.

There was no way they could block that black divine light. Moreover, that divine light directly passed through space and was equal to instantly transferring to the area above the Amethyst Heavenly Palace; wanting to intercept it midway was impossible.

Another 2000 years passed. And sure enough, the world-destroying light appeared once more!

Two beams of divine light fell down again. Everyone held their breath as they saw this. No one had any idea whether or not the Asura Road Master would form that heaven-blocking hand once more to resist the attack. But suddenly, from above the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, a white light shot out. An ancient white altar appeared, welcoming the world-destroying light!

This stone altar was 100,000 feet tall and divided into 33 levels. This was the spirit treasure that the Asura Road Master had refined himself and placed into the final trial’s seventh level – the Divine Seal Altar!

3.6 billion years ago, Empyrean Divine Seal had once imitated the Divine Seal Altar to refine his own magic tool. This was where Empyrean Divine Seal’s name had come from.

The two world-destroying lights recklessly fell down upon the Divine Seal Altar!

Bang!

The Divine Seal Altar wildly shook. Tumultuous waves rose up in the Asura Sea. Terrifying tsunamis soared a thousand miles into the skies, piercing into the heavens!

These thousand mile high tsunamis could be called a calamity, but at this time the common people of the Asura Road had already been evacuated. Thus, no matter how those giant tsunamis crashed into the earth, it still didn’t create a scene where massive numbers of lives were cut down.

“I wonder how much longer Lin Ming’s seclusion needs…” Xiao Moxian held her hands together, looking towards the direction of the Amethyst Heavenly Palace with a heavy heart.

Lin Huang gently took hold of Xiao Moxian’s hand. He knew that this world-destroying divine light was only the overture to the arrival of the true war…

Chapter 2238 – Invasion of the Abyss

The Amethyst Heavenly Palace was gone. Lin Ming’s original place of seclusion had been completely destroyed. Within the terrifying storm that spanned the heavens and earth, everyone could vaguely make out a person’s figure. This figure was charred black, like a piece of dead wood struck by lightning!

“Lin Ming!”

“Father!”

Xiao Moxian and Lin Huang were intimately related to Lin Ming and were able to instantly recognize that this charred figure was him. As they saw the pitiful condition that Lin Ming was in, Xiao Moxian’s heart wrenched and every martial artist of the 33 Heavens held their breath.

“It’s over! His Majesty Human Sovereign’s seclusion has been broken!”

“Must the heavens destroy my human race?”

“Is today the end for us saints?”

In that moment, the overlords of the three races all felt despair surge in their hearts.

They hadn’t even fought and yet they had been defeated? They had put forth so much effort in the last several tens of thousands of years, and yet they didn’t even have the qualifications to fight?

“Father hasn’t died…” Jiu’er said. She could feel fluctuations of energy coming from Lin Ming. Jiu’er had experienced Lin Ming’s baptism of Laws when he broke into True Divinity, and in terms of energy resonance she was even closer than Lin Huang.

“It’s good that he hasn’t died…”

The primal god race’s Diwuhen suddenly said. Although it sounded good to say that Lin Ming hadn’t died, no one was able to relax in this situation.

From Lin Ming’s horrible condition it was likely he had suffered some severe wound. And, it had to be known that Lin Ming was currently in seclusion and he was also in his most crucial period, the final stretch to break into the realm Beyond Divinity!

How could such a period of seclusion accommodate an attack like this? Seeing Lin Ming’s charred body and severely wounded appearance, the situation was absolutely awful. This was an attack from the Demon God’s Tomb Master!

In the situation, if Lin Ming’s cultivation was broken midway, could he still complete his seclusion? Or would the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s attack ruin everything and cause Lin Ming to fail?

If this was really the result then the 33 Heavens was done for. Everything was finished.

Even if Lin Ming could still continue his seclusion, his injuries might ruin his plans of completing his cultivation in 10,000 years.

To the current 33 Heavens, time was life. If Lin Ming were to leave seclusion after the Soul Emperor then the end result was the same as Lin Ming’s seclusion being interrupted midway.

The 33 Heavens would still be destroyed and all native races sentenced to extinction!

Everyone had placed their hopes on Lin Ming, but as they saw his current state, their mood could be imagined!

At this time, space began to twist all around Lin Ming. A massive amount of world strength gathered, forming into a force field around him. This force field enveloped him and began to slowly sink back into the destroyed Asura Sea, vanishing from sight within the vortex that continued to swallow everything.

“His Majesty Human Sovereign has gone to recover his wounds…” A young, newly-promoted human Empyrean said with a heavy heart.

“If he wants to continue cultivating he certainly must restore his wounds… but, His Majesty the Human Sovereign still requires time to heal his wounds… and it will take more time than before his seclusion was interrupted. If this continues…”

A spiritas True Divinity sighed. He didn’t finish speaking, but everyone understood the meaning behind his words.

“Stop spouting such discouraging words! If the Human Sovereign has not yet died then that means we still have hope! Everyone, take a brief break and continue your training!” The one who spoke was Soaring Feather God King. As the current top figure and leader of the saints, Soaring Feather had an extremely high level of prestige. In the 33 Heavens she even neared Divine Dream in fame. But now, even Soaring Feather called Lin Ming the Human Sovereign. This was because Lin Ming was the ultimate leader of the 33 Heavens, and in public it was reasonable for her to refer to him with his title.

After stopping everyone’s panicked discussions, Soaring Feather continued to say, “The Human Sovereign has already resisted attacks at 2000 years, 4000 years, 6000 years, 8000 years, and 10,000 years. Even if there is another attack after 12,000 years and 14,000 years, how do you know that the Human Sovereign cannot withstand it? Perhaps there have been more miracles that have happened to him than the rest of us combined!”

What Soaring Feather said was the truth. It wasn’t an exaggeration to say that there were far too many miracles occurring around Lin Ming.

As long as Lin Ming was able to withstand this attack and take that final step Beyond Divinity then the entire situation would be reversed!

And according to the last two attacks of the Demon God’s Tomb Master, the second attack was far weaker than the first. He had clearly overdrawn himself to make such an attack; in other words, the Demon God’s Tomb Master might stop his attacks for the next several thousand years…

If so, then the 33 Heavens had a glimmer of hope…

As everyone was thinking this, a bolt of black lightning broke out from 10,000 miles above their heads!

This black lightning was like the sword of a spiritual god, forcefully severing the vault of the heavens in two!

“What happened!?”

“It’s not over!?”

All the overlords of the various races raised their vigilance once more. They looked up into the skies where the heavens had been divided in half by that black lightning. At that place, there was a giant black hole. The black hole exuded an incomparably evil aura, and black flames spat out from the edges, wildly dancing around it like giant pythons!

“That is…”

“Space channel!”

The overlords of the 33 Heavens were all highly experienced and knowledgeable individuals. They quickly recognized that the black hole which appeared in the skies was not some attack used by a top master, but a space channel!

“This… this space channel is too big!”

The True Divinities of the three races were all stunned. The space channel began to recklessly proliferate outwards until it occupied half the skies. This feeling was as if a black universe had appeared out of thin air and was forcefully merging together with the Asura Road.

And what followed left the hearts of all martial artists quaking!

From that great black world, black figures began to appear. Dense and endless, an inexhaustible number, it looked like a swarm of locusts flying in from afar.

“That is…”

“Abyssals!”

In these years, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens naturally learned of the abyssal demons and also saw what they looked like. These countless dense waves of dark figures were abyssals!

The Eternal Wall had long since been destroyed and the abyssals had been uncaged; they could invade the 33 Heavens at any moment!

The reason they patiently bided their time was not to give the races of the 33 Heavens a chance to catch their breath. Rather, it was because the Asura Road was protected by the Asura Road Master and it was meaningless to attack the 33 Heavens.

But now, the Demon God’s Tomb Master seemed to have calculated that the Asura Road Master was helping Lin Ming in the final stages of his seclusion, and because of this his strength had plummeted to its weakest point. When the Demon God’s Tomb Master had attacked, he had destroyed the Amethyst Heavenly Palace and simultaneously pierced through the great defensive array formation laid down by the Asura Road Master.

Like this, even if the Demon God’s Tomb Master couldn’t attack again, he could still send in the abyssals to destroy Lin Ming!

This was the fully gathered strength of the many Empyrean and True Divinity abyssals!

The curtains to the great war of calamity had been opened!

Chapter 2241 – Heaven and Man Array

“Your strength isn’t too bad. It seems that we underestimated you!”

A demon king stood up and sneered at the martial artists of the 33 Heavens. He originally thought that with the difference of strength between the 33 Heavens and Dark Abyss, it would be a completely lopsided battle. But he never thought that while the Dark Abyss had been weakened, the 33 Heavens would actually rise up in their desperation and so many masters would appear.

In this battle, although it seemed that the Dark Abyss’s victory was assured, they would still have to pay a considerable price.

But so what? If the abyssals were able to leave the Dark Abyss, become the sole rulers of the 33 Heavens and have their race continue onwards for another trillion years, even surviving the next great Shattering of the universe, then all of these sacrifices would be worth it.

The four upper True Divinity abyssals also attacked at this time. Demonic energies surged from their bodies but they didn’t attack the martial artists of the 33 Heavens. Rather, they used their energies to draw up a massive array diagram.

With so many True Divinity abyssals in front of them, the 8600 Empyreans of the Dark Abyss also flew into the array diagram.

“This is bad, they are planning to go all-out!”

With 60 some True Divinities and over 8000 Empyreans, this was the complete strength of the Dark Abyss. Now, they gathered their strength in a grand array formation. If they were to attack like this then their strength could be imagined!

In a large-scale battle between martial artists, the effects of battle arrays were remarkable. If they scattered out the attack they could absolutely sweep away the entire battlefield.

The Dark Abyss had already formed an array formation. The only way for the 33 Heavens to deal with them was to also form a battle array and meet them head-on!

But in a situation where the overall strength of the 33 Heavens was far inferior to the Dark Abyss’s, if their battle arrays were to collide then the 33 Heavens were sure to suffer serious casualties!

Death was not fearful. What was scary was to die without meaning.

In this final battle, no one held back. Many martial artists of the 33 Heavens even spat out blood essence and overdrew their own life potential!

Everyone came into this battle with the determination to die. At this time, no one wavered; they were already pushed into a corner without any path to retreat!

As the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were ready to risk their lives in this battle, the Asura Sea separated below them and a mottled stone altar began to rise up from the sea into the skies.

“Divine Seal Altar!?”

The martial artists of the 33 Heavens certainly knew what the Divine Seal Altar was; it was a spirit treasure that the Asura Road Master had refined in the past. It had nearly been destroyed by the Demon God’s Tomb Master and everyone thought that it was damaged beyond use or repair. But now, it actually appeared!

“Mm? That is - !?”

Everyone saw glittering Asura Heavenly Dao runes shimmering atop the Divine Seal Altar. Could this be the work of… the Asura Road Master!?

The martial artists of the 33 Heavens were already in desperate straits. Now, as they saw these shimmering Asura Heavenly Dao runes, all of them were left excited. If the Asura Road Master could help them out then even the demon army before them wouldn’t be enough!

Everyone was filled with expectations. They all fervently wished to see the Asura Road Master display his heaven-transcending abilities to slaughter all their enemies.

But, this did not occur. Instead, runes shot out from the Divine Seal Altar, turning into divine beams of light that shrouded a part of the world.

“Use this Heaven and Man Array as the foundation to protect me for one month!”

At this time, a dignified sound transmission echoed into the ears of the 33 Heavens’ martial artists.

They could immediately tell that this was Lin Ming’s voice.

Although the tone was the same as Lin Ming’s voice, the majesty and momentum contained within was eternal and forever, like that of a supreme general, leaving everyone’s hearts shocked.

They all immediately realized that the one who moved to action just now was not the Asura Road Master but Lin Ming!

In fact, the grand array that appeared in front of everyone was not purely the Asura Heavenly Dao Array, but a Heaven and Man Array formed from Lin Ming fusing together the world of the universe and the world of the body.

“His Majesty Human Sovereign is still in seclusion but he can also help at this time?”

What Lin Ming said was to protect him for one month. This was different from the 100 years that they had expected before this.

Would Lin Ming be able to leave seclusion in one month?

Many people were inexplicably thrilled at this possibility. They didn’t know that Lin Ming had used every method at his disposal to leave seclusion in advance, and they also didn’t know that the Demon God’s Tomb Master had calculated this date ahead of time and had launched the final war to destroy Lin Ming before his seclusion finished.

“Protect His Majesty the Human Sovereign for a month!”

The martial artists of the 33 Heavens all gripped their fists. Before this, they thought that all their hopes were ruined, but now they knew that as long as they could protect Lin Ming for a month, they might have a path to survival!

As long as they could guarantee Lin Ming’s safety then the bloodline of the races of the 33 Heavens would be able to continue onwards. This was their only chance.

The Heaven and Man Array covered all martial artists of the 33 Heavens.

At this time, no one held back. They poured all of their strength into this grand array.

Hum –

The grand array formed a giant barrier of light that radiated outwards, colliding with the abyssals’ battle array!

The abyssals’ array formation shattered. Dozens of Empyreans abyssals were unable to withstand the impact of energy through their bodies and instantly burst apart into pieces of flesh and bloody mist!

In this horrifying collision, the deaths of Empyreans only took a brief moment.

“Retreat!”

The four demon kings shouted out in unison. The 33 Heavens’ counterattack had exceeded their expectations.

They didn’t think Lin Ming would actually have such skills. Even in seclusion he was still able to interfere in their fight.

They didn’t know what Lin Ming’s plans were and they also didn’t know that Lin Ming had sent out a sound transmission telling the martial artists of the 33 Heavens to protect him for one month.

It was naturally impossible to reveal this plan to the abyssals, otherwise they would desperately attack for a full month non-stop.

“This brat, he’s already at death’s door yet he’s still putting up a last ditch struggle.”

“Humph, he’s only delaying the end. This grand array formation can only defend and not attack, just like a turtle shell. If we continue to attack then sooner or later we’ll break through!”

The four demon kings soon discovered the ‘weakness’ of the Heaven and Man Array. This was a purely defensive array formation, but for Lin Ming, as long as he could defend then it was his victory!

However, defending against the siege of this demon army for an entire month was easier said than done.

Although dozens of abyssal Empyreans had died in that brief collision just now, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens weren’t in a much better state.

Many people had burned their blood essence and greatly depleted their life potential. Many of them had also received heavy wounds.

“Those that are wounded hurry and restore yourselves! Those that are uninjured, guard the grand array! Everyone that has precious pills, take them all out and tend to the wounded!”

The one speaking was Divine Dream. She also moved first to set an example. She took out all the precious pills within her spatial ring to help heal others.

Soon after, Soaring Feather, Astral Vault, and Emperor Shakya also took out their pills. The spiritas, saint, primal god race martial artists, all of them followed suit.

A month would be a prolonged war. These precious pills and various energy stones would all be of great use and would need to be arranged ahead of time. At this time, no one hid anything any longer. They all understood that the only way to survive this calamity was to work together as one!

Chapter 2242 – Until the End

“Not attacking and only defending, you’re just waiting for death! Humph!”

“Although Lin Ming is strong he is actually in seclusion and was also wounded by the Demon God. The array formation he laid down can’t stop us!”

The abyssal True Divinities all attacked, working together to crush the defensive array formation in front of them. They knew that all array formations had a limit to the amount of energy they contained, and once this limit was reached the array formation would naturally shatter. At that time, all that awaited the martial artists of the 33 Heavens was slaughter.

However, as the abyssal True Divinities released world-shocking demonic strikes again and again, their complexion began to turn ugly.

The firmness of this array formation had surpassed their imaginations! They attacked for such a long time but there hadn’t been much energy loss at all.

“How could this be…?”

“This array formation is strange… that Lin Ming, even in seclusion he could lay down such an array?”

The abyssal True Divinities muttered, shocked.

In fact, it wasn’t just them who were shocked, but the martial artists of the 33 Heavens within the Heaven and Man Array were also stunned by the effectiveness of this array formation.

Within the array formation they could feel the energy structure to an even clearer degree.

The structure was a sublime and perfect composition, just like an eggshell. It dispersed the attack of every abyssal across the entire array formation, minimizing the impact of every strike to its lowest possible degree.

This array formation was named the Heaven and Man Array. The light barrier that shrouded everyone was ‘heaven’, and the martial artists within were ‘man’. With heaven and man combined together, this was a perfect union to enforce the array formation.

The abyssals possessed a horrifying strength. But even though they had over 60 True Divinities and 8000 Empyreans gathered together they still couldn’t manage to break past the array formation, and the person who set up the array formation was still in seclusion.

“Lin Ming, it seems he is far stronger than we expected. No wonder the lord Demon God places so much importance on him…”

“I thought that we could slowly erase the runes of the array formation then all of us could attack together to completely destroy it, but it seems that this isn’t a good idea.”

“Let’s change methods. Break through the defensive array with our battle array!”

The leading demon kings made a decisive change in tactics. They led the 8000 some abyssal Empyreans and 60 abyssal True Divinities to set up their battle array once more and directly attack the Heaven and Man Array.

“We cannot let those abyssal get what they want. We’ve only managed to hold out for a day so far.”

“There are still 29 days remaining. We must persist until the end, otherwise all that we have worked for will end in vain!”

Seeing the abyssals go all-out, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens revolved their blood vitality to the limit. Energy surged out from them in monstrous waves!

They were inferior to the Dark Abyss in overall strength, but by relying on the Heaven and Man Array they could greatly diminish the disparity.

The 33 Heavens had 28 True Divinities that guarded 28 different spots within the array formation. As for the 1800 some Empyreans, they were dispersed equally around the array formation. All of them utilized their energies to the limit to resist the abyssals.

The abyssals began their attacks once more. The distant skies were already swallowed up by tumbling waves of demonic flames!

Divine light howled and pierced through the world. The demon army’s attack brutally fell down upon the Heaven and Man Array.

Bang!

Like a thousand stars exploding, all sounds faded as light seemed to disappear from the heavens and earth.

Even the defensive abilities of the Heaven and Man Array were unable to completely isolate out the impact of energy. Ripples appeared in the light barrier and spread out in all directions.

20 some Empyreans bore the brunt of this attack and weren’t able to withstand the impact force. They were sent tumbling backwards, spitting out blood. Three Empyreans amongst them blew apart as they were sent flying back, immediately dying a miserable death!

People had died!

Ever since the final apocalyptic war arrived, this was the first time that people from the side of the 33 Heavens had died!

The losses of these three Empyreans didn’t seem like much, but everyone knew that this was only the beginning.

Of the full month needed, only a single day had passed.

As the battle continued it would only become increasingly heated and violent. The energies consumed would grow larger and larger, and inevitably there would be more and more that died.

This was would be a bitter and protracted defensive war. Their only hope to live on was to… last until the end!

“Heal the wounded!”

Divine Dream’s voice echoed out from within the Heaven and Man Array.

As for the three Empyreans that had died, their mutilated and incomplete corpses had already been respectfully received into the spatial rings of their companions.

At this time, no one was sad and no one mourned. This was because no one knew just when they themselves would become icy cold corpses that were put away by others.

If some people managed to luckily live through this war then their corpses would be buried and they would be lifted up as heroes, recorded in the annals of history and in the hearts of their descendants.

But if they all died then their corpses would be turned to ashes and the abyssals would mock them as naught but dead slaves.

The martial artists of the 33 Heavens silently distributed pills around. Everyone began to meditate and restore themselves because they knew that before long, the next attack of the abyssals would arrive.

Since they were only defending and not attacking, the number of abyssals would not lower over time.

But as for them, every collision meant that some people would die. And the more people that died the weaker the defensive strength of the array formation would become. And the weaker the defensive strength of the array formation, the more people would die. This cycle would continue until the entire array eventually collapsed!

“These trash races are actually so difficult to deal with…”

The four demon kings all had gloomy complexions. Their attack had only managed to kill three Empyreans. It was hard for them to accept this as a victory.

“A good number of them burnt their blood essence so it will surely be a problem for them to restore themselves. As for our demon army, no one has burnt their blood essence so our recovery speed will be faster.”

“If we continued to wear them down then they will undoubtedly die!”

“Burning their blood essence? Humph!” Cold light flashed in the eyes of the Deep King Road Sovereign. “With so many people, if they each took turns burning their blood essence then they could drag things out for a long time! I do not want them to live this long. The lord Demon God has ordered us to destroy them as soon as possible! If they can burn their blood essence then so can we! Our six great totem level sects have accumulated countless blood pills and heavenly materials for all these years. If it is only the Empyrean level abyssals then even if they burn their blood essence we could still make up for their lost blood vitality!”

“Good! Then there is no need to delay. Destroy them all!”

The abyssals began to eat up blood pills and restore their strength.

Infernal energy gushed out from their bodies, soaring to the heavens. Killing intent seethed all around them. Even from far away and beneath the Heaven and Man Array, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens could still clearly feel this.

The abyssals had used less than a day to restore themselves to their peak state.

They had formed their battle array once more and wanted to tear the Heaven and Man Array apart. This time, a good number of abyssals chose to burn their blood essence.

Terrifying levels of energy began condensing in the horizon.

The Asura Sea surged. The heavens trembled. A sneer appeared on the lips of the four upper True Divinity abyssals. All of them were diabolically grinning.

“Lin Ming, no matter how outstanding your talent is, you will still die here!”

Chapter 2243 – One Month Period

Weng!

In the skies, the energies of over 8000 abyssals gathered together, transforming into the phantom of a giant demon god.

This demon god was like the ancestor god capable of destroying all of existence. It emitted a terrifying pressure, overlooking the world with disdain!

“What is that!?”

On the side of the 33 Heavens, many martial artists had just finished their meditation. As they looked at the giant demon god phenomenon swirling in the skies, all of them felt greatly suppressed.

Even though they were separated by the Heaven and Man Array, this demon god’s aura still left them gasping for breath.

Some of the 33 Heavens’ martial artists with weaker cultivations paled, their palms dripping with sweat.

“This is a battle array, one even stronger than the last. If I’m not wrong then this battle array is fused with runes of the Demon God!”

The one who spoke was Ink. His sight and experience was naturally something that the martial artists of the 33 Heavens couldn’t compare with.

“Runes of the Demon God?” Emperor Shakya’s heart chilled. They had heard the name Demon God many times already. It seemed that this Demon God was the founder of the Demon God’s Tomb.

“It’s just like Lin Ming adding his power of Laws unto our bodies. Similarly, the abyssals can find higher level runes to strengthen themselves. Things are going to become more difficult from here on out…”

Clear bitterly smiled. He realized that this battle would be more severe than first imagined.

But no matter what runes were fused into the battle array of the demon army, this wasn’t what the martial artists of the 33 Heavens needed to care about. All they had to do was to fight with everything they had.

Roar!

The demon god roared. Its cry shattered mountains and sundered rivers. It was like a boundless curtain of night came falling down, covering the defensive array of the 33 Heavens martial artists inside.

Kacha!

The Heaven and Man Array emitted a creaking sound from the immense burden; cracks began to appear on the surface.

This was strength capable of destroying a world. The closest several hundred Empyreans bore the brunt of this attack. Their bodies shook and they were sent flying away. In the terrifying impact they were no different from tiny leaves in a storm, simply incapable of resisting. Even the True Divinity level Jun Bluemoon spat out a mouthful of blood that dyed his snow white clothes red.

“Ahhh!”

As everyone drew back, screams emitted from the martial artists of the 33 Heavens. Some people were unable to withstand the violent energy shockwaves that were released and exploded into pieces!

Everyone watched helplessly as those who were just breathing a moment ago were torn to shreds.

Within this energy storm, if one was able to maintain their protective shields then they would be able to withstand it. But if one’s protective shields were shattered then one would immediately be ripped to pieces!

This miserable way of death left everyone’s scalps tingling with fear.

The storm ravaged the world for a full incense stick of time before slowly subsiding. The Asura Sea had evaporated from the heat, and over 20 martial artists of the 33 Heavens had died in the chaos. Many of them didn’t even have skeletons remaining and were only a vague pile of blood and goo on the ground.

“This is too tragic!”

Those that died had all been overlords of the 33 Heavens. Many of them had lived for millions of years already and were rulers of their own worlds. But in a war of this level, all of them were incomparably fragile.

All that could be collected for burial were incomplete corpses. The hearts of the 33 Heavens’ martial artists were filled with sadness and grief.

However, no one stopped to mourn the dead. Without instruction from Divine Dream they all began to sit down and meditate to restore their energies.

What awaited them was an even more brutal battle.

“Jun Bluemoon, are you alright?”

Divine Dream worriedly inquired into Jun Bluemoon’s wounds. Within the 33 Heavens, there were only 28 True Divinities left remaining. If Empyreans died then they wouldn’t collapse, but every time one of the 28 True Divinities died it would make the array formation lose a supporting corner, causing the pressure to be that much greater.

“I’m fine…”

Jun Bluemoon forced out a smile, indicating that he could still continue to fight.

Clear took out a pill and fed it to Jun Bluemoon to help him recover as soon as possible.

“These wretches!”

In the distance, a pale Great Flood Demon Kingdom Imperial Scholar hatefully gnashed out. In that strike just now, he and the other upper True Divinities had formed the foundation of the array formation and had consumed a tremendous amount of energy.

Although they had struck open a crack in the Heaven and Man Array, this crack wasn’t enough to shatter the grand array. And as they watched, the array formation was clearly repairing itself. This left the many abyssals stunned. This array formation was far stronger than their initial expectations.

“Humph, let’s see just how long they can last.”

This was a protracted war of attrition. The Dark Abyss would launch an attack against the 33 Heavens every day. Sometimes several of the 33 Heavens’ martial artists would die, sometimes it would be around a dozen, and sometimes it would be in the dozens.

Everyone had already become accustomed to their allies dying by their sides. After witnessing so much death all around them, these overlords of the 33 Heavens were actually no longer afraid of dying.

In truth, they valued their lives, but they feared the annihilation of their races even more. They feared that after their death their descendants would be taken in as slaves and even reared as beasts in pens, butchered whenever the abyssals wished.

The fierce battle continued for another 12 days. The 33 Heavens had lost around 300 Empyrean level martial artists so far.

Three True Divinities had been injured, of which Jun Bluemoon was the most severely wounded. This wasn’t because Jun Bluemoon was weak. In fact, Jun Bluemoon’s strength was outstanding amongst lower True Divinities. However, because he had to withstand the direct frontal impact of the abyssal race’s battle array, his injuries had superimposed on each other, causing him to suffer heavy losses.

Even so, Jun Bluemoon didn’t withdraw to the rear because the current situation didn’t allow him to do so.

After the 15th day, over 400 Empyreans had died on the side of the 33 Heavens.

To the Heaven and Man Array, the 28 True Divinities were the most important figures; they were the crux, the foundation of the array. But Empyreans were also important. When 1800 Empyreans gathered together, the war strength they displayed was incredible.

For this Empyrean level war strength, if a few dozens died then the losses were acceptable. But after hundreds died, it became clear that the defensive capabilities of the Heaven and Man Array had weakened.

With every attack, more and more large cracks formed and these cracks also healed themselves at an increasingly slow pace.

The 33 Heavens’ martial artists could clearly feel the pressure rapidly increasing on them. It had to be known that on the side of the Dark Abyss, they suffered nearly no losses. At most some abyssals had burnt too much blood essence and temporarily drew back to restore themselves.

In a situation where one side’s overall strength was twice that of the other side, and in a situation where that side chose to use a continuous attack to wear down their enemy, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were finding themselves slowly unable to continue!

And currently, only half the amount of the required time that Lin Ming had spoken of had passed!

Could they really last for a month? No one could guarantee this.

Perhaps before a month passed, all the martial artists of the 33 Heavens would have died in battle already.

From the 16th day onwards, the abyssals’ onslaught actually slowed down a little.

But in this situation Divine Dream and the other high level figures of the 33 Heavens didn’t feel any sense of ease. Rather, their moods became increasingly dark and tense. They realized that this was likely the calm before the storm. The abyssals were gathering their energies for an even more terrifying attack!

Chapter 2244 – Evil

Divine Dream’s speculations weren’t wrong; the abyssals were indeed gathering their strength. And, their next attack completely surpassed the expectations of the 33 Heavens martial artists.

After a quiet three days, it was the 18th day of the abyssal invasion.

Winds began to suddenly surge. 10,000 miles high in the sky, the vault of the heavens was torn open and a space channel appeared from nowhere.

“Space channel!”

Seeing this, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens all felt their hearts tighten. The Demon God’s Tomb Master’s attack and the abyssal invasion had all been done through space channels.

If this space channel suddenly appeared then it was likely the work of the Dark Abyss. In other words, it was absolutely bad news.

“Are those reinforcements from the Dark Abyss!?”

“The current demon army has already forced us to the edge of the cliff. If more reinforcements come then we’re doomed!”

A blood-drenched martial artist of the 33 Heavens said. No one doubted that if more reinforcements came rushing out from that space channel, then they wouldn’t even be able to last until the 20th day.

Roar!

A heaven-shaking roar blasted out from the space channel.

This was different from what the martial artists of the 33 Heavens suspected. What passed through the space channel were not reinforcements of the abyssal army, but a massive demon head.

This demon looked like a skull that was soaked in blood. Its entire body was bathed in deep purple flames and it was over a thousand miles tall. As it floated in the skies, it was like a hideous purple-red star.

When this demon appeared, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens suddenly felt a tremendous pressure push down upon them. It was like the world itself were falling down upon them, and even the Heaven and Man Array was aroused because of this pressure.

“What is that thing!?”

“I have no idea!”

Seeing this abyssal appear, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were left in a frenzied panic. This monster was only a head – could it be an abyssal?

No matter what this thing was, what was true was that this demon head was their great enemy!

“It…” Ink and Clear looked at the demon head in the skies, their complexions turning ugly.

“Do two seniors know what that is?” Divine Dream’s heart raced as she saw Ink and Clear’s complexions. It was clear from their reactions that this demon head was incredibly formidable.

“If I’m not wrong then that giant demon head is… one of the six great totem abyssals – Evil!” Ink and Clear were subordinates of Asura and knew what the scene of the great war from 10 billion years past had been like.

These words shocked everyone. “Evil? How is that possible?”

The 33 Heavens martial artists now knew that Deep, Flood, and the Soul Emperor were all avatars of the Demon God’s Tomb Master. And in order to complete his seclusion, the Demon God’s Tomb Master had already fused together his three avatars.

As for the other totem level abyssals like Evil, Eon, Nether, and so forth, they had already died. 10 billion years ago they had been struck down by the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign.

“Evil indeed died, but a totem level abyssal can be reborn. An abyssal can accept the abyssal ritual within the Demon God’s Tomb to create a new totem level abyssal…”

Ink and Clear’s words caused despair to surge in the hearts of all those present. A totem level abyssal was an existence only inferior to a Beyond Divinity powerhouse!

This abyssal demon army had already pushed them to the limits of what they could withstand. If this Evil that was stronger than all of them was added on, then the result could be imagined.

They feared the Heaven and Man Array might instantly explode!

“Lin Ming…”

Divine Dream bit her lips and gazed towards the direction where Lin Ming was in seclusion. She sighed and muttered to herself, “You have protected us so many times, and yet we cannot even manage to protect you once?”

“Don’t panic! This is indeed ‘Evil’, but its strength might not be as high as you imagine. The six totem level abyssals are born after passing through the test of the abyssal ritual, but in truth that is the strength of the Demon God’s Tomb Master. The Demon God’s Tomb Master divides a portion of his strength to seal into the bodies of these totem level abyssals.”

“But now, the Demon God’s Tomb Master is in seclusion and needs to condense as much strength as he can. It is unlikely that he was able to form the complete ‘Evil’… moreover, the ‘Evil’ before us has only grown in the last 10,000 some years. Its true strength should be far from being able to compare with a true totem level abyssal.”

As Ink and Clear were speaking, Evil was already launching its attack!

Evil roared, its massive jaws opening and shooting out a beam of red divine light. This divine light fused together with the total strength of the Dark Abyss’s demon army and came crashing down onto the Heaven and Man Array!

Peng!

The Heaven and Man Array fiercely trembled. The thick barrier of the array actually had a hole blown open in it!

Waves of energy raged outwards. Dozens of 33 Heavens martial artists were swept into these waves and instantly disintegrated. This divine beam of light would soon tear open the great array formation propped up by the martial artists of the 33 Heavens! In this crucial moment, all seven of the several strongest martial artists of the 33 Heavens – Divine Dream, Mo Eversnow, Ink, Clear, Lin Huang, Xiao Moxian, and Divine Mist who had seized the body of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, attacked together.

Divine Dream led the counterattack and bore the brunt of the strike. She overdrew the strength of her divine soul to cut out with her sword!

However, the strength that the abyssals had been gathering for so long was incredibly potent. Divine Dream’s chest was crushed inwards by the impact force. Her arms broke and she was sent tumbling backwards, spitting out a mouthful of blood.

Mo Eversnow, Lin Huang, Xiao Moxian, Divine Mist, and the others could all feel an evil strength break into their bodies. This strength began to rapidly eat away at the vitality within their bodies as a deathly energy broke into their inner worlds. This icy cold sensation felt as if they were on the verge of death.

“Senior Divine Dream!”

“Fairy Maiden Ji!”

Several people cried out in alarm. But at this time, who could worry about such things? Divine Dream held onto her chest and hurriedly said, “Repair the array formation! Fix it, no matter the cost!”

A hole had been torn in the Heaven and Man Array. And at this time, abyssals had already broken in through the gap!

“Kill them!”

The 33 Heavens martial artists were enraged. They recklessly rushed towards the abyssals. The seven or eight abyssal demons in the front were directly cut down by various Law lights without even their bones left remaining!

Divine Dream ignored her injuries to forcefully summon up her spirit essence. She opened the divine dream space and used this force field to cover the opening in the Heaven and Man Array.

For a time, a massive number of abyssals were blocked out by the divine dream force field. As for those abyssals who had already flown into the Heaven and Man Array, they fell into stupors like flies that had lost their heads. They were caught in the illusions of the divine dream force field, unable to distinguish reality from illusion.

With an overwhelming difference in numbers within the barrier, the abyssals that rushed into the gap were quickly cut down and the Heaven and Man Array was also slowly being restored. But at this time, no one could cheer over this.

Divine Dream’s complexion was pale white without even a hint of blood. She had been wounded again and in any case it would be impossible for her to recover by the time the abyssals attacked next.

Even Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang, and the others were also left in poor conditions. Next time, just what would they use to block the attack of the abyssals?

Had their end finally arrived?

Chapter 2245A – Explosion

The battle reached an unprecedented state of brutality. When the martial artists of the 33 Heavens desperately tried to kill off the abyssals and repair the Heaven and Man Array, eight True Divinity abyssals recklessly rushed through the giant gap!

These eight abyssals seemed unaffected by the divine dream space. Their eyes were blood red and their gazes like those of wild beasts; it seemed they had lost all wisdom and reasoning.

“Be careful!”

Xiao Moxian cried out in alarm. She could feel dark and evil fluctuations of energy within the eight abyssals. She had felt these fluctuations of energy before – this was the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s world strength.

Thinking of the manic, beast-like eyes of these eight True Divinities, Xiao Moxian realized that they were likely puppets controlled by the Demon God’s Tomb Master!

They were just like Deep Child, filled with an absolutely unwavering faith and loyalty towards the Demon God’s Tomb Master and completely unafraid of death!

Just as Xiao Moxian was about to warn everyone about these eight abyssals that wouldn’t fear death, something occurred that left everyone shuddering.

Without a word, the eight True Divinity abyssals plunged towards the 28 True Divinities of the 33 Heavens and exploded without hesitation!

Four abyssals split apart, one each going towards the True Divinities of the primal god race, saint race, human race, as well as the Asura Road.

But the four other abyssals hurtled towards Divine Dream. It was clear they could see that Divine Dream was the true leader of the 33 Heavens and wanted to break down the pillar that held up the hearts of the 33 Heavens martial artists!

“Senior Divine Dream!”

In that instant Xiao Moxian, Mo Eversnow, and Lin Huang all rushed towards Divine Dream. However, the four True Divinities exploding themselves happened too quickly. And with the speed of the explosive force and impact waves, it was simply impossible for Xiao Moxian and the others to stop it.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

The strength from a True Divinity blowing themselves up was incredible. In particular, these True Divinities were controlled by the Soul Emperor so they committed suicide without a second thought, immediately burning away the entirety of their blood vitality and divine soul.

Divine lights shot out. The True Divinities of the 33 Heavens were all drawn into the chaos of the explosion.

“Brother To Bagui!”

On the side of the primal god race, Diwuhen’s body cracked as the impact from the True Divinity explosion struck him! And this was only because the primal god race martial artists had gathered together to block the True Divinity explosion; otherwise, Diwuhen would have likely suffered a grisly death by now. In terms of strength, Diwuhen was still weaker than the abyssal True Divinity who had blown himself up.

The saints were in an even worse state. Even with Soaring Feather’s protection, the saint True Divinities suffered tremendous losses. Astral Vault’s chest was pierced through and another newly promoted saint True Divinity was directly torn apart because his foundation was too shallow.

But the most miserable were Sovereign Heaven Union and Divine Void. They came from the Asura Road and stood in a different camp from the True Divinities of the 33 Heavens. Here, the different True Divinities all stood together on their own sides. When the eight True Divinity abyssals blew themselves up, the True Divinities of each camp had joined together to resist the explosion. But, Sovereign Heaven Union and Divine Void had only the two of them and their strengths were also amongst the weakest.

Moreover, they were both weaker than the abyssal True Divinity who had blown up. Now, as the two of them were sucked into the explosion they both released miserable cries as their mortal bodies were ripped apart and their divine souls were sundered!

But at this moment, no one had time to pay attention to the dead Sovereign Heaven Union and Divine Void; they were all worried about Divine Dream.

Divine Dream bore the brunt of the attack, forced to face off against the strength from four abyssal True Divinities blowing themselves up!

Mo Eversnow and the others were only able to block a little bit of the energy for Divine Dream; the rest had to be withstood by her.

The divine dream space shattered and Divine Dream’s body was stained wet with blood. She was sent flying away like a butterfly with broken wings…

“Senior Divine Dream!”

Xiao Moxian rushed forwards to catch Divine Dream, her eyes filled with worry and anxiousness. In this war, Divine Dream was their central pillar. If something happened to her then morale would plummet.

Divine Dream had wounds upon wounds. Her face was pale like funeral paper and blood flowed out from her mouth and ears.

“Her spiritual sea has been torn and she overdrew her life. It will be impossible for her to restore her combat strength in a short period of time…”

Ink could make out Divine Dream’s current state from a glance. As he did, his heart sank even deeper.

Divine Dream was the pillar of the 33 Heavens. If Divine Dream fell, how could they continue fighting this war?

Now, there was still 10 days left. A powerful ally had appeared on the side of the abyssals, and as for themselves, they had suffered severe losses. Things had become completely disproportionate now, and it was likely they couldn’t even last another day.

“Lin Ming… please hurry…”

Xiao Moxian bit her lips as she glanced at where Lin Ming was in seclusion.

She knew that Lin Ming must have entered the most critical period of his seclusion. If he were to be interrupted at this time then all his previous efforts would end in vain…

Lin Huang and Jiu’er flew forwards and grabbed hold of Xiao Moxian’s hand.

Lin Ming was their final hope. The reason they persisted until now was all in order to allow him to complete his seclusion. But the longer this continued, the more difficult it became...

There was still 10 days remaining. In the lifespan of a True Divinity, 10 days was not even a flicker of time. But now these 10 days had become an impassable moat, a distant goal that seemed unattainable…

Perhaps they would really die here. But if she could die with Lin Ming, then that didn’t seem like something difficult to accept…

Xiao Moxian humorlessly smiled. And at this time, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were processing the corpses of Divine Void, Sovereign Heaven Union, and the newly promoted saint True Divinity.

Three True Divinities had perished and Divine Dream had been grievously wounded. Without a doubt, this was a calamitous turn of events for the 33 Heavens martial artists.

“Divine Void… hah…”

Seeing Divine Void die here, Empyrean Divine Mist was filled with a deep and strange emotion.

Divine Void was Divine Mist’s sworn enemy. Divine Mist had wanted to burn Divine Void’s bones to ashes and refine his soul, but today Divine Void had died and Divine Mist could only feel a sense of grief, completely unable to summon any joyful thoughts.

Divine Void was not a good person. In fact, he was a thankless person who forgot graces and held no virtues. He was extremely selfish and cruel, but today he had died in battle for the 33 Heavens.

This wasn’t what he wanted. Divine Void wasn’t someone with such noble thoughts, but instead was forced to because he had no choice.

In the current 33 Heavens, whether someone walked the righteous path, whether they walked the demonic path, whether or not they had committed countless sins or had taken countless innocent lives, everyone was forced to lay down their pasts and fight for their continued survival. This was because there was no path to escape left for anyone anymore.

The Heaven and Man Array fell into a deathly silence. The atmosphere was filled with an unprecedented level of tenseness!

“Is there nothing else we can do?”

Divine Dream weakly said as she swallowed a pill. She wryly shook her head.

In front of her, the armies of the Dark Abyss were gathering once more!

Just now, they had lost eight True Divinity abyssals in a single breath. But to them, this loss wasn’t anything at all because they still had over 50 True Divinities in their ranks.

Moreover, the four upper True Divinities and ‘Evil’ remained uninjured!

They just needed around a single day to fully restore themselves. That moment would be the end of times for the 33 Heavens!

“Perhaps… perhaps… there might be a way…”

At this time, Clear suddenly spoke up, his voice grim and sad.

But his words actually caused everyone’s hearts to shake.

“What can we do?”

Everyone’s eyes began to shine. Common logic indicated that they had all fallen into a hopelessly dire situation without any chance of survival. But, the one who spoke was Clear, a Guardian of the Asura Road. When people were in desperate straits it was always easy for them to accept a slim chance of hope, no matter how uncertain that hope was. If there was a chance to live, just who would willingly accept death?

“Yin Yang Despair Valley, Forsaken Mortal Tomb…”

Chapter 2246 – Jade-like Gentleman

“Senior Diwuhen…”

As Diwuhen volunteered himself, many of those on the side of the primal god race couldn’t bear to lose him.

Diwuhen was their Patriarch. 20,000 years ago, the primal god race had been invaded by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and the old Patriarch had died in battle. Afterwards, Diwuhen had been left in charge of managing all matters concerning the primal god race, becoming the new Patriarch.

He had silently held this position for 20,000 years. In the face of his race’s extinction, as they stood upon the raging winds and waves, there was no joy and beauty in the position of Patriarch. Rather, to carry this title meant heavy responsibility and immense pressure.

Ink and Clear looked at Diwuhen and sighed inwardly. The Asura Road Master had been of the primal god race in the past, and yet that incomparably powerful primal god race had fallen to such a degree.

“Good… then, we still require one more person…”

As Clear swept his eyes over the other True Divinities, a white-clothed youth quietly stood up. “Then it should be me…”

This calm and indifferent voice caused everyone’s hearts to shake!

“Jun Bluemoon!?”

Everyone was shocked. If one stood out to volunteer with Ink and Clear, then death was certain. Those who chose to step forwards were mostly from the older generation. The younger generation still had glorious times awaiting them. For instance, if Jun Bluemoon were to walk further he could become a middle True Divinity; even an upper True Divinity was within the realm of possibility.

To die like was too great a pity.

“Child, don’t be so impulsive…” Ink wasn’t cruel enough to sacrifice Jun Bluemoon here. He had many higher achievements he could reach.

Jun Bluemoon faintly smiled. “My wounds are heavy and I don’t have much combat strength left remaining. I won’t be able to play much of a role in the future fights to come…”

In the previous battle, Jun Bluemoon had been wounded twice and his injuries were heavy.

Although he was severely wounded his source of life remained uninjured. Like that, it wouldn’t be difficult for him to join forces with Ink and Clear to activate the great array.

Clear and Ink were speechless. They could stop Jun Bluemoon, but who would sacrifice themselves in his place?

It would be a pity if Jun Bluemoon were to die here, but for anyone else, all they had was their life. If they died then they would have nothing at all. They had no right to force anyone to do anything, so the two of them simply didn’t try to discourage Jun Bluemoon anymore.

“You… ah…”

Clear shook his head. “Since this is the decision you have made, I will say no more. The required people have already been gathered. Everyone can have two hours to meditate as well as bid their farewells…”

Ink and Clear sighed as they spoke.

The Empyreans and True Divinities of the 33 Heavens had cultivated for 10,000 years together. In addition to the time enchantment, they knew each other for much longer. It was inevitable that people would form friendships, and if there would be those that died then there would surely be matters to settle beforehand.

Diwuhen called the people of the primal god race to his side and began to state what should happen after his death as well as including who would be the next candidate for the position of Patriarch. His tone was gentle, as if he were simply saying goodbye before leaving for a long trip. Many primal god race martial artists sat in deep worship and veneration, and some martial artists quietly shed tears.

Vast Universe quietly accompanied Divine Dream. The two of them were silent as they passed their final two hours before they would never see each other again together.

Vast Universe looked at Divine Dream’s silhouette, saw the black hair hanging down her forehead. This would be the last time he saw Divine Dream...

From the spiritas, an upper Empyrean passed a jade slip containing all his lifetime of studies to his friend. He bid his friend to keep living and seek out a descendant for him that could continue his legacy.

From the saints, a tall and handsome Empyrean bid his farewells to his wife. His wife was only at the World King boundary and simply didn’t have the qualifications to participate in the battle. She could only throw herself into her husband’s chest and weep tears of sorrow.

From the human race, an Empyrean took out a child that was still swaddled in cloth from her spatial ring. Then, she carefully passed this baby to her friend who had grown with her since childhood and asked her to take good care of her child.

Although she passed her child to her friend, this Empyrean still seemed reluctant to let go of the sleeping baby’s hand. As she looked at the sleeping baby, her eyes were filled with love and attachment…

In various areas, similar scenes were occurring all over.

As for Jun Bluemoon, he quietly stood in a corner by himself, withstanding the loneliness and solitude…

In his arms, there was a white and cute little bunny. Jun Bluemoon stroked the soft and chubby bunny again and again. The small bunny enjoyed this, but it seemed to understand something and then look up at Jun Bluemoon with sadness...

Xiao Moxian quietly looked at Jun Bluemoon. She thought that he was a particularly peculiar character.

Over 20,000 years ago at the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, that was the first time Xiao Moxian met Jun Bluemoon and also the first time she met Lin Ming.

At that time, the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting was basically equivalent to a stage for all Empyrean descendants. Empyrean descendants basically occupied all top ten spots, and it was already a lifetime's worth of honor if a Great World King disciple was able to break into the top 50. As for martial artists from the common people, there were nearly none of them as it was difficult for them to even pass the preliminaries.

However, in such a First Martial Meeting with countless peerless masters and rival geniuses, there were actually two martial artists from the common people that were able to rush into the finals and enter the top 10!

One was Lin Ming and the other was Jun Bluemoon.

Like Lin Ming, Jun Bluemoon had ascended from the lower realms. On the side of the First Martial Meeting he had always been holding onto the furry white bunny and gently stroking it, completely indifferent to all around him.

This little bunny had left a deep impression on Xiao Moxian.

Jun Bluemoon was dressed in white, completely looking like a scholarly youth lost in thought. If this were the mortal world, then there wouldn’t be anyone who thought he was a martial artist from first glance, but would instead think he was some weak and fragile scholar that was preparing to study in imperial examinations.

He had always been silent and collected, and if one were to describe him, it would be – jade-like gentleman.

Afterwards, Jun Bluemoon became a World King, Empyrean, and then stepped into True Divinity, become one of the supreme masters of humanity. Even so, his disposition remained the same as before, without the least bit of arrogance around him.

He joined Mount Potala, becoming a lay disciple. He stood indifferent to worldly sins, approaching buddha with all his heart.

Many of those in the younger generation had broad social circles. Even Dragon Fang had his own friends and had even accepted disciples and married his wife.

But Jun Bluemoon remained a single bachelor his entire life, and he remained untouched by the attraction towards feminine sexuality.

Like this, he lived alone. He seemed to be accustomed to bearing this loneliness, like a sword sealed away in the box. The feeling he gave off was always a simple one, that was completely unpretentious.

For a full hour, Jun Bluemoon continued petting the small bunny in his chest, not speaking a single word.

As the final moments approached, he stood up and looked towards Xiao Moxian.

“Fairy Ji, please help me take care of it…”

Jun Bluemoon passed the small bunny to Xiao Moxian. Then, he took out his sword from his spatial ring and passed it to Xiao Moxian.

“This bunny…” As Xiao Moxian received the small white bunny she held it close to her chest, puzzled. In truth, she had always been confused; just why did Jun Bluemoon bring this small white bunny everywhere with him?

She subconsciously stroked the little white bunny. As she did so, her energies came into contact with the small white bunny and then her heart shook.

This bunny…

She could faintly feel that sealed within this bunny was an extremely weak wisp of remnant soul.

If she carefully probed, she could feel that this was the remnant soul of a woman!

In other words, what she hugged in her chest was simply not a little bunny, but the incarnation of a woman?

Realizing this incredible point, Xiao Moxian looked at Jun Bluemoon, unable to find the words to say.

“She is your…”

As Xiao Moxian looked at Jun Bluemoon, she seemed to suddenly understand many things.

Jun Bluemoon gently traced the little bunny’s head and softly said, “Fairy Ji… if there is a day when Sir Lin can wield the Heavenly Dao and even reverse the cycle of life and death, then I ask you to request Sir Lin to give her a good life…

“This is my final wish… with me alone, I would forever be unable to revive her. But if it is Sir Lin, there might be a slim hope…”

“Just who is she…” Xiao Moxian sucked in a deep breath. The ‘her’ that Jun Bluemoon referred to was naturally the incomparably weak wisp of remnant soul sealed within the bunny. Xiao Moxian didn’t know just what Jun Bluemoon’s story was.

But without a doubt, Jun Bluemoon’s unwavering certainty in stepping forwards was likely related to this mysterious woman’s incarnation. Since he felt that he couldn’t rescue this mysterious woman, then he hoped that once Lin Ming stepped Beyond Divinity he would be able to reverse life and death and revive her.

Xiao Moxian was shocked by all of these realizations.

Jun Bluemoon faintly smiled. Without much else, he only said, “If that isn’t possible, then please bury her and I together…”

Then, Jun Bluemoon turned and walked towards Clear and Ink.

“Wait… wait a moment!”

Xiao Moxian stepped forwards and grabbed onto Jun Bluemoon as well as Clear and Ink. “Seniors, are there really no other means? Will those that join together with you truly die? If I also help, if more people help, can we share the burden and preserve their lives? Even just a little, even just a little bit would be good!”

Chapter 2247 – Reckless

“Preserve their lives?”

Ink and Clear looked at Xiao Moxian and sighed. “I fear that is too difficult. The great array sucks in one’s source of life… if it is all drawn away then a person will die. Even if a little bit of their life source is left over, they will slowly fade away because too much has been taken.”

“If several more people come, that only means there will be several more victims. And if more people sacrifice themselves then just who will fight in the following battles?”

Ink and Clear would work together to summon the ancient overlords that lived 10 billion years ago. But, even if their summoning was successful, they wouldn’t be able to kill off all the abyssals. In the battles to follow, they still needed everyone to work together and it wouldn’t be an easy task at all.

If too many people died here, how could they possibly continue fighting the abyssal demons?

“I understand…”

Xiao Moxian said, her voice bitter. Lin Ming had lost his source soul force in the past and had only managed to slowly restore it through countless tribulations and lucky chances. But, these tribulations and lucky chances might not necessarily be able to be replicated by others.

“Are you prepared?”

Ink and Clear looked towards the many Empyreans and True Divinities.

Their expressions showed that they were already prepared for anything.

“Then let us begin!”

As Ink and Clear spoke, runes began to ripple out beneath their feet…

………..

Even though Lin Ming was deep in seclusion, he was still keenly aware of everything that was occurring outside.

His seclusion had entered its final and also its most crucial stage!

In order to increase the rate of fusion as much as possible, Lin Ming had already become recklessly desperate!

Because of the powerful impacts of energy against his body, his muscles had torn and his hair had scattered. He looked just like a rakshasa that had crawled up from the pits of hell!

“Faster! Just a little bit faster!”

Lin Ming shouted, burning with impatience. That month he spoke of was only an approximation. Currently, he was doing everything to hasten his cultivation and hopefully reduce this time!

Ever since the Asura Road Master blocked the final strike of the Demon God’s Tomb Master, he had fallen into a deep silence. Lin Ming didn’t know what happened to the Asura Road Master nor could he care about it right now.

He only knew that he had to complete his seclusion as fast as possible, otherwise everyone outside would die.

His family, his friends, his wives, even all those fellow comrades of the 33 Heavens who were fighting that gruesome battle up above.

He could not allow these people to die. If he were the only one left alive, then what would be the point of all this?

“Little Black, give me your strength!”

In front of Lin Ming, there was a black dragon that had already shrunk itself to the size of a tiger.

Originally, Lin Ming’s seclusion required 10,000 years. In order to shorten the time needed, Lin Ming had summoned Little Black to the Amethyst Heavenly Palace.

Little Black shared the same roots with Lin Ming, and the energies within Little Black were also inherited from Lin Ming. Between the man and dragon, their energies were completely intertwined.

Thus, for these past years, Little Black had been absorbing energy within the Amethyst Heavenly Palace and then using itself as the medium to transfer this energy to Lin Ming.

If Lin Ming were to absorb energy by himself it would naturally be somewhat slow. But with man and dragon working in tandem, even if Little Black absorbed energy at a rate far slower than Lin Ming, it would still hasten Lin Ming’s speed.

Everything was supposed to happen along a prescribed and orderly path, but now Lin Ming had become desperate.

He reached out a hand and pressed it against Little Black’s chest. His fingers nearly dug into Little Black’s flesh and blood.

Bang!

The energy within Little Black seemed to explode!

Powerful energy flowed out with blood from Little Black’s chest, gushing towards Lin Ming like a dam that had burst open.

“Awu…”

Little Black emitted a low growl of pain. This crazy and wild outpour of energy nearly caused its body to blow up. But, Little Black knew that Lin Ming had entered the most critical period of his seclusion. Let alone pain, even if Little Black were to die here and turn into a mass of flesh and blood on the floor, it would still persist until his final breath to help Lin Ming complete his cultivation.

“Little Black, bear with me!”

Seeing Little Black’s appearance, Lin Ming’s heart was pained. But at this time just what was pain?

Energy wildly broke into Lin Ming’s body. Within this independent world, a powerful attraction force erupted from him, causing the world strength all around him to form a great vortex. And the center of this vortex was Lin Ming.

In this brutal impact of energy, the pain that Lin Ming withstood was no less than Little Black’s. His skin and blood vessels began to crack open as if his body would implode at any moment!

If this were a normal martial artist they would have long since been too scared to continue and would have done everything in their power to stop their cultivation, lest their body explode.

But Lin Ming crazily absorbed energy. He only hated that he couldn’t absorb even more energy at an even faster pace!

“Almost, just a little bit more! Fuse!”

Lin Ming roared out in his heart. His comprehension of Laws was high enough, but in order to completely fuse these two great worlds together what he required was a massive amount of energy.

This energy boiled together, brewing towards the peak of possibility. At this time in the world outside, the earth began to shake.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Mountains toppled over and rivers collapsed. In the nearly dried up Asura Sea, massive cracks began to appear in the seabed. These cracks were fathomless, as if the entire Asura Road would be torn apart.

“This is…”

The martial artists of the 33 Heavens naturally noticed the changes occurring to the Asura Road.

Could this world-breaking scene be related to Lin Ming?

Xiao Moxian’s breath quickened. She looked towards the place where Lin Ming was in seclusion, her eyes unblinking. She prayed in her heart that Lin Ming could pass this final hurdle and leave seclusion!

However, high in the air, the abyssals also saw these changes. They decided to push forwards regardless of the cost.

“Is this all because of that brat Lin Ming?”

“I don’t know, but it doesn’t matter what it is. We must attack now to prevent any future nightmares!”

In the brief battle just now, the abyssals had consumed a great deal of strength. Their original plan was to recuperate a bit before attacking again, but now they couldn’t attend to such things.

The Great Flood Demon Kingdom’s Imperial Scholar crushed a token in his hand. The instant this token crumbled, the eyes of dozens of higher abyssals suddenly turned blood red, just like those eight True Divinities that had blown themselves up.

They were also completely controlled by the Demon God’s Tomb Master. During this raid to kill Lin Ming, the Demon God’s Tomb Master had done everything in his power to ensure the mission would go smoothly. He had sent over a hundred loyal servants here, including 10 True Divinities and dozens of Empyreans.

And now, these servants had lost their ability to act and were then swallowed up by ‘Evil’!

Dozens of Empyrean level abyssals were swallowed up by Evil!

Seeing this scene, Ink and Clear didn’t dare to delay any further. They didn’t know if the changes occurring within the Asura Road were related to Lin Ming or not. If they were, then it might mean Lin Ming had entered the most critical period of his seclusion and they would have to prevent these abyssals from disturbing Lin Ming no matter the cost.

“Begin!”

Ink and Clear shouted out in unison. Their burned all the energy within their bodies, and their life source and blood essence seethed within them.

Around Ink and Clear, the 50 Empyreans and three True Divinities also offered their life energies without hesitation. They could all feel their strength rapidly fading away, but the power of life that gathered became increasingly intense!

Chapter 2249 – Lin Ming Leaves Seclusion

“His Majesty the Human Sovereign! The Human Sovereign has left seclusion?”

At this time, many martial artists of the 33 Heavens started to realize this possibility. The great earthquakes occurring throughout the Asura Road might be an indicator of Lin Ming leaving his seclusion.

That was right… everyone had heard that the Human Sovereign had to fuse with the Asura Road and Akashic Dream Universe. Although they didn’t understand how this could occur or the specifics, if the Asura Road was fused by Lin Ming then perhaps it disintegrating because he left seclusion was possible…

“These wretches, just what are they babbling about!”

On the side of the abyssal army, the four demon kings all had incredibly ugly complexions. At this time they also realized that the most likely possibility was that Lin Ming had emerged!

“Don’t panic!”

At this time, several upper True Divinity abyssals barely managed to maintain their calm. “Although Lin Ming has left seclusion, he might not have stepped Beyond Divinity. Don’t forget – he has been wounded by the Lord Demon God!”

“Right, that’s right.”

As the abyssals spoke amongst themselves, the earth began to continually crack. Divine light shot out and a pair of massive black wings stretched out, covering the entire bed of the Asura Sea like titanic black clouds!

These were the wings of a black dragon!

Ao - !

A resonant dragon’s cry pierced into the highest heavens. Within the storm of energy, two cold lights shot out like a divine sword, thrusting into the skies and leaving the mind shaking.

Lin Ming had most likely left seclusion!

And those two cold lights were his burning gaze!

“Lin Ming!”

“Lin Ming!!”

The moment that Lin Ming appeared, the four demon kings stepped back in the skies, their pupils shrinking.

This fear came from Lin Ming’s aura!

The aura was from the countless victories that Lin Ming had accumulated, from the countless powerhouses that had been felled by his hand, from the blood of all the proud sons of heaven who he had slain, this was an emperor’s majesty that Lin Ming had cast himself!

The four demon kings were awed and horrified. They drew back again and again, a cold chill running down their backs. None of them were able to summon the courage to face Lin Ming!

There were too many legends concerning Lin Ming. Moreover, he was an opponent that even the Demon God’s Tomb Master somewhat feared. Before they even fought, they were already terrified in the depths of their hearts!

The storm of energy faded away. A thousand mile long black dragon stood above the ruined earth, and Lin Ming stood alone above the dragon’s head, a spear in his hands!

His body was straight and tall but his appearance left one startled.

He no longer appeared youthful and majestic, shining like a jade sculpture. Instead, his body was thin and his skin was charred black as if he had exhausted his blood vitality.

When the Demon God’s Tomb Master’s final strike destroyed the Amethyst Heavenly Palace, it had also caused Lin Ming to appear in everyone’s vision for a brief period of time. Back then, he still had this burnt appearance and it had left everyone worried. Would Lin Ming have received some sort of irrecoverable wound?

Now that his seclusion had ended and he emerged, everyone thought that he would be restored to the appearance of his peak state. But his body was still like before…

Not only was Lin Ming’s figure thin and withered but his long hair lay scattered across his head like chopped grass. This spirit treasure clothing he wore had been torn to pieces, leaving nothing but rags hanging off his body.

With Lin Ming’s current appearance, all of the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were left with heavy hearts. Did Lin Ming complete his fusion of heaven and man? Had he been severely wounded? If so, then how much combat strength would he have remaining?

“Hehe! I thought that you completed your seclusion and stepped Beyond Divinity, but you are nothing but a dried up well, a lamp that has lost all oil!”

Seeing Lin Ming’s appearance, Deep King Road’s Sovereign laughed out loud, seeming to have found his courage again.

That was right. The Lord Demon God’s attack had been horrifying. In order to send out an attack of such strength, the Lord Demon God had sacrificed strength that he had accumulated for many years. Lin Ming had been forced to withstand that attack so how could he not be injured?

And even the Asura Road Master likely had his soul turned to ashes! Otherwise, why would he have disappeared?

Lin Ming was strong, but no matter how strong he was could he be stronger than the Lord Demon God?

“Stop with the act. Did you think we wouldn’t know that your seclusion needed 10,000 years to complete, and even if you were given 10,000 years you still might not be able to succeed? Now, only 9900 years have passed, so how could you have finished?”

The Great Flood Demon Kingdom Imperial Scholar tamped down the fear in his heart and stepped forwards towards Lin Ming.

“Your seclusion was interrupted by the Lord Demon God and you suffered a backlash. Now, you are likely suffering from a deficiency in blood vitality and even if your aura is like this, just how much combat strength do you truly have left over? The reason you forcefully left seclusion now is because you know that not leaving is only a road to death. So, how is it? How does it feel to fail right before you reach the end?”

The four demon kings all spoke one after another and agreed with each other. The more they spoke, the more they suspected that their words were correct. Not only did Lin Ming’s cultivation not rise but his strength fell instead!

And on the side of the 33 Heavens, all the martial artists held their breath. They were worried for Lin Ming, and seeing the abyssals forcing their way forwards once more, they subconsciously moved in front of Lin Ming and continued to activate the Heaven and Man Array.

At this time, not even Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang, or Jiu’er, knew what Lin Ming was thinking. He was like a mass of dense fog, leaving one completely unable to understand him.

Then the black dragon whipped its wings and flew into the skies.

Lin Ming stood on top of the dragon, flying closer and closer to the abyssals!

Seeing Lin Ming fly towards them, the four demon kings were horrified. Although they had all spoken rampant and arrogant words, the truth was that it was merely a front and they were actually afraid in their hearts. They actually had no idea just how injured Lin Ming was.

“Attack him, destroy him!” A demon king gnashed out.

They had no other choice. Even if they didn’t want to face Lin Ming, he has already left seclusion. So, would they even be able to escape?

Moreover, even if they managed to escape from Lin Ming’s grasp, even if they returned to the Dark Abyss the Lord Demon God would likely punish them with a fate worse than death.

“Evil, rush forwards!”

The four demon kings came to a tacit understanding with each other. At this time, none of them dared to attack themselves. Rather, they activated the seal planted within Evil’s soul, taking control of it and sending it into a suicidal explosion against Lin Ming; this was the safest method to deal with him.

But the total amount of energy within Evil was terrifying. If it were to explode, it would be no different from a supernova, destroying all!

With its soul seal activated, Evil was completely controlled. Its eyes turned blood red and with a loud roar it rushed towards Lin Ming.

“Just die. With so many of our people being buried with you and even a totem level abyssal dying with you, you should be more than content!”

“Someone like you should have lived a glorious and heroic life, but what a pity you encountered the Lord Demon God and are doomed to be destroyed!”

Several demon kings roared out loud, trying to convince themselves and pump up their courage. They crazily poured their energies into Evil, and Evil began to rapidly expand like a balloon!

At this time, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were able to see Evil about to explode. If such a giant totem level abyssal were to explode, the force behind that would be unimaginable.

But Lin Ming’s complexion remained as calm and serene as before. Facing the menacing Evil whose body ballooned more and more, Lin Ming simply reached out a hand and gently and slowly grasped the void!

“Ahhhh!”

The four demon kings that were pouring their energies into Evil suddenly cried out in alarm. In that instant they were able to feel their energy and divine sense severed by a terrifying strength. Then, they stared helplessly on as the planet-sized Evil seemed to be grasped by a giant invisible hand and compressed!

Peng!

After Evil’s head was squeezed to the limit, it directly blasted open!

Evil’s flesh and blood also scattered in all directions as its entire body disintegrated!

This was not an explosion of energy but an explosion of pure flesh and blood. The moment Lin Ming reached out his hand, all of the energies within Evil’s body had been controlled by Lin Ming and it was left unable to explode itself at all!

Blood gushed out like an erupting volcano, recklessly falling all over the skies. Evil’s flesh and blood was crushed to goo as it started to flow out from its broken body. Sounds of Evil’s cracking skull filled the world.

This was a horrifying sound, one left that one’s scalp tingling with fear!

The four demon kings all stared at this scene with wide eyes, their palms wet with sweat. Turbulent waves rose up in their hearts!

They already expected that Lin Ming was strong, likely very strong, but they never imagined he could make such an attack.

The massive planet-sized Evil that had such a hard skull protecting it was actually… pinched to death?

Chapter 2250 – World Destruction Spear

When it came to Evil being killed by Lin Ming, the truth was that the abyssals weren’t shocked. Before the attack began they had already planned for the worst case scenario.

If Evil couldn’t severely wound Lin Ming by self-explosion and simply died, then that wouldn’t be strange. Evil could be pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear or even overwhelmed with an even greater amount of energy. There were all sorts of possibilities for how Lin Ming could defeat Evil.

But, they never thought that the massive, planet-sized Evil would actually be pinched to death by Lin Ming no differently from a frog!

Just what kind of abnormal strength was this!?

Now it seemed that Lin Ming had likely completed his seclusion.

In other words, he had stepped into the realm Beyond Divinity!

When one’s strength reached the peak of True Divinity and when one’s Laws simultaneously reached perfection, then one would be able to step into this boundary. This was the same boundary that the Asura Road Master, Immortal Sovereign, and Demon God stood upon!

“What do we do?” The higher abyssals turned to the four demon kings, all of them panicked as they searched for help. But, the four demon kings were also left at a loss for what to do. Facing Lin Ming, they were no different from a bunch of ants in front of a lion!

“How could he have left seclusion so early? He had to withstand several attacks from the Lord Demon God, so how could he possibly have completed his seclusion!?”

A demon king roared out in unwillingness. But no matter how much he roared, it was all meaningless; Lin Ming was already rushing towards them!

Or, it was more accurate to say that he only took a single step forwards to instantaneously teleport in front of the abyssal army. His figure was relatively smaller compared to the abyssals’, but for the abyssals right now, the Lin Ming in front of them was no different from a god that stood upon the highest heavens!

The four demon kings all held their breath.

The pressure emitting from Lin Ming was simply too great, so heavy that it left them gasping for breath. Their hands and feet turned cold and their shoulders seemed to carry a weight so immense that they couldn’t help but kneel down in the air.

They had already lost all courage to resist Lin Ming.

“Wait… don’t attack us, I will recognize you as my lord and master…”

An abyssal grit out from between clenched teeth, unable to resist the pressure. He hoped that there was some glimmer of a chance that Lin Ming could let him be and simply plant a slave seal in his body.

For martial artists, living with a slave seal planted within them was a fate worse than death. The four demon kings were certainly unwillingly to exchange their lives to live on as slaves, but now, it was likely that Lin Ming would fight the Demon God’s Tomb Master in a final battle.

If Lin Ming controlled them and was killed by the Demon God’s Tomb Master later, then wouldn’t their freedom also be restored?

Hearing the cunning suggestions of these abyssals, Lin Ming only smiled. He reached out a hand. The many abyssals sucked in a breath as they saw this, unsure what Lin Ming was planning to do.

Would he plant a slave seal in them? Or would he kill them?

Facing this dark star Lin Ming that could even pinch Evil to death, none of them dared to escape. Thinking about it, Lin Ming only needed to open a force field to completely trap them like flies in a spider’s web, unable to escape at all.

From the heavens and earth of the universe, infinite energy began to condense in Lin Ming’s hand, becoming increasingly strong!

This terrifying amount of energy left the abyssals stunned. Just what was Lin Ming planning to do?

When Lin Ming killed Evil he had simply needed to reach out his hand and grasp the air. He hadn’t condensed energy at all. To kill the abyssals, he didn’t need such extravagant motions.

It wasn’t just the abyssal demons, but even the martial artists of the 33 Heavens were left puzzled. As Lin Ming gathered more and more strength in his hand, the Asura Road beneath their feet began to disintegrate at an increasing pace!

A crack of unprecedented size began to race through the middle of the Asura Road!

The Asura Road was long and linear, just like a straight road. This was where its name had come from. And now, a massive lengthwise fissure was spreading through the Asura Road!

This fissure was millions of miles wide and countless billions of miles long. From start to end, the entire Asura Road was cracked open!

The Asura Road had been divided in two!

Magma started to gush out from deep underground, forming turbulent waves that rose up into the skies. The void collapsed and disappeared. Massive mineral lodes broke apart, turned into the purest form of energy that was absorbed by some unknown existence. The various mystic lands that dotted the landscape, the innumerable danger zones, all of them fell apart!

The Asura Road was being destroyed!

This was true destruction!

This level of destruction left everyone stunned. “This is…”

“Look below!”

Someone suddenly cried out in alarm. They discovered that the fissure that had broken through the Asura Road wasn’t fathomless at all. Rather, deep deep down, one could see something shimmering with an icy cold light.

There was actually a giant cylinder buried deep in the Asura Road.

This cylinder shined with a metallic luster and was abnormally long. If one used the divine sense of a True Divinity to probe this cylinder, they would discover that it extended from one end of the Asura Road to the other!

“What is that!?”

“This is…”

Everyone, whether they were abyssals or martial artists of the 33 Heavens, were all shocked speechless. Beneath the earth of the Asura Road, there was actually a giant metal cylinder!

Could this giant metal cylinder by the reason for the Asura Road’s shape?

The Asura Road was indeed formed in an extremely strange shape. Normally, when one formed their own world it would be in the shape of a square or circle, giving it an overall comprehensive and whole feel, unlike the long ‘road’ that was the Asura Road.

The earth completely disintegrated and countless mountains and rivers broke apart into dust and ashes. The sea vanished into mist and the entire Asura Road finally and completely shattered, placing the metal cylinder in full view of all.

It was unimaginably huge, like a divine pillar that supported the entirety of the 33 Heavens. And at the end of this divine pillar was an icy sharp edge, one that was dark and glossy, fierce and horrible, like a peerless weapon!

…Weapon?

Could it be…

This thought suddenly lit up in everyone’s mind. This giant cylinder was actually a pole, a spear that had been enlarged countless times over!

“Heavens!”

People couldn’t help but cry out in alarm. The divine spear that could pierce through the cosmos had been buried beneath the Asura Road!

It was even possible that the Asura Road itself was formed by this divine spear. Or, it could be that the Asura Road Master’s ultimate goal in creating the Asura Road was to utilize the infinite destiny and resources accumulated over 10 billion years, to use the blood of all those outstanding elites that had sprinkled upon the earth, to forge this divine spear!

This was the reason for the Asura Road’s strange shape!

The spear began to shrink and shrink again. Lin Ming looked towards this ultimate divine weapon that floated in the void.

This was a spear capable of destroying a world!

And what he wanted to destroy was the world of the Demon God’s Tomb.

To use a world as a weapon to destroy another world!

Just what sort of crazy idea was this!?

However, for Lin Ming, this weapon was still incomplete. He began to condense energy once more. Through the countless layers of space, the already refined Akashic Dream Universe also began to disintegrate!

The Akashic Dream Universe was created by Immortal Sovereign. It was originally an incomparably massive spiritual world without any true physically substantive life inside. And when Lin Ming began to refine the Akashic Dream Universe, the spiritas had already severed their spiritual connection with the world.

The giant Akashic Dream Universe began to shrink and shrink again.

In the boundless sea of stars, the Akashic Dream Universe finally turned into the phantom of a great spiritual god. Its body was hazy and dim, completely blurry, simply unable to be seen clearly.

This spiritual god phantom passed through layers of the universe, stepping through space until finally arriving in front of Lin Ming!

This phantom seemed to be Lin Ming’s own incarnation. At this moment, Lin Ming seemed to have become a true and legitimate god, wielding the Heavenly Dao and controlling the cycle of samsara.

The Akashic Dream Universe had disintegrated and turned into this divine phantom?

Whether it was the abyssals or martial artists of the 33 Heavens, they were all shocked. This divine phantom was…

As everyone was lost in shock and awe, that giant divine phantom turned into a flow of light that fused into the World Destruction Spear!

Divine light burned like a conflagration of flames. The endless starlight in the universe seemed to converge at this moment, all of it swallowed up by that pitch black spear. This feeling was as if this spear had sucked out all the energy in the universe!

“That divine phantom is…”

The voices of the four demon kings shivered. They wanted to flee, but beneath the immense pressure they couldn’t even move their bodies. Moreover, they felt as if the energy within their bodies would be drawn out by this demonic spear.

This divine phantom finally fused together perfectly with the World Destruction Spear.

This caused everyone to recall something…

“Is that… an artifact spirit!?”

This thought flashed through Divine Dream’s mind. To use the Asura Road to forge the body and then cast in the artifact spirit with the Akashic Dream Universe!

Were all of these things arranged earlier, or was it done by Lin Ming himself?

Or, could it be that this was the Asura Road Master’s original plan, and after Lin Ming fused together the highest Laws of heaven and man, he had finally managed to complete the last step!

To thoroughly refine two great worlds and use these two worlds as the main source to forge his own life weapon, this was the method Lin Ming used to refine these worlds!

“Since ancient times, ever since a peerless divine weapon has been born it must drink blood. On this day, I forge this spear and bring it into existence. All of you shall be its blood sacrifice!”

Lin Ming said, indifferently looking at the thousands of abyssals before him as well as the 30 some abyssal True Divinities.

Lin Ming’s gaze seemed to overlook all of existence, bringing with it a pressure that could not be defied!

“Ahhh!”

The abyssals were frightened beyond compare. Using their final ounce of strength, they scattered in all directions in hopes of escape. But beneath the force field and pressure, how could they possibly escape?

The long spear broke through the void, piercing through the heavens. Screams sounded out one after another. The thousands of abyssals began to explode beneath the pressure of the terrifying strength, their blood blooming like flowers in the sky!

Even the four demon kings were unable to resist. In the end, they also suffered the fate of a cruel death.

These were enchanting blooms of blood formed from thousands of abyssals dying in unison. Such a scene shocked the heart and mind!

It had to be known that every splash of blood came from a peerless abyssal master!

Such a scene hadn’t even occurred in the ancient war 10 billion years ago!

All of the blood, even Evil’s flesh and blood, was all absorbed by the World Destruction Spear.

In that originally pitch black spear, a faint red luster appeared!

With the Asura Road as the spear body and the Akashic Dream Universe as the spear soul, this was a weapon that had been refined for 10 billion years and cast using the two highest Laws.

With the blood sacrifice of 8000 Empyreans and 30 some True Divinities, Lin Ming used his Beyond Divinity strength to wield this World Destruction Spear!

Pa!

It finally shrank into a normal-sized spear that fell into Lin Ming’s hand!

Lin Ming slowly turned around, his eyes like cold arcs of electricity. He looked at a place deep in the void, fighting spirit gushing out from him like a burning star.

Chapter 2251 – Your Era Has Been Ended

At this moment, Lin Ming could feel his body filled with endless strength. The World Destruction Spear in his hands could be called a weapon, but in truth it was no different from a part of his body. It was as close to him as his flesh and blood, and whether it was his aura, divine soul, inner world, life wave fluctuations, spirit mark, everything that made him was cast as one with this spear, completely inalienable!

With a thought, Lin Ming’s body directly integrated into the World Destruction Spear.

Lin Ming vanished; man and spear had become one!

Rumble rumble rumble!

At the point of the World Destruction Spear, thunder and flame wildly gushed out. Endless fog appeared in the void and a black hole-like space channel appeared in front of the World Destruction Spear.

Storms howled through the void. The World Destruction Spear suddenly flew out, passing through the world, tearing through stars.

As it vanished through the space channel, it seemed to carry away all the energy in the universe.

“Lin Ming…”

Looking at the direction that Lin Ming disappeared in, the martial artists of the 33 Heavens held their breath.

At this time, they had already guessed just what Lin Ming was planning to do. Lin Ming wanted to engage the Demon God’s Tomb Master in a final showdown. This would be the last battle, one whose result would determinate the future of the 33 Heavens!

For Lin Ming, the layers of space existed in name only. As he passed through space, distance lost all meaning. He shattered through space barriers again and again. The God Lamenting Wall isolated out the different Heavens of the 33 Heavens, and this was a barrier that even True Divinities found difficult to overcome. But to Lin Ming, the God Lamenting Wall was as frail as glass!

He quickly flew from the Asura Road, through the ancient universe, and into the skies above the Dark Abyss!

Infinite killing intent burst out from their eyes. The World Destruction Spear came crashing down!

Kacha!

The World Destruction Spear pierced through the skies of the Dark Abyss, flew through the world and plummeted into the black earth!

This spear was like a coiling dragon column that fell down from the highest nine heavens. It broke through all barriers, an unstoppable force. The heavy black earth was pierced through by the divine spear, and the first level of the Dark Abyss was forcefully ripped open!

The Dark Abyss was formed by 18 independent spaces superimposed upon each other. The earth of the first level was the skies of the second.

As the World Destruction Spear tore through the earth of the first level, it also ripped open the heavens of the second.

Because of the massive opening, endless world strength began to flow out. For Lin Ming who had cultivated the inner and outer universes to the extreme, who comprehended the highest Laws and who had also reached the boundary of fusing together heaven and man, absorbing the world strength that leaked out from the Dark Abyss was no problem at all!

Thus, while the World Destruction Spear pierced through the first level of the Dark Abyss, the waves of energy winded backwards, and all the endless energy that flowed forth from the Dark Abyss’s first level was absorbed by the World Destruction Spear!

The earth cracked apart, skies turned dark gray, and the seas dried up. The entire Dark Abyss seemed to have all of its spiritual energy completely siphoned away.

After absorbing this strength, the World Destruction Spear became increasingly powerful. Without slowing in the least, it broke into the seas of the Dark Abyss’s second level!

The seas were sundered and massive 10,000 mile waves rose up. The Dark Abyss’s second level was also pierced through!

By absorbing the world strength, the World Destruction Spear became increasingly fierce, increasingly powerful!

Thunderclaps rolled through the world. Storms swept across the void. Layer after layer of the Dark Abyss was broken open. Lin Ming fused together with World Destruction Spear, fusing together infinite strength in this strike. Finally, he pierced through the Dark Abyss’s 17th layer and arrived at the space of the Demon God’s Tomb!

Lin Ming clearly remembered the warning that Immortal Sovereign had given him before he left the Demon God’s Tomb – the Demon God’s Tomb Master was able to control everything within the Demon God’s Tomb, and was the absolute ruler of that land. He must never fight the Demon God’s Tomb Master within the Demon God’s Tomb, unless he had the ability to break apart the world of the Demon God’s Tomb!

Just how firm was the Demon God’s Tomb? This was a world that had survived the great Shattering of the last universe.

But today, Lin Ming would pierce through it!

Lin Ming’s spear was named the World Destruction Spear, and the world it would destroy was the world of the Demon God’s Tomb!

The Demon God’s Tomb Master had fused together with the Demon God’s Tomb. As long as this world was destroyed then the foundation of his strength would also be ruined. This was the best and only method to defeat the Demon God’s Tomb Master!

“Break!”

Lin Ming gave a deep roar, his voice echoing straight into the Dark Abyss’s 18th level!

The totality of Lin Ming’s strength was condensed into this strike. He had poured the entirety of his lifetime of Laws and all of his cultivation into this attack!

Bang!

The point of the World Destruction Spear thoroughly pierced through the world barrier of the Demon God’s Tomb. A beam of divine light passed through the world, as if the sword of a spiritual god was breaking it apart.

Energy scattered outwards, forming horrifyingly large explosions. It was like the great Shattering of the universe had arrived early. Endlessly energy storms swept out, completely disintegrating the 18th layer of the Dark Abyss!

The Demon God’s Tomb was torn apart by Lin Ming.

Today, this world that was said to be indestructible was actually broken apart by Lin Ming!

In that moment, a powerful impact of energy rushed out from the Demon God’s Tomb, causing Lin Ming’s body to shake and nearly vomit out a mouthful of blood.

Rich world strength burned all around Lin Ming. Fused together as one with the World Destruction Spear, he was like a burning meteor as he crashed down into the boundless earth, pounding open a terrifying pit that was millions of miles deep!

Rumble rumble rumble –

The vault of heaven collapsed and the earth caved in. This apocalyptic scene was like the end of times had arrived.

As the world began to break apart, the originally indestructible Demon God’s Tomb suddenly became frail.

Lin Ming shot out from the massive pit. As he rose up with his scattered hair, he was like a newly born war god!

Pa pa pa!

Burnt black skin cracked and fell off from Lin Ming’s body, rustling down all around him.

Lin Ming lifted the World Destruction Spear, stepping forwards one step at a time. His originally dried and withered mortal body began to shine after the old skin fell off, becoming as glorious and beautiful as jade.

“You’re done for! You have lived for far too long. Your era has been ended, by me!”

Lin Ming looked at the surging energy in front of him – this was… the Emperor Bone Sea!

Dense infernal energy and death energy gushed out from the Emperor Bone Sea, recklessly filling the air.

Lin Ming could clearly feel the pained cries of ancient souls as well as that abyssal’s demonic aura!

Death energy became increasingly rich before turning into black smoke that was visible to the naked eye. The black smoke began to rise up like an inferno.

An old man with a head of sparse white hair emerged from the black smoke. His body was as thin as a skeleton and his eyes were filthy. His complexion was that of a dying man, of fading embers.

He was like a dried corpse that had been slumbering in a grave for 100 billion years. Step by step, he moved towards Lin Ming, his movements stiff and awkward.

As this old man saw Lin Ming, dreadful waves of killing intent flashed out from his filthy eyes!

Seeing this hideous and grotesque Demon God, Lin Ming coldly smiled. “It looks like… in the end you were unable to achieve eternal life. You had fused together with the Demon God’s Tomb, but unfortunately, the Demon God’s Tomb has been destroyed by me. Because the universal system here has collapsed, the energy that was bound by it has also escaped. With your life forcing having been drained, you can no longer fuse with the Demon God’s Tomb. You are done for!”

“Jejejeje!” The Demon God bizarrely cackled, as if he had gone completely insane. “If I kill you and swallow you alive I can still make up for all the vitality I lost! I can still repair the Demon God’s Tomb! Now die!”

Chapter 2254 – Epilogue (1)

In the 33 Heavens, at the intersection point between the Divine Realm and Saint Convocation Heavens, there existed a newly established great world.

This world had a history of a mere 200,000 years so far and was called the Human Sovereign World.

It was a world created by the Human Sovereign Lin Ming. It was made using his total lifetime of studies, his Laws of heaven and man, as well as the infinite essence energy gathered from the 33 Heavens and Dark Abyss.

This world was even broader than the Asura Road of the past. It was a holy land which every genius of the 33 Heavens yearned to visit!

In the Human Sovereign World there were many precious cultivating training areas as well as many popular trial lands that people chased after in packs. When Lin Ming established the system of rules in this world, he included the wonderful mysteries of the Asura Road as well as the spiritual spaces of the Akashic Dream Universe.

Many geniuses sharpened their weapons and hearts, putting forth every effort and thought into struggling to obtain a single spot to enter the smelting trials of the Human Sovereign World.

This was a world created by that god-like existence of the 33 Heavens. He was a character who had climbed to the highest Laws of martial arts, and the trial spaces he created held all sorts of lucky chances and unbelievable treasures. It was so rich in resources that it was hard for the average man to imagine them.

If one could obtain just a tiny bit of these treasures then it would be an inestimable benefit to a martial artist’s future road of cultivation.

Not to mention the geniuses of the younger generation, even Empyreans and True Divinities wished to obtain certain inheritances.

However, quotas for the Human Sovereign World’s trials were extremely rare. Although the Human Sovereign World was incredibly broad the number of trial lands was limited. Within the 33 Heavens, there was humanity, the saints, the spiritas, as well as the ancient races. With all the various races added together there was a countless number of races and wanting to bloom brightly amongst them was easier said than done!

“I finally did it… I finally obtained a Human Sovereign Token!”

Within a large city in the Human Sovereign World, three youths were excitedly chatting with each other. All of them wore the uniform clothing of a sect.

After entering the Human Sovereign World, there were many trials and tests that one could take, and once one’s results reached a certain degree they could obtain a Human Sovereign Token!

With a Human Sovereign Token, one could enter the Human Sovereign Pagoda. The Human Sovereign Pagoda was the final trial land that Lin Ming created, and it was similar to the Asura Road’s final trial of the past.

The Asura Road’s final trial utilized the completion percentage as a tool for evaluation, and the Human Sovereign Pagoda was also the same.

When Lin Ming created the Human Sovereign World, he emulated many settings and rules that were once in the Asura Road; this was all done in commemoration of the Asura Road Master.

A great deal of energy and time had been spent in creating this world. One reason he did this was to obtain an even more perfect boundary of Heaven and Man by observing the process of creating a world. Another reason was to create more opportunities and allow the younger generation of the 33 Heavens to grow.

Through the many years that Lin Ming cultivated the martial path he had obtained many comprehensions into martial arts and also learned of far too many cultivation methods. All of these things were precious treasures.

Lin Ming didn’t plan to discriminate against anyone. As long as one possessed the talent and will, they could obtain these inheritances!

Inheritances were far too important. If one had to investigate the reason as to why the great calamity 200,000 years ago had been so brutal and tragic, the main reason would be because of the vast difference in strength between the Dark Abyss and the races of the 33 Heavens. If it weren’t for Lin Ming being able to turn the tides of the war just in time, then the 33 Heavens would surely have been destroyed.

Thus, Lin Ming wanted to restore the martial arts civilization of the 33 Heavens to the level that it reached 10 billion years ago, or even surpass that standard.

If the martial world was bright and strong then masters would pour forth from the ranks of the 33 Heavens. Like this, Lin Ming would have no need to take action himself; the 33 Heavens would have the ability to resist other unknown calamities in the future.

Because of this, Lin Ming had spared no effort when he created the Human Sovereign World. In particular when he was making the final Human Sovereign Pagoda, Lin Ming had come up with all possible means to create all sorts of exquisite tests and trials and also laid down rich rewards without hesitation.

This was why the Human Sovereign Pagoda became the ultimate smelting trial that countless elites fervently wished for. There were all sorts of incomparably precious cultivation methods and heavenly materials inside that could make one’s eyes go red with jealousy. Not just that, but if one’s completion percentage was high enough then they could listen to that person give a lecture about the Laws, or there was even a chance to become that person’s secret disciple!

Compared to mere treasures, becoming that person’s secret disciple was a lucky chance that one couldn’t even imagine dreaming of.

Treasures could be used for a while, but becoming that person’s secret disciple was a glory that could be enjoyed for a lifetime.

Whether one was a common martial artist or whether one was a proud son of heaven that came from a large sect, nothing mattered in front of that person. One’s past status was utterly meaningless, because that person stood at far too high a height. Compared to a towering mountain, a speck of sand was not much different from a tiny piece of gravel.

As long as one could become that person’s secret disciple then they could leap to the heavens in a single jump!

However, these three young disciples that just managed to obtain a Human Sovereign Token clearly didn’t entertain these fanciful dreams. They had already exerted themselves to their limit in order to obtain a single qualification token to enter the Human Sovereign Pagoda, and wanting to become that person’s disciple with their talent was no different from a moron babbling nonsense.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, how high do you think our completion percentage will be?” A disciple excitedly said, his face filled with anticipation.

“Fifty something percent. It will be hard to reach any higher…”

The Elder Senior-apprentice Brother shook his head. His words left the other two stunned. “Only fifty some percent? Would it really be that low?”

The three of them were famous figures from their native great world. Although they didn’t have much hope of grabbing the spotlight once they reached the Human Sovereign World, 50 some percent seemed a bit too low…

“It should be around that much.” The Elder Senior-apprentice Brother shrugged. “Cloudmoon should know…”

“I naturally know.”

Cloudmoon came from the same great world as these three disciples. She was a proud daughter of heaven from that great world, and compared to these three disciples, she surpassed them in strength and talent. Even her looks were like those of a fairy maiden.

With all of these factors combined together, Cloudmoon’s fame in her native great world far outstripped these three disciples.

“Cloudmoon just barely managed to obtain a 60 percent completion rate. The rules of the Human Sovereign World state that one needs to obtain a completion rate above 90 in order to become a disciple of His Majesty the Human Sovereign. Those that obtain a completion rate above 85 can become his secret disciple, and those that obtain a completion rate above 70 can listen to His Majesty the Human Sovereign lecture about the Dao once. Further down from that, there aren’t any more rewards… Cloudmoon’s goal is also to enter the Human Sovereign Palace and listen to that person speak of the Dao.”

“That is…” Listening to their senior-apprentice brother’s words, the two other disciples were left dispirited.

This was far too difficult!

“It is that difficult. Even if one obtains a completion rate of 70, being able to listen to His Majesty the human Sovereign lecture about the Dao isn’t easy at all. I hear that His Majesty hasn’t given a lecture about the Dao for the last 200 years…”

“Oh? Why is that?” The two disciples were left speechless. To hold a single discussion once every 200 or so years, that was far too infrequent.

“His Majesty must cultivate… I heard that he has recently gone into seclusion…”

“Cultivate?”

The two disciples glanced at each other, puzzled. They both felt this was a bit unbelievable. “His Majesty the Human Sovereign already became the number one figure in the universe 200,000 years ago. Even the Demon God was slain by His Majesty. In the heavens and earth, there is no one whose strength can compare to even a single percent of His Majesty. So, why is he still desperately cultivating?”

“Mm… the road of martial arts diverges in myriad paths without any end. It isn’t some secret that His Majesty the Human Sovereign has been bitterly cultivating all this time. It is said that His Majesty has two wishes and with his current strength he cannot fulfill these two wishes…”

“Even His Majesty cannot fulfill these two wishes?”

The two disciples were left stunned. Just what sort of wishes were these that even that god-like character wouldn’t be able to complete them?